[[{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government needs to ____ its tax proposals. They are less than clear to most people.", "Opt_1": "threaten", "Opt_2": "consent", "Opt_3": "clarify", "Opt_4": "differentiate", "Answer": "clarify", "Opt_1_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_2_def": "to agree", "Opt_3_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_4_def": "to make different; to see the difference"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Dr. Pruitt said that he was very confident that all aspects of the law, as well as any other concerns, would be closely looked at ____ to any deal being made.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you have the amnio test late in pregnancy and are carrying a baby with Downs Syndrome, it will be too late to ____ the pregnancy.", "Opt_1": "terminate", "Opt_2": "reveal", "Opt_3": "associate", "Opt_4": "consent", "Answer": "terminate", "Opt_1_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_3_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_4_def": "to agree"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I have a ____ idea why she has been absent, but I'm not sure.", "Opt_1": "vague", "Opt_2": "pure", "Opt_3": "artificial", "Opt_4": "extraordinary", "Answer": "vague", "Opt_1_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_2_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_3_def": "not real or natural", "Opt_4_def": "very unusual"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ family is expected to drive past the school tomorrow morning. The children will be standing by the road waving flags.", "Opt_1": "genuine", "Opt_2": "royal", "Opt_3": "loose", "Opt_4": "competent", "Answer": "royal", "Opt_1_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_2_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_3_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_4_def": "good at something (often a job)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The explanation for this extraordinary decision lies in the immediate ____ surrounding the creation of the United Nations.", "Opt_1": "obligation", "Opt_2": "relationship", "Opt_3": "dispute", "Opt_4": "circumstances", "Answer": "circumstances", "Opt_1_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_2_def": "the way to things are connected", "Opt_3_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_4_def": "situation"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Frankfurt International School needs to ____ its curriculum with that of German state schools.", "Opt_1": "investigate", "Opt_2": "interact", "Opt_3": "exist", "Opt_4": "align", "Answer": "align", "Opt_1_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_2_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_3_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_4_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "For some years in the UK personal computers have been used to provide sensory stimulation in schools for children with ____ and multiple learning difficulties.", "Opt_1": "chief", "Opt_2": "profound", "Opt_3": "deficient", "Opt_4": "medium", "Answer": "profound", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_3_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_4_def": "in the middle"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Major Smith occupied the city as ordered but was unable to ____ the bridge, lacking both a drill and powder.", "Opt_1": "commit", "Opt_2": "behave", "Opt_3": "destroy", "Opt_4": "yield", "Answer": "destroy", "Opt_1_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_2_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_3_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_4_def": "to produce"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Kaiya reminds him that they have never been ____ before, and it is apparent that Willow is experiencing feelings of guilt.", "Opt_1": "apart", "Opt_2": "verbal", "Opt_3": "domestic", "Opt_4": "overall", "Answer": "apart", "Opt_1_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_2_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_3_def": "home", "Opt_4_def": "general"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He uses Blanche White to ____ the problems of color and class difference between blacks and whites.", "Opt_1": "expose", "Opt_2": "manipulate", "Opt_3": "view", "Opt_4": "suffer", "Answer": "expose", "Opt_1_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_2_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_3_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_4_def": "to experience something bad or painful"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This survey is being used to ____ information about the current level of frustration with computers and the extent to which users feel rage.", "Opt_1": "avoid", "Opt_2": "verify", "Opt_3": "persuade", "Opt_4": "gather", "Answer": "gather", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_2_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_3_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or get together"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "To ____ your head while mountain biking, you should wear a helmet.", "Opt_1": "attach", "Opt_2": "obtain", "Opt_3": "protect", "Opt_4": "assess", "Answer": "protect", "Opt_1_def": "to put together with", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_4_def": "to judge or test"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Our ____ problem is how to convince the governors that we are right.", "Opt_1": "willing", "Opt_2": "chief", "Opt_3": "slight", "Opt_4": "previous", "Answer": "chief", "Opt_1_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "small", "Opt_4_def": "the one before"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The factory worker was awarded \ufffd\ufffd30,000 ____ for losing his arm in an accident.", "Opt_1": "legislation", "Opt_2": "ratio", "Opt_3": "compensation", "Opt_4": "rise", "Answer": "compensation", "Opt_1_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_2_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_3_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_4_def": "to go up"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The objective is to find the right ____ of materials that will result in the creation of clear electrical signals.", "Opt_1": "mixture", "Opt_2": "gap", "Opt_3": "survey", "Opt_4": "concept", "Answer": "mixture", "Opt_1_def": "combination", "Opt_2_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_3_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_4_def": "idea; understanding"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Consequently, the percentages will not sum to 100% because many students were ____ on the questions in the survey.", "Opt_1": "neutral", "Opt_2": "obsolete", "Opt_3": "crucial", "Opt_4": "supplementary", "Answer": "neutral", "Opt_1_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_2_def": "not used or needed any more; out of date", "Opt_3_def": "extremely important", "Opt_4_def": "extra; additional"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Though Sima and Codreanu both attempted to prevent the murder, it ____ took place, and produced harsh consequences.", "Opt_1": "approximately", "Opt_2": "definitely", "Opt_3": "extremely", "Opt_4": "nevertheless", "Answer": "nevertheless", "Opt_1_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_2_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_3_def": "very", "Opt_4_def": "however (although / despite that)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "As people are defining a process or a problem, sometimes solutions emerge in that moment, in the ____ of their description.", "Opt_1": "grant", "Opt_2": "assignment", "Opt_3": "minimum", "Opt_4": "detail", "Answer": "detail", "Opt_1_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization", "Opt_2_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_3_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_4_def": "a small piece of information"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The political system must not be allowed to ____ into unlimited majority rule, which could result in the erosion of individual liberty.", "Opt_1": "remain", "Opt_2": "reinforce", "Opt_3": "align", "Opt_4": "degenerate", "Answer": "degenerate", "Opt_1_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_2_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_3_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_4_def": "to get worse"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "An exciting and dynamic teacher will receive more ____ results than a teacher who is boring and low key.", "Opt_1": "hostile", "Opt_2": "willing", "Opt_3": "positive", "Opt_4": "familiar", "Answer": "positive", "Opt_1_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_2_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_3_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_4_def": "known; well-known"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It must be obvious what the primary theme of each section is, and how that theme connects with the paper's ____ theme.", "Opt_1": "overall", "Opt_2": "superior", "Opt_3": "particular", "Opt_4": "evident", "Answer": "overall", "Opt_1_def": "general", "Opt_2_def": "better", "Opt_3_def": "specific", "Opt_4_def": "clear"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Although the amendment claimed to reduce opportunities for voter fraud, it did not ____ the more common problems of fraudulent voter registration.", "Opt_1": "commence", "Opt_2": "suffer", "Opt_3": "address", "Opt_4": "destroy", "Answer": "address", "Opt_1_def": "to start", "Opt_2_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_3_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_4_def": "to break or damage completely"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "A student whose total absences in a course, excused or unexcused, exceed ten per trimester is ____ to fail the course.", "Opt_1": "liable", "Opt_2": "royal", "Opt_3": "passive", "Opt_4": "global", "Answer": "liable", "Opt_1_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening", "Opt_2_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_3_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_4_def": "world"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Assad did not want to ____ a cease-fire until Israel evacuated at least those parts of the Golan Heights occupied in the October war.", "Opt_1": "explain", "Opt_2": "create", "Opt_3": "utilize", "Opt_4": "accept", "Answer": "accept", "Opt_1_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_3_def": "to use", "Opt_4_def": "to agree (to have)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This ____ is being used to gather information about the current level of frustration with computers and the extent to which users feel rage.", "Opt_1": "perspective", "Opt_2": "substitute", "Opt_3": "survey", "Opt_4": "anomaly", "Answer": "survey", "Opt_1_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_2_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_3_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data", "Opt_4_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Educational websites have the ____ suffix: .edu. For example, the URL of this website is: esl.fis.edu.", "Opt_1": "term", "Opt_2": "domain", "Opt_3": "fund", "Opt_4": "principle", "Answer": "domain", "Opt_1_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_2_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_4_def": "rule"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ resulted from the fact that the Jews agreed to the resolution but the local Arabs refused to acknowledge the Israeli State.", "Opt_1": "controversy", "Opt_2": "fund", "Opt_3": "symbol", "Opt_4": "industry", "Answer": "controversy", "Opt_1_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_2_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_3_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_4_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Gladwin County decided to ____ the sale of dogs from its animal shelter in order to give citizens the chance to review the county's earlier decision.", "Opt_1": "utilize", "Opt_2": "ensure", "Opt_3": "suspend", "Opt_4": "revise", "Answer": "suspend", "Opt_1_def": "to use", "Opt_2_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_3_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_4_def": "to change (in order to improve)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The company director decided to ____ his son as the new head of marketing.", "Opt_1": "install", "Opt_2": "depart", "Opt_3": "expand", "Opt_4": "edit", "Answer": "install", "Opt_1_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_2_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_4_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I have no ____ to students wearing hats in the classroom, but many teachers do.", "Opt_1": "friction", "Opt_2": "objection", "Opt_3": "profit", "Opt_4": "mechanism", "Answer": "objection", "Opt_1_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_2_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "money gained", "Opt_4_def": "procedure, process"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If we want to maintain support for an open and dynamic economy, our programs need to become as ____ and adaptable as the economy itself.", "Opt_1": "automatic", "Opt_2": "competent", "Opt_3": "physical", "Opt_4": "flexible", "Answer": "flexible", "Opt_1_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_2_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_3_def": "of the body", "Opt_4_def": "can be changed or bent"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The nine women here say the poor ____ of domestic workers is an apartheid-era relic that has no place in democratic South Africa.", "Opt_1": "treatment", "Opt_2": "incentive", "Opt_3": "responsibility", "Opt_4": "committee", "Answer": "treatment", "Opt_1_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_2_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_3_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It started to ____ after much questioning that the reasons for his bad behaviour were problems at home.", "Opt_1": "devise", "Opt_2": "emerge", "Opt_3": "assist", "Opt_4": "stipulate", "Answer": "emerge", "Opt_1_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_2_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_3_def": "to help", "Opt_4_def": "to require"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The police chief found it difficult to ____ why the wrong man had been arrested.", "Opt_1": "address", "Opt_2": "explain", "Opt_3": "compile", "Opt_4": "defend", "Answer": "explain", "Opt_1_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_2_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_4_def": "to give reasons for"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This finding may explain why increasing numbers of people in the United States lack the natural ability to ____ food intake and body weight.", "Opt_1": "regulate", "Opt_2": "store", "Opt_3": "broadcast", "Opt_4": "forego", "Answer": "regulate", "Opt_1_def": "to control", "Opt_2_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_3_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_4_def": "to do without; to give up"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The police could find no ____ of the girl who was kidnapped from her hotel.", "Opt_1": "decade", "Opt_2": "proportion", "Opt_3": "innovation", "Opt_4": "trace", "Answer": "trace", "Opt_1_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_2_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_3_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_4_def": "sign; indication; evidence"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The Supreme Court held that the free exercise of religion did not entitle an Orthodox Jew to wear a yarmulke when he was on ____ as an officer of law.", "Opt_1": "duty", "Opt_2": "precaution", "Opt_3": "boundary", "Opt_4": "ignorance", "Answer": "duty", "Opt_1_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_2_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_3_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_4_def": "lack of knowledge"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "During its congress, Committee failed to ____ even one woman to a leading position.", "Opt_1": "elect", "Opt_2": "require", "Opt_3": "conform", "Opt_4": "release", "Answer": "elect", "Opt_1_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_2_def": "to need", "Opt_3_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_4_def": "to let go or let out"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You need to be careful not to ____ people that you meet on the internet They may not be who they claim to be..", "Opt_1": "regret", "Opt_2": "culminate", "Opt_3": "trust", "Opt_4": "adjust", "Answer": "trust", "Opt_1_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_2_def": "to end", "Opt_3_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You must ____ the US using the visa document issued by the institution you will be attending.", "Opt_1": "enter", "Opt_2": "join", "Opt_3": "cancel", "Opt_4": "apply", "Answer": "enter", "Opt_1_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_2_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_3_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_4_def": "to be relevant (to)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The organizations that take ____ for putting ecology first have failed to reform or develop a system that will allow them to achieve their goals.", "Opt_1": "finance", "Opt_2": "credit", "Opt_3": "detail", "Opt_4": "impact", "Answer": "credit", "Opt_1_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_2_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_3_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_4_def": "effect"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "However, continuous and systematic research on the ____ did not emerge until after World War II.", "Opt_1": "hierarchy", "Opt_2": "rate", "Opt_3": "disaster", "Opt_4": "surplus", "Answer": "disaster", "Opt_1_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_2_def": "quantity; proportion; speed", "Opt_3_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_4_def": "to be, go or make all the way around"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is not always easy for teachers to ____ poor work that is due to laziness and poor work that is due to inability.", "Opt_1": "suppress", "Opt_2": "recommend", "Opt_3": "differentiate", "Opt_4": "decrease", "Answer": "differentiate", "Opt_1_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_3_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller, to go down"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Don't forget to ____ your research sources at the end of your writing.", "Opt_1": "enumerate", "Opt_2": "appear", "Opt_3": "cover", "Opt_4": "appeal", "Answer": "enumerate", "Opt_1_def": "to list", "Opt_2_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_4_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Even more extraordinary, every child ____ one was more than willing to state his or her name to the stranger.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Some people believe that smokers should not be ____ for free medical treatment.", "Opt_1": "harsh", "Opt_2": "similar", "Opt_3": "eligible", "Opt_4": "effective", "Answer": "eligible", "Opt_1_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_2_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_3_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_4_def": "good, working well"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Tests are valid when they measure what they claim to measure, and ____ when they measure consistently.", "Opt_1": "ultimate", "Opt_2": "cautious", "Opt_3": "wise", "Opt_4": "reliable", "Answer": "reliable", "Opt_1_def": "final or most important", "Opt_2_def": "careful", "Opt_3_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_4_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The text should ____ a concise description of the aims and scope of your thesis.", "Opt_1": "collaborate", "Opt_2": "contain", "Opt_3": "contribute", "Opt_4": "disperse", "Answer": "contain", "Opt_1_def": "to work together", "Opt_2_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_3_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_4_def": "to spread out; to move apart"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This was not ____ of Serbia alone; the population felt similar frustration in other parts of Yugoslavia and in Eastern Europe.", "Opt_1": "subjective", "Opt_2": "suitable", "Opt_3": "characteristic", "Opt_4": "intense", "Answer": "characteristic", "Opt_1_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_2_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "typical", "Opt_4_def": "strong, extreme"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ way of attacking the security of computer programs is to feed them unexpected and deceptive inputs.", "Opt_1": "royal", "Opt_2": "typical", "Opt_3": "perpetual", "Opt_4": "classic", "Answer": "classic", "Opt_1_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_2_def": "usual", "Opt_3_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_4_def": "very good, the best or most used"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The profits of most industrial companies ____ on the price of oil.", "Opt_1": "attract", "Opt_2": "approach", "Opt_3": "attach", "Opt_4": "depend", "Answer": "depend", "Opt_1_def": "to be interesting; to cause to like", "Opt_2_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_3_def": "to put together with", "Opt_4_def": "be influenced (by)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is not necessarily subjected to a thorough analysis, ____ it will need to be evaluated by the user.", "Opt_1": "largely", "Opt_2": "occasionally", "Opt_3": "thus", "Opt_4": "absolutely", "Answer": "thus", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_3_def": "so", "Opt_4_def": "completely; 100%"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Many students who receive a grade lower than they want, do so because they fail to ____ their texts.", "Opt_1": "annotate", "Opt_2": "expand", "Opt_3": "select", "Opt_4": "consider", "Answer": "annotate", "Opt_1_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_3_def": "to choose", "Opt_4_def": "to think"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "An ____ of English that many learners find difficult is verb grammar.", "Opt_1": "habit", "Opt_2": "aspect", "Opt_3": "majority", "Opt_4": "effect", "Answer": "aspect", "Opt_1_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_2_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_3_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Typically held the 3rd week of February, this is an ____ event that helps College of Fine Arts students explore careers, develop strategies to pursue career and artistic goals successfully.", "Opt_1": "subsequent", "Opt_2": "extraordinary", "Opt_3": "annual", "Opt_4": "final", "Answer": "annual", "Opt_1_def": "next, following", "Opt_2_def": "very unusual", "Opt_3_def": "yearly", "Opt_4_def": "last"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Many of the research questions involved are ____ to more mainstream systems research, albeit larger in scale.", "Opt_1": "rational", "Opt_2": "domestic", "Opt_3": "available", "Opt_4": "similar", "Answer": "similar", "Opt_1_def": "base on reason, not on emotion or instinct", "Opt_2_def": "home", "Opt_3_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_4_def": "like, almost the same as"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Kaiya reminds him that they have never been apart before, and it is ____ that Willow is experiencing feelings of guilt.", "Opt_1": "passive", "Opt_2": "widespread", "Opt_3": "profound", "Opt_4": "apparent", "Answer": "apparent", "Opt_1_def": "not active; unresponsive", "Opt_2_def": "common", "Opt_3_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_4_def": "clear; obvious"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "He seems to be lacking the impulse to improve his rather ____ grades.", "Opt_1": "sound", "Opt_2": "pure", "Opt_3": "deficient", "Opt_4": "poor", "Answer": "poor", "Opt_1_def": "good; strong", "Opt_2_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_3_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_4_def": "bad, unsatisfactory"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Because there was the threat of losing funding if they failed to participate, there was a strong ____ to do so.", "Opt_1": "section", "Opt_2": "incentive", "Opt_3": "argument", "Opt_4": "motive", "Answer": "incentive", "Opt_1_def": "part", "Opt_2_def": "reason to do something", "Opt_3_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_4_def": "reason"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Different ideas about what is fashionable - in clothes, music, etc. - ____ at different times and in different countries.", "Opt_1": "prevail", "Opt_2": "associate", "Opt_3": "infer", "Opt_4": "reveal", "Answer": "prevail", "Opt_1_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_2_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_3_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_4_def": "to show or uncover"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The student who had forgotten his homework was fortunate that the teacher was ____ that day.", "Opt_1": "invisible", "Opt_2": "absent", "Opt_3": "perpetual", "Opt_4": "forthcoming", "Answer": "absent", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_2_def": "being not there; missing", "Opt_3_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_4_def": "coming soon"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This page includes materials relating to the continuing ____ over the teaching of evolution and creationism in schools.", "Opt_1": "controversy", "Opt_2": "expert", "Opt_3": "exponent", "Opt_4": "potential", "Answer": "controversy", "Opt_1_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_2_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_3_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_4_def": "good possibility"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This week's anniversary of the US-led war against Iraq is an appropriate ____ to ask: Are Americans safer than we were a year ago?", "Opt_1": "operation", "Opt_2": "account", "Opt_3": "loss", "Opt_4": "occasion", "Answer": "occasion", "Opt_1_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_2_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_3_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_4_def": "time (opportunity)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You are making ____ progress in learning English.", "Opt_1": "steady", "Opt_2": "legitimate", "Opt_3": "aware", "Opt_4": "harsh", "Answer": "steady", "Opt_1_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_2_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_3_def": "knowing", "Opt_4_def": "hard, unfair"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The Birth Control Pill may have modernized society, but it tore ____ a nation and created many social problems that did not exist before its invention.", "Opt_1": "uniform", "Opt_2": "permanent", "Opt_3": "apart", "Opt_4": "substantial", "Answer": "apart", "Opt_1_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_2_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_3_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_4_def": "large"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "An employee is entitled to no ____ for the first seven calendar days of disability unless the disability continues for more than 21 days.", "Opt_1": "compensation", "Opt_2": "opinion", "Opt_3": "stereotype", "Opt_4": "episode", "Answer": "compensation", "Opt_1_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_2_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If you are eligible for Financial Aid in excess of your tuition and fees then you do not ____ Ivy Tech Community College money.", "Opt_1": "appoint", "Opt_2": "owe", "Opt_3": "appear", "Opt_4": "shrink", "Answer": "owe", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_2_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_3_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "It is fair to praise the government for their successful efforts to reduce unemployment ____ older people.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "After several years of work, the project team was not able to gather the ____ support needed to maintain funding for the integrated service program.", "Opt_1": "inevitable", "Opt_2": "apart", "Opt_3": "political", "Opt_4": "ideal", "Answer": "political", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_2_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_3_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_4_def": "best, optimal"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "A very ____ way to check how the use of an English word is to look in Google for pages that contain it.", "Opt_1": "homogeneous", "Opt_2": "effective", "Opt_3": "complete", "Opt_4": "forthcoming", "Answer": "effective", "Opt_1_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_2_def": "good, working well", "Opt_3_def": "full or finished", "Opt_4_def": "coming soon"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The College will take no ____ for any actions taken by students who have been drinking, on or off campus.", "Opt_1": "code", "Opt_2": "policy", "Opt_3": "circumstances", "Opt_4": "responsibility", "Answer": "responsibility", "Opt_1_def": "a set of rules", "Opt_2_def": "formal rules", "Opt_3_def": "situation", "Opt_4_def": "job, duty to do something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Many students look for ____ work between leaving school and starting university.", "Opt_1": "novel", "Opt_2": "averse", "Opt_3": "numerous", "Opt_4": "temporary", "Answer": "temporary", "Opt_1_def": "new", "Opt_2_def": "against", "Opt_3_def": "very many", "Opt_4_def": "for a short or limited time"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "She said she initially had planned to ____ earlier, but that she postponed her departure because of pressing issues at the hospital.", "Opt_1": "devote", "Opt_2": "consent", "Opt_3": "lessen", "Opt_4": "retire", "Answer": "retire", "Opt_1_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_2_def": "to agree", "Opt_3_def": "to reduce", "Opt_4_def": "to stop working"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The Institute itself was an entity ____ from the Chemistry department.", "Opt_1": "complicate", "Opt_2": "analyze", "Opt_3": "publish", "Opt_4": "separate", "Answer": "separate", "Opt_1_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_2_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_3_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_4_def": "to pull or put apart"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Most car companies are putting money into research into ____ forms of fuel. It will take a number of years, however, before anyone can develop a car that runs on water.", "Opt_1": "gain", "Opt_2": "profession", "Opt_3": "alternative", "Opt_4": "surplus", "Answer": "alternative", "Opt_1_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_2_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_3_def": "other possibility", "Opt_4_def": "to be, go or make all the way around"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It was found that only 10 of these comparisons were acceptably consistent, meaning that their inconsistency ____ exceeded 35%.", "Opt_1": "gap", "Opt_2": "ratio", "Opt_3": "license", "Opt_4": "condition", "Answer": "ratio", "Opt_1_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_2_def": "mathematical relationship between two amount", "Opt_3_def": "permission to do something (often an official document)", "Opt_4_def": "state"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The set of elective courses must ____ a well-defined focus and must be approved by the student's advisor.", "Opt_1": "constitute", "Opt_2": "increase", "Opt_3": "accomplish", "Opt_4": "raise", "Answer": "constitute", "Opt_1_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_2_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_3_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_4_def": "to lift; to make higher"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "She is yet to master basic verb grammar. She often says He do .. ____ of He does ...", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "against", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Sports events such as the World Cup or the Olympic Games often culminate in an ____ firework display.", "Opt_1": "valuable", "Opt_2": "enormous", "Opt_3": "compulsory", "Opt_4": "ultimate", "Answer": "enormous", "Opt_1_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_2_def": "very big", "Opt_3_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_4_def": "final or most important"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "English may be a global language but it is not yet a proper ____ for exploring most of the world's societies and cultures.", "Opt_1": "power", "Opt_2": "tool", "Opt_3": "constraint", "Opt_4": "scheme", "Answer": "tool", "Opt_1_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_2_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_4_def": "plan. idea, project"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The committee expects that as NOAA moves forward it will have to revise the plan on a regular basis to ____ new understanding.", "Opt_1": "explain", "Opt_2": "incorporate", "Opt_3": "absorb", "Opt_4": "degenerate", "Answer": "incorporate", "Opt_1_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to include", "Opt_3_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_4_def": "to get worse"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "New challenges, opportunities, and demands are necessary to ensure that creativity and motivation do not ____ away.", "Opt_1": "exist", "Opt_2": "justify", "Opt_3": "fade", "Opt_4": "govern", "Answer": "fade", "Opt_1_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_2_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_4_def": "to control or influence"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Next the teacher must ____ that nicotine in tobacco products is addictive.", "Opt_1": "stress", "Opt_2": "prepare", "Opt_3": "seek", "Opt_4": "compel", "Answer": "stress", "Opt_1_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_2_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_3_def": "to look for or want", "Opt_4_def": "to force or make happen"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Turning in work completed by other students will only ____ you when it comes to the exams.", "Opt_1": "select", "Opt_2": "compile", "Opt_3": "harm", "Opt_4": "generate", "Answer": "harm", "Opt_1_def": "to choose", "Opt_2_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_3_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_4_def": "to make or produce"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In tomorrow's TV ____ the government will declare its intention to reduce taxes during its time in office.", "Opt_1": "broadcast", "Opt_2": "succeed", "Opt_3": "fare", "Opt_4": "present", "Answer": "broadcast", "Opt_1_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_2_def": "to do well", "Opt_3_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_4_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "They ____ that they did the work independently of each, but I don't believe them.", "Opt_1": "contemplate", "Opt_2": "claim", "Opt_3": "submit", "Opt_4": "prefer", "Answer": "claim", "Opt_1_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_2_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_3_def": "to give; to send", "Opt_4_def": "to like better"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In most of Africa, for example, weaker institutions have failed to ____ restrictions on rulers and undemocratic power politics has been employed.", "Opt_1": "accompany", "Opt_2": "qualify", "Opt_3": "maintain", "Opt_4": "impose", "Answer": "impose", "Opt_1_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_2_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_3_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_4_def": "to force; to require to happen"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Not everyone agrees with the ____ of reducing drug-taking by putting more users in prison.", "Opt_1": "region", "Opt_2": "portion", "Opt_3": "format", "Opt_4": "strategy", "Answer": "strategy", "Opt_1_def": "part of a place", "Opt_2_def": "part, amount", "Opt_3_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_4_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you change your ____ or place of study, please amend your log-in details accordingly.", "Opt_1": "trade", "Opt_2": "address", "Opt_3": "contribute", "Opt_4": "discover", "Answer": "address", "Opt_1_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_2_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_3_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_4_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government official wrote to ____ that the new law applied only to people born after the year 1990.", "Opt_1": "confirm", "Opt_2": "multiply", "Opt_3": "conform", "Opt_4": "regulate", "Answer": "confirm", "Opt_1_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_2_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_3_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_4_def": "to control"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If you look at the course policies you will ____ an item that accounts for 4% of your grade.", "Opt_1": "request", "Opt_2": "fluctuate", "Opt_3": "appoint", "Opt_4": "notice", "Answer": "notice", "Opt_1_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_2_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_3_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_4_def": "to see or realize"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The students made a ____ that they would speak to each other only in English.", "Opt_1": "policy", "Opt_2": "deal", "Opt_3": "experiment", "Opt_4": "layer", "Answer": "deal", "Opt_1_def": "formal rules", "Opt_2_def": "agreement", "Opt_3_def": "test", "Opt_4_def": "level"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Bogart and Methot got married and the ____ was total disaster for both of them.", "Opt_1": "limit", "Opt_2": "labour", "Opt_3": "proportion", "Opt_4": "result", "Answer": "result", "Opt_1_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_2_def": "work", "Opt_3_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_4_def": "outcome, effect"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We have a special ____ at this school for students whose first language is not English and who need some extra support.", "Opt_1": "intention", "Opt_2": "effect", "Opt_3": "programme", "Opt_4": "treatment", "Answer": "programme", "Opt_1_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_4_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The police had difficulty in trying to ____ the enormous crowd after the pop concert.", "Opt_1": "disperse", "Opt_2": "train", "Opt_3": "proceed", "Opt_4": "transmit", "Answer": "disperse", "Opt_1_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_2_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_4_def": "to send or convey"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "These ever-changing factors necessitate the creation of a flexible policy that can respond and ____ to the needs of our library users.", "Opt_1": "align", "Opt_2": "adapt", "Opt_3": "override", "Opt_4": "oppose", "Answer": "adapt", "Opt_1_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_3_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_4_def": "to be against or fight against something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "He is an American citizen which obviously puts him in a different ____ from the kinds of individuals that the president has suggested might be suitable.", "Opt_1": "gap", "Opt_2": "category", "Opt_3": "justice", "Opt_4": "constraint", "Answer": "category", "Opt_1_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_2_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_3_def": "fairness in law", "Opt_4_def": "to hold back; to prevent"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Counselors will begin on-going sessions with a student only after having obtained signed ____ of the student and signed consent of the parent.", "Opt_1": "device", "Opt_2": "entity", "Opt_3": "assent", "Opt_4": "deal", "Answer": "assent", "Opt_1_def": "object; method", "Opt_2_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_3_def": "agreement", "Opt_4_def": "agreement"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "I found a ____ of her homework on the cafeteria. It looked like half the school had stepped on it!", "Opt_1": "compensation", "Opt_2": "contract", "Opt_3": "surface", "Opt_4": "fragment", "Answer": "fragment", "Opt_1_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_2_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_3_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_4_def": "part of something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Some students claim that they can ____ watch TV and do their homework.", "Opt_1": "largely", "Opt_2": "generally", "Opt_3": "dramatically", "Opt_4": "simultaneously", "Answer": "simultaneously", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "usually", "Opt_3_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_4_def": "at the same time"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "I usually keep a supply of ____ pencils in my desk, so that I can lend one to any student who comes without.", "Opt_1": "conscious", "Opt_2": "spare", "Opt_3": "basic", "Opt_4": "supplementary", "Answer": "spare", "Opt_1_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_2_def": "not needed", "Opt_3_def": "first or easy", "Opt_4_def": "extra; additional"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Biological processes interact strongly with ____ and chemical processes to create the planetary environment.", "Opt_1": "substantial", "Opt_2": "chief", "Opt_3": "physical", "Opt_4": "political", "Answer": "physical", "Opt_1_def": "large", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "of the body", "Opt_4_def": "to do government and politics"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "President Tom Gerety announced today that he will ____ on June 30, 2003, after nine years as the head of the college.", "Opt_1": "cooperate", "Opt_2": "estimate", "Opt_3": "submit", "Opt_4": "resign", "Answer": "resign", "Opt_1_def": "to work (well) with another person", "Opt_2_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_3_def": "to give; to send", "Opt_4_def": "to give up (one's job)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "For the second meeting of the Forum, we have arranged a debate between two legal professionals who must struggle with the death ____ regularly.", "Opt_1": "pressure", "Opt_2": "limit", "Opt_3": "penalty", "Opt_4": "region", "Answer": "penalty", "Opt_1_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_2_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_3_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_4_def": "part of a place"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "So, the possibility of humans bringing about significant evil is a ____ consequence of having free will.", "Opt_1": "genuine", "Opt_2": "sound", "Opt_3": "authentic", "Opt_4": "logical", "Answer": "logical", "Opt_1_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_2_def": "good; strong", "Opt_3_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_4_def": "making sense"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Art is every artist's attempt to communicate in a way ____ words what they feel, see, and think about life.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The Education Department's increased demand for paperwork will ____ the patience and good will of teachers.", "Opt_1": "strain", "Opt_2": "communicate", "Opt_3": "denote", "Opt_4": "cease", "Answer": "strain", "Opt_1_def": "to put under stress or make difficult", "Opt_2_def": "to convey information", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Although Katrina affected the material environment of Louisiana, it did not ____ the great spirit of the people here.", "Opt_1": "overcome", "Opt_2": "accept", "Opt_3": "procure", "Opt_4": "diminish", "Answer": "diminish", "Opt_1_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_2_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_3_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller or less important"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If the picture on your TV is not very clear, you need to ____ the controls.", "Opt_1": "notice", "Opt_2": "acknowledge", "Opt_3": "represent", "Opt_4": "adjust", "Answer": "adjust", "Opt_1_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_2_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_3_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Teachers can suggest that students get a ____ of 8 hours sleep per night, but they cannot dictate it.", "Opt_1": "minimum", "Opt_2": "interpretation", "Opt_3": "element", "Opt_4": "revolution", "Answer": "minimum", "Opt_1_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_2_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_3_def": "aspect, part", "Opt_4_def": "a time of great change"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This fact demonstrates that immigrants are not ____ to learning the language of their new country.", "Opt_1": "hostile", "Opt_2": "technical", "Opt_3": "economic", "Opt_4": "logical", "Answer": "hostile", "Opt_1_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_2_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_3_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_4_def": "making sense"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "An even number multiplied by an odd number will always ____ an even number.", "Opt_1": "apply", "Opt_2": "yield", "Opt_3": "protect", "Opt_4": "comprise", "Answer": "yield", "Opt_1_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_2_def": "to produce", "Opt_3_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_4_def": "to be made up of; to include"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Including future irrelevant costs generally will not lead to a ____ choice; it will only complicate the analysis.", "Opt_1": "poor", "Opt_2": "hostile", "Opt_3": "urban", "Opt_4": "former", "Answer": "poor", "Opt_1_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_2_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_3_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_4_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The candidate must ____ clear written and verbal communication skills, and must be willing to work in a team project environment.", "Opt_1": "command", "Opt_2": "battle", "Opt_3": "proportion", "Opt_4": "deal", "Answer": "command", "Opt_1_def": "control", "Opt_2_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_3_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_4_def": "agreement"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Erving Goffman pointed out that when one person speaks on ____ of another, the former steals the latter's conversational role.", "Opt_1": "anomaly", "Opt_2": "background", "Opt_3": "resource", "Opt_4": "behalf", "Answer": "behalf", "Opt_1_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_2_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_3_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_4_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The bank did not ____ to make payment but insisted first on the signature of the husband.", "Opt_1": "behave", "Opt_2": "refuse", "Opt_3": "enforce", "Opt_4": "discover", "Answer": "refuse", "Opt_1_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do", "Opt_3_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_4_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Previous ____ in such areas, especially microscopy, would be an advantage but is not essential.", "Opt_1": "attitude", "Opt_2": "magnitude", "Opt_3": "experience", "Opt_4": "dispute", "Answer": "experience", "Opt_1_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_2_def": "size; amount", "Opt_3_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_4_def": "argument; conflict"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The first of the allegations came from a woman who, in the ____ of the Committee, was not a credible witness.", "Opt_1": "trace", "Opt_2": "speed", "Opt_3": "opinion", "Opt_4": "episode", "Answer": "opinion", "Opt_1_def": "sign; indication; evidence", "Opt_2_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_3_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In tomorrow's TV broadcast the government will ____ its intention to reduce taxes during its time in office.", "Opt_1": "dictate", "Opt_2": "ignore", "Opt_3": "advise", "Opt_4": "declare", "Answer": "declare", "Opt_1_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_2_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_3_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_4_def": "to state"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "My father has a workshop in the garage so I have a lot of ____ knowledge.", "Opt_1": "technical", "Opt_2": "satisfactory", "Opt_3": "essential", "Opt_4": "physical", "Answer": "technical", "Opt_1_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_2_def": "enough;OK", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "of the body"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The ____ of this unit is to teach students how a seemingly unimportant event can have a significant effect on their lives.", "Opt_1": "series", "Opt_2": "principle", "Opt_3": "sample", "Opt_4": "goal", "Answer": "goal", "Opt_1_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "rule", "Opt_3_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_4_def": "aim or intention"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "No program has developed an approach that is ____ successful in working with the types of problems that we try to solve.", "Opt_1": "universally", "Opt_2": "rather", "Opt_3": "dramatically", "Opt_4": "absolutely", "Answer": "universally", "Opt_1_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_2_def": "instead", "Opt_3_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_4_def": "completely; 100%"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This program will ____ entry to the field and to advanced study of nutrition.", "Opt_1": "fear", "Opt_2": "condemn", "Opt_3": "notice", "Opt_4": "accelerate", "Answer": "accelerate", "Opt_1_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_2_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_4_def": "to get or make faster"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We recognize that ____ beyond a family's control may inhibit a family's ability to contribute to educational expenses.", "Opt_1": "circumstances", "Opt_2": "version", "Opt_3": "period", "Opt_4": "portion", "Answer": "circumstances", "Opt_1_def": "situation", "Opt_2_def": "form", "Opt_3_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)", "Opt_4_def": "part, amount"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Erving Goffman pointed out that when one person speaks on behalf of another, the ____ steals the latter's conversational role.", "Opt_1": "former", "Opt_2": "conscious", "Opt_3": "odd", "Opt_4": "previous", "Answer": "former", "Opt_1_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_2_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_3_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_4_def": "the one before"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We are in the middle of the most serious ____ with the governments of these peoples and nations.", "Opt_1": "community", "Opt_2": "defeat", "Opt_3": "image", "Opt_4": "conflict", "Answer": "conflict", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people", "Opt_2_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_3_def": "picture", "Opt_4_def": "problem, struggle or battle"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ of young men who walk around with large aggressive dogs is that they are from the working class and are criminals.", "Opt_1": "obstacle", "Opt_2": "performance", "Opt_3": "implication", "Opt_4": "stereotype", "Answer": "stereotype", "Opt_1_def": "barrier; problem", "Opt_2_def": "action or achievement", "Opt_3_def": "result or consequence", "Opt_4_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Sunnis believe that the Prophet Mohammed did not appoint a successor and ____ gave permission to Muslims to elect or choose their own leader after his death.", "Opt_1": "perhaps", "Opt_2": "hence", "Opt_3": "fairly", "Opt_4": "therefore", "Answer": "therefore", "Opt_1_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_2_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_3_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_4_def": "so, as a result"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Military ____ is not an appropriate tool to transform the Middle East.", "Opt_1": "speed", "Opt_2": "custom", "Opt_3": "function", "Opt_4": "power", "Answer": "power", "Opt_1_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_2_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_3_def": "job or role", "Opt_4_def": "the right or authority to do something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "His examination failure did not ____ through lack of effort or ability but because of serious illness in the weeks before.", "Opt_1": "occur", "Opt_2": "include", "Opt_3": "override", "Opt_4": "launch", "Answer": "occur", "Opt_1_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_2_def": "to put in; to have in", "Opt_3_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_4_def": "to begin"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The course will develop the knowledge base ____ the finance of community education programs.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "After about a year his family realized that this was not just a ____ and that he was serious about me and that we really cared about each other.", "Opt_1": "territory", "Opt_2": "phase", "Opt_3": "service", "Opt_4": "state", "Answer": "phase", "Opt_1_def": "land; area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_3_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_4_def": "condition, situation"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "What do western Louisville and the Appalachian ____ have in common besides being two of the poorest areas in Kentucky?", "Opt_1": "format", "Opt_2": "command", "Opt_3": "region", "Opt_4": "sphere", "Answer": "region", "Opt_1_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_2_def": "control", "Opt_3_def": "part of a place", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Please ____ these papers - two sheets to each student.", "Opt_1": "succeed", "Opt_2": "compel", "Opt_3": "circulate", "Opt_4": "distribute", "Answer": "distribute", "Opt_1_def": "to do well", "Opt_2_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_3_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_4_def": "to give out"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is not the government's ____ to supervise what people are doing when they are online.", "Opt_1": "aim", "Opt_2": "role", "Opt_3": "impact", "Opt_4": "volume", "Answer": "role", "Opt_1_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_2_def": "job or function", "Opt_3_def": "effect", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If the human body is weak or cold, it is less able to ____ infection.", "Opt_1": "base", "Opt_2": "refuse", "Opt_3": "criticize", "Opt_4": "resist", "Answer": "resist", "Opt_1_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_2_def": "to not do something that someone wants you to do", "Opt_3_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to fight against"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Students will learn to ____ what epidemiologists mean when they say that an exposure and an outcome are associated.", "Opt_1": "approve", "Opt_2": "appreciate", "Opt_3": "reflect", "Opt_4": "base", "Answer": "appreciate", "Opt_1_def": "to agree to", "Opt_2_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_3_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_4_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Most of the school's ____ comes from the school fees paid by the companies who send their employees to work in Germany.", "Opt_1": "object", "Opt_2": "revenue", "Opt_3": "reluctance", "Opt_4": "shortage", "Answer": "revenue", "Opt_1_def": "thing", "Opt_2_def": "money, income", "Opt_3_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_4_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The case of Nicaragua demonstrates how the United States failed to ____ on the implementation of democratic procedures.", "Opt_1": "assimilate", "Opt_2": "annotate", "Opt_3": "insist", "Opt_4": "magnify", "Answer": "insist", "Opt_1_def": "to take in", "Opt_2_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim", "Opt_4_def": "to make or show larger"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "A good way to guess the meaning of a new word is to ____ its context in the sentence.", "Opt_1": "separate", "Opt_2": "deserve", "Opt_3": "restrict", "Opt_4": "examine", "Answer": "examine", "Opt_1_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_2_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_3_def": "to limit", "Opt_4_def": "to look at carefully"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If you want to ____ in English, I recommend that you read plenty of books for pleasure.", "Opt_1": "improve", "Opt_2": "continue", "Opt_3": "notice", "Opt_4": "control", "Answer": "improve", "Opt_1_def": "to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_3_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_4_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The most serious ____ raised against the survey questions the use of self-report scales to assess prejudice.", "Opt_1": "staff", "Opt_2": "labour", "Opt_3": "career", "Opt_4": "objection", "Answer": "objection", "Opt_1_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)", "Opt_2_def": "work", "Opt_3_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_4_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Please ____ these papers - two sheets to each student.", "Opt_1": "request", "Opt_2": "reserve", "Opt_3": "trust", "Opt_4": "distribute", "Answer": "distribute", "Opt_1_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_2_def": "to keep", "Opt_3_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_4_def": "to give out"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Some scientists believe that there is an ____ supply of oil waiting to be discovered at the bottom of deep oceans.", "Opt_1": "abundant", "Opt_2": "extraordinary", "Opt_3": "sole", "Opt_4": "classic", "Answer": "abundant", "Opt_1_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_2_def": "very unusual", "Opt_3_def": "only", "Opt_4_def": "very good, the best or most used"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Abortion is not a ____ right; it can be limited if the state wishes.", "Opt_1": "radical", "Opt_2": "fundamental", "Opt_3": "related", "Opt_4": "confident", "Answer": "fundamental", "Opt_1_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_4_def": "sure that something will happen"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Visit our Student Support page to see how you can set up a ____ to give someone the opportunity to pursue higher education at Michigan Tech.", "Opt_1": "field", "Opt_2": "fund", "Opt_3": "cycle", "Opt_4": "pattern", "Answer": "fund", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_2_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_3_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_4_def": "clear and consistent behaviour"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There is land ____ the ice in Antarctica, but water ____ it at the North Pole.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Plants that ____ certain traits or characteristics not common to the entire species are referred to as biotypes.", "Opt_1": "depend", "Opt_2": "emerge", "Opt_3": "possess", "Opt_4": "conduct", "Answer": "possess", "Opt_1_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_2_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_3_def": "to have or own", "Opt_4_def": "to do or perform; to behave"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The fact that he can only speak a little English is sure to magnify his already ____ learning problems.", "Opt_1": "common", "Opt_2": "flexible", "Opt_3": "severe", "Opt_4": "average", "Answer": "severe", "Opt_1_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_2_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_3_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_4_def": "ordinary, typical"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There are many things that people can do in the battle against ____ warming. For instance, they can turn off lights when they leave the room.", "Opt_1": "common", "Opt_2": "conscious", "Opt_3": "confident", "Opt_4": "global", "Answer": "global", "Opt_1_def": "often seen or happening", "Opt_2_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_3_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_4_def": "world"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It operated below 60%, was generally poorly designed and therefore not ____ considering.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "among", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "in, between", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "I'm in a ____ with John's parents. They want me to give him more homework, but I know he won't do it.", "Opt_1": "battle", "Opt_2": "gap", "Opt_3": "magnitude", "Opt_4": "period", "Answer": "battle", "Opt_1_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_2_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_3_def": "size; amount", "Opt_4_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The last ____ of the flooded village was evacuated by a helicopter.", "Opt_1": "perspective", "Opt_2": "volume", "Opt_3": "resident", "Opt_4": "service", "Answer": "resident", "Opt_1_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_4_def": "work done for others; help"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government failed to ____ its goal of reducing unemployment among young people.", "Opt_1": "accomplish", "Opt_2": "enforce", "Opt_3": "found", "Opt_4": "diverge", "Answer": "accomplish", "Opt_1_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_2_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_3_def": "to begin (often an organization)", "Opt_4_def": "to move apart; to be different from"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "An employee is entitled to no ____ for the first seven calendar days of disability unless the disability continues for more than 21 days.", "Opt_1": "device", "Opt_2": "compensation", "Opt_3": "labour", "Opt_4": "lecture", "Answer": "compensation", "Opt_1_def": "object; method", "Opt_2_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_3_def": "work", "Opt_4_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I would be more prepared to ____ with the rules if I understood the reasons for them.", "Opt_1": "comply", "Opt_2": "provide", "Opt_3": "detect", "Opt_4": "cease", "Answer": "comply", "Opt_1_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_2_def": "to give", "Opt_3_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Ventures like Amazon.com will only continue to ____ as long as they make money.", "Opt_1": "signify", "Opt_2": "reject", "Opt_3": "exist", "Opt_4": "invent", "Answer": "exist", "Opt_1_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_2_def": "to refuse", "Opt_3_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_4_def": "to create (often a new object)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A frequent ____ in editing is to fix a word or phrase at one part of a sentence and not see that the fix affected something else in the sentence.", "Opt_1": "diagram", "Opt_2": "substitute", "Opt_3": "error", "Opt_4": "justice", "Answer": "error", "Opt_1_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_2_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_3_def": "a mistake", "Opt_4_def": "fairness in law"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Many of the world-wide organizations such as Greenpeace and Oxfam ____ very heavily on voluntary workers.", "Opt_1": "depend", "Opt_2": "sustain", "Opt_3": "negotiate", "Opt_4": "import", "Answer": "depend", "Opt_1_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_2_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_3_def": "to discuss (usually in politics or business)", "Opt_4_def": "to bring in (to a country)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government failed to ____ street demonstrations against its decision to increase petrol tax.", "Opt_1": "suppress", "Opt_2": "verify", "Opt_3": "consist", "Opt_4": "protest", "Answer": "suppress", "Opt_1_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_3_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it", "Opt_4_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It's always better to be overly ____ and to protect yourself by asking for a written contract.", "Opt_1": "apart", "Opt_2": "secure", "Opt_3": "cautious", "Opt_4": "outstanding", "Answer": "cautious", "Opt_1_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_2_def": "safe", "Opt_3_def": "careful", "Opt_4_def": "excellent"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The doctor examined the patient carefully, ____ that he forgot to check blood pressure.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The most important ____ of living near the school is that I can go home for lunch every day.", "Opt_1": "advantage", "Opt_2": "distance", "Opt_3": "argument", "Opt_4": "procedure", "Answer": "advantage", "Opt_1_def": "benefit", "Opt_2_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_3_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_4_def": "the way to do something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In order to match you up with the most ____ roommate we can, please fill out the Housing Intake Questionaire.", "Opt_1": "confident", "Opt_2": "wise", "Opt_3": "entire", "Opt_4": "compatible", "Answer": "compatible", "Opt_1_def": "sure that something will happen", "Opt_2_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_3_def": "whole, all", "Opt_4_def": "able to work with someone or something else"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Sometimes it is necessary to ____ force in order to achieve peace in a troubled region.", "Opt_1": "exert", "Opt_2": "raise", "Opt_3": "claim", "Opt_4": "comprise", "Answer": "exert", "Opt_1_def": "to use", "Opt_2_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_3_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_4_def": "to be made up of; to include"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Clinton certainly did not invent these word games, but in recent years they have risen to a high art ____ in Washington.", "Opt_1": "measure", "Opt_2": "fulfill", "Opt_3": "supervise", "Opt_4": "form", "Answer": "form", "Opt_1_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_2_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_3_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to make (into a shape)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If the student refuses to leave after being requested to do so, the instructor may summon University Police to ____ the student.", "Opt_1": "distribute", "Opt_2": "trust", "Opt_3": "shrink", "Opt_4": "remove", "Answer": "remove", "Opt_1_def": "to give out", "Opt_2_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_4_def": "to take away"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The IGH claims that Preval's ____ was the result of more information coming through.", "Opt_1": "accelerate", "Opt_2": "embody", "Opt_3": "demonstrate", "Opt_4": "decrease", "Answer": "decrease", "Opt_1_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_2_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to show", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller, to go down"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There were complications with the pregnancy, so she had to ____ starting school for a semester.", "Opt_1": "postpone", "Opt_2": "accomplish", "Opt_3": "suspend", "Opt_4": "retire", "Answer": "postpone", "Opt_1_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_2_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_3_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_4_def": "to stop working"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I'm not sure that his parents realize the ____ of the problems he is having in school.", "Opt_1": "doubt", "Opt_2": "extent", "Opt_3": "drawback", "Opt_4": "objective", "Answer": "extent", "Opt_1_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_2_def": "size, amount", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_4_def": "aim or goal"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Your ____ course grade will depend on your grades in the 3 trimester exams.", "Opt_1": "urgent", "Opt_2": "typical", "Opt_3": "compatible", "Opt_4": "final", "Answer": "final", "Opt_1_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_2_def": "usual", "Opt_3_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_4_def": "last"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This is the completely rational response of a country that has no hope of defeating the United States in battle but ____ wants to insure that it isn't attacked.", "Opt_1": "therefore", "Opt_2": "indeed", "Opt_3": "nevertheless", "Opt_4": "occasionally", "Answer": "nevertheless", "Opt_1_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_2_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_3_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_4_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions."}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "My father's ____ in Germany will terminate at the end of the year.", "Opt_1": "process", "Opt_2": "responsibility", "Opt_3": "contract", "Opt_4": "quantity", "Answer": "contract", "Opt_1_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_2_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_3_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Both Initial and Wokingham now ____ the figure for the cost of food and say it is lower.", "Opt_1": "policy", "Opt_2": "dispute", "Opt_3": "liberty", "Opt_4": "error", "Answer": "dispute", "Opt_1_def": "formal rules", "Opt_2_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_3_def": "freedom", "Opt_4_def": "a mistake"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Worse yet, 1992 was no ____ but the culmination of bad trends, most of them directly related to the company's lack of focus.", "Opt_1": "victory", "Opt_2": "legislation", "Opt_3": "doubt", "Opt_4": "anomaly", "Answer": "anomaly", "Opt_1_def": "win", "Opt_2_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_3_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_4_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Does anyone really believe that governments will ____ tax incomes on trillions of dollars of e-commerce sales?", "Opt_1": "enable", "Opt_2": "forego", "Opt_3": "acquire", "Opt_4": "afford", "Answer": "forego", "Opt_1_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_3_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_4_def": "to be able to pay for something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The Institute must take greater measures to assure students that they need not ____ consequences when seeking medical help for substance abuse.", "Opt_1": "qualify", "Opt_2": "fear", "Opt_3": "persist", "Opt_4": "conform", "Answer": "fear", "Opt_1_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_2_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_3_def": "to continue (often in the face of difficulty)", "Opt_4_def": "to do what is required"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "She has gained ____ good grades since she has started attending school more regularly.", "Opt_1": "barely", "Opt_2": "indeed", "Opt_3": "occasionally", "Opt_4": "predominantly", "Answer": "predominantly", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_2_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_3_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The development of ____ communication protocols is a critical issue in today's age of pervasive communication.", "Opt_1": "ancient", "Opt_2": "secure", "Opt_3": "stable", "Opt_4": "exact", "Answer": "secure", "Opt_1_def": "very old", "Opt_2_def": "safe", "Opt_3_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_4_def": "precise, opposite of approximate"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "How to increase employment and reduce crime are the two most ____ problems that confront the new government.", "Opt_1": "broad", "Opt_2": "diverse", "Opt_3": "firm", "Opt_4": "serious", "Answer": "serious", "Opt_1_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_2_def": "many and different", "Opt_3_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_4_def": "severe, large"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "How did you decide that some items were ____ necessary?", "Opt_1": "universally", "Opt_2": "definitely", "Opt_3": "absolutely", "Opt_4": "thus", "Answer": "absolutely", "Opt_1_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_2_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_3_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_4_def": "so"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In most countries of the world education is ____ for all children.", "Opt_1": "sole", "Opt_2": "subsequent", "Opt_3": "discrete", "Opt_4": "compulsory", "Answer": "compulsory", "Opt_1_def": "only", "Opt_2_def": "next, following", "Opt_3_def": "separate", "Opt_4_def": "required, must be done"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The university's plan to admit more students from poor backgrounds is an ____ that is not certain to succeed.", "Opt_1": "atmosphere", "Opt_2": "image", "Opt_3": "exercise", "Opt_4": "surface", "Answer": "exercise", "Opt_1_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_2_def": "picture", "Opt_3_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_4_def": "the outside layer of an object"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ information provides details on the spiking neuron model used in this work.", "Opt_1": "permanent", "Opt_2": "supplementary", "Opt_3": "harsh", "Opt_4": "inevitable", "Answer": "supplementary", "Opt_1_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time", "Opt_2_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_3_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "While you may not admit to political pressure, you must be ____ of its almost constant presence; and you must recognize it and be prepared to deal with it.", "Opt_1": "profound", "Opt_2": "aware", "Opt_3": "loose", "Opt_4": "ambiguous", "Answer": "aware", "Opt_1_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_2_def": "knowing", "Opt_3_def": "not firm or finished", "Opt_4_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The winner of the competition must ____ a plan to remove greenhouse gases from the atmosphere without creating adverse effects.", "Opt_1": "supervise", "Opt_2": "devise", "Opt_3": "derive", "Opt_4": "predict", "Answer": "devise", "Opt_1_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_3_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_4_def": "to say what will happen in the future"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The main cause of her poor grades are her ____ absences from school.", "Opt_1": "poor", "Opt_2": "discrete", "Opt_3": "frequent", "Opt_4": "complex", "Answer": "frequent", "Opt_1_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_2_def": "separate", "Opt_3_def": "often", "Opt_4_def": "difficult, complicated"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "TSU Employees who ____ University network and computing resources may be subject to disciplinary action.", "Opt_1": "release", "Opt_2": "enable", "Opt_3": "deserve", "Opt_4": "abuse", "Answer": "abuse", "Opt_1_def": "to let go or let out", "Opt_2_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_4_def": "to treat someone or something badly"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The Bush administration will not back down on pursuing new sanctions against Iran over its nuclear program ____ questions about their effectiveness.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "despite", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "although"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In 1993 a student wrote an article critical of Martin Luther King. The response was ____ and negative.", "Opt_1": "concise", "Opt_2": "fortunate", "Opt_3": "distinct", "Opt_4": "immediate", "Answer": "immediate", "Opt_1_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_2_def": "lucky", "Opt_3_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_4_def": "first (without delay)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The Latin alphabet did not ____ between the vowel and consonant sounds of i and u.", "Opt_1": "proceed", "Opt_2": "distinguish", "Opt_3": "fulfill", "Opt_4": "eliminate", "Answer": "distinguish", "Opt_1_def": "to go forward (and do ..)", "Opt_2_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_4_def": "to dispose of"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "For my next step I would ____ to the students certain distinctions that might at first glance seem to be completely arbitrary or valueless.", "Opt_1": "propose", "Opt_2": "complicate", "Opt_3": "fade", "Opt_4": "disperse", "Answer": "propose", "Opt_1_def": "to suggest", "Opt_2_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_3_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_4_def": "to spread out; to move apart"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Many language teachers believe that their learners should use only ____ materials, not ones especially made for ESL students.", "Opt_1": "infinite", "Opt_2": "visual", "Opt_3": "authentic", "Opt_4": "familiar", "Answer": "authentic", "Opt_1_def": "without an end", "Opt_2_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_3_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_4_def": "known; well-known"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Television and the other news media have helped to magnify the person and the ____ of the presidency.", "Opt_1": "province", "Opt_2": "institution", "Opt_3": "region", "Opt_4": "asset", "Answer": "institution", "Opt_1_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_2_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_3_def": "part of a place", "Opt_4_def": "advantage"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There is a growing ____ to use the cell phone as the primary phone, without any need for landlines.", "Opt_1": "series", "Opt_2": "instruction", "Opt_3": "trend", "Opt_4": "level", "Answer": "trend", "Opt_1_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_2_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_3_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "standard; layer; amount"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The court also held that because of the ____ between the classification society and the shipyard, the owners operated the ship under the French flag.", "Opt_1": "contract", "Opt_2": "crisis", "Opt_3": "progress", "Opt_4": "transition", "Answer": "contract", "Opt_1_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_2_def": "very dangerous situation, catastrophe", "Opt_3_def": "improvement or development", "Opt_4_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is not easy to represent an abstract idea in picture ____ so that ESL students can understand it.", "Opt_1": "contemplate", "Opt_2": "form", "Opt_3": "distort", "Opt_4": "continue", "Answer": "form", "Opt_1_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_2_def": "to make (into a shape)", "Opt_3_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_4_def": "to carry on, not stop"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Furthermore, as an educational institution, the College cannot ____ the background and perspectives of its students and must attempt to promote teaching practices and a campus atmosphere that benefits and ensures the success of all of its learners.", "Opt_1": "induce", "Opt_2": "ignore", "Opt_3": "transfer", "Opt_4": "investigate", "Answer": "ignore", "Opt_1_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_2_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_3_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_4_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "A ____ driving license does not entitle the license holder to drive a bus or a truck.", "Opt_1": "chief", "Opt_2": "regular", "Opt_3": "effective", "Opt_4": "verbal", "Answer": "regular", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_3_def": "good, working well", "Opt_4_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Your writing shows a basic ____ of care or thought.", "Opt_1": "duty", "Opt_2": "lack", "Opt_3": "responsibility", "Opt_4": "conflict", "Answer": "lack", "Opt_1_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_2_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_3_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_4_def": "problem, struggle or battle"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Many a ____ that was once believed by everyone later proves to be false - e.g. that the sun goes around the earth.", "Opt_1": "theory", "Opt_2": "demand", "Opt_3": "event", "Opt_4": "implication", "Answer": "theory", "Opt_1_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_2_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_3_def": "a happening", "Opt_4_def": "result or consequence"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Do you think that the school will ____ the suggestion to increase the number of holidays?", "Opt_1": "cover", "Opt_2": "approve", "Opt_3": "focus", "Opt_4": "advocate", "Answer": "approve", "Opt_1_def": "to do; to complete", "Opt_2_def": "to agree to", "Opt_3_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_4_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Well done. The ____ of all your labour is an fine grade in your ESL test.", "Opt_1": "result", "Opt_2": "skill", "Opt_3": "bias", "Opt_4": "exponent", "Answer": "result", "Opt_1_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_2_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_3_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_4_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Students needed to devote ____ time to recognizing the three basic tenses (past, present, and future) and using the appropriate tense in their own writing.", "Opt_1": "official", "Opt_2": "considerable", "Opt_3": "abundant", "Opt_4": "capable", "Answer": "considerable", "Opt_1_def": "approved by an authority", "Opt_2_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_3_def": "existing in large quantities", "Opt_4_def": "able"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The lack of available parking spaces is a significant ____ to faculty and students.", "Opt_1": "speed", "Opt_2": "object", "Opt_3": "detriment", "Opt_4": "privilege", "Answer": "detriment", "Opt_1_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_2_def": "thing", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_4_def": "a right (to do something)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is not difficult to ____ on what could happen to these laws if the computer really does change our attitude to knowledge.", "Opt_1": "compel", "Opt_2": "include", "Opt_3": "speculate", "Opt_4": "distribute", "Answer": "speculate", "Opt_1_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_2_def": "to put in; to have in", "Opt_3_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_4_def": "to give out"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Significant progress has been toward reaching this ____ through the broad workforce planning effort as well as specific unit managerial decisions.", "Opt_1": "concept", "Opt_2": "version", "Opt_3": "goal", "Opt_4": "duration", "Answer": "goal", "Opt_1_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_2_def": "form", "Opt_3_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The Education Department's increased ____ for paperwork will strain the patience and good will of teachers.", "Opt_1": "diagnosis", "Opt_2": "supply", "Opt_3": "demand", "Opt_4": "structure", "Answer": "demand", "Opt_1_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_2_def": "provision, store", "Opt_3_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_4_def": "the way something is made or organized"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Successful applicants will have to provide ____ of medical insurance for the duration of their stay in the Ukraine.", "Opt_1": "revenue", "Opt_2": "district", "Opt_3": "range", "Opt_4": "evidence", "Answer": "evidence", "Opt_1_def": "money, income", "Opt_2_def": "region of a city", "Opt_3_def": "extent, distance between two points", "Opt_4_def": "proof, signs"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Scientists don't know how to ____ drought a month or more in advance for most locations.", "Opt_1": "judge", "Opt_2": "inspect", "Opt_3": "predict", "Opt_4": "evaluate", "Answer": "predict", "Opt_1_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_4_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "During this course you will review your knowledge of German, by focusing on the four language skills, ____ speaking, listening, reading and writing.", "Opt_1": "namely", "Opt_2": "extremely", "Opt_3": "especially", "Opt_4": "occasionally", "Answer": "namely", "Opt_1_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_2_def": "very", "Opt_3_def": "particularly", "Opt_4_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions."}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "What is the correct key ____ on a calculator for working out a percentage from a fraction?", "Opt_1": "sequence", "Opt_2": "potential", "Opt_3": "design", "Opt_4": "prejudice", "Answer": "sequence", "Opt_1_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_2_def": "good possibility", "Opt_3_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_4_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You will need to get your parents' ____ for your attendance at the sex education classes.", "Opt_1": "career", "Opt_2": "stereotype", "Opt_3": "lecture", "Opt_4": "assent", "Answer": "assent", "Opt_1_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_2_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_3_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "agreement"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The ____ question in the test was the most difficult.", "Opt_1": "temporary", "Opt_2": "practical", "Opt_3": "final", "Opt_4": "overall", "Answer": "final", "Opt_1_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_2_def": "useful; possible", "Opt_3_def": "last", "Opt_4_def": "general"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The idea that there is ____ in nature is part of most world views.", "Opt_1": "impact", "Opt_2": "hierarchy", "Opt_3": "circumstances", "Opt_4": "balance", "Answer": "balance", "Opt_1_def": "effect", "Opt_2_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_3_def": "situation", "Opt_4_def": "equalness"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It is an advantage for a politician to be able to give a clear but ____ statement of what he or she believes in.", "Opt_1": "vital", "Opt_2": "concise", "Opt_3": "adequate", "Opt_4": "obvious", "Answer": "concise", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_3_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_4_def": "clear, evident"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Doctors are ____ encouraged by the reduction in the numbers of young people starting to smoke.", "Opt_1": "somewhat", "Opt_2": "nevertheless", "Opt_3": "roughly", "Opt_4": "recently", "Answer": "somewhat", "Opt_1_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_2_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_3_def": "about, approximately", "Opt_4_def": "in the near past"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Israel and Korea are two countries that have compulsory ____ service for their male citizens.", "Opt_1": "minor", "Opt_2": "cautious", "Opt_3": "sane", "Opt_4": "military", "Answer": "military", "Opt_1_def": "small, not important", "Opt_2_def": "careful", "Opt_3_def": "reasonable; not mad", "Opt_4_def": "to do with army"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Unfortunately, many drug users emerge from prison only to find themselves back there a few months later. This is because they cannot find or keep a job, and need to steal to ____ their drug-taking habits.", "Opt_1": "finance", "Opt_2": "term", "Opt_3": "purpose", "Opt_4": "growth", "Answer": "finance", "Opt_1_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_2_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_3_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_4_def": "development, increase"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "A student who fails to cite sources in a deliberate attempt to ____ the source of the work should be considered to be cheating.", "Opt_1": "emerge", "Opt_2": "conceal", "Opt_3": "install", "Opt_4": "request", "Answer": "conceal", "Opt_1_def": "to come out; to become known", "Opt_2_def": "to hide", "Opt_3_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_4_def": "to ask politely"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Testing personnel will not ____ any tester who is cheating, but will complete the Testing Incident Report and submit to the supervisor.", "Opt_1": "confront", "Opt_2": "afford", "Opt_3": "undergo", "Opt_4": "amend", "Answer": "confront", "Opt_1_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_2_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_3_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_4_def": "to change (usually to improve something)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The geographer urges upon his students that they first master those principles and then consider the ____ problems.", "Opt_1": "subsequent", "Opt_2": "sufficient", "Opt_3": "suitable", "Opt_4": "legal", "Answer": "subsequent", "Opt_1_def": "next, following", "Opt_2_def": "enough", "Opt_3_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "After 11 years at the helm of the Scientific Computing Division, Bill Buzbee recently announced his intention to ____ at the end of this year.", "Opt_1": "alter", "Opt_2": "retire", "Opt_3": "ignore", "Opt_4": "comprehend", "Answer": "retire", "Opt_1_def": "to change", "Opt_2_def": "to stop working", "Opt_3_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_4_def": "to understand"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In some businesses it is the ____ that the eldest son takes over when the father dies.", "Opt_1": "bond", "Opt_2": "priority", "Opt_3": "tradition", "Opt_4": "quantity", "Answer": "tradition", "Opt_1_def": "link; tie", "Opt_2_def": "first and most important task", "Opt_3_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The university follows a ____ policy of expelling any student caught plagiarizing.", "Opt_1": "strict", "Opt_2": "adequate", "Opt_3": "uniform", "Opt_4": "stable", "Answer": "strict", "Opt_1_def": "hard, not changeable", "Opt_2_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_3_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_4_def": "not changing; not easy to change"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The company report did not do much to ____ the reasons for the fall in business in the previous year.", "Opt_1": "precede", "Opt_2": "lessen", "Opt_3": "confine", "Opt_4": "illuminate", "Answer": "illuminate", "Opt_1_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to reduce", "Opt_3_def": "to limit", "Opt_4_def": "to show clearly; to light up"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Many people used to believe that if cancer did not ____ within five years, a person was safe.", "Opt_1": "recur", "Opt_2": "continue", "Opt_3": "dedicate", "Opt_4": "depend", "Answer": "recur", "Opt_1_def": "to happen again", "Opt_2_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_3_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_4_def": "be influenced (by)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "He may ____ to any political party he pleases, or he may ____ to none.", "Opt_1": "belong", "Opt_2": "reward", "Opt_3": "reverse", "Opt_4": "illuminate", "Answer": "belong", "Opt_1_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_2_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_4_def": "to show clearly; to light up"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The school is likely to lose students if the government goes ahead with its proposed ____ to reduce tax benefits for parents.", "Opt_1": "rise", "Opt_2": "instruction", "Opt_3": "legislation", "Opt_4": "generation", "Answer": "legislation", "Opt_1_def": "to go up", "Opt_2_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_3_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_4_def": "group of people all born around the same time"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Listening to the people is an intrinsic ____ of good government.", "Opt_1": "phase", "Opt_2": "district", "Opt_3": "aspect", "Opt_4": "detriment", "Answer": "aspect", "Opt_1_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_2_def": "region of a city", "Opt_3_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain.", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "For some people God is an ____ that influences every aspect of their life.", "Opt_1": "support", "Opt_2": "entity", "Opt_3": "surface", "Opt_4": "shortage", "Answer": "entity", "Opt_1_def": "help", "Opt_2_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_3_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_4_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If a student is caught with drugs in the building, the school will ____ him or her.", "Opt_1": "expel", "Opt_2": "construct", "Opt_3": "reserve", "Opt_4": "threaten", "Answer": "expel", "Opt_1_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_2_def": "to make", "Opt_3_def": "to keep", "Opt_4_def": "to warn or show signs of danger"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Any student who is at least 13 years old on September 30 is eligible to ____ the mathematics competition.", "Opt_1": "accuse", "Opt_2": "claim", "Opt_3": "speculate", "Opt_4": "enter", "Answer": "enter", "Opt_1_def": "to blame", "Opt_2_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_3_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_4_def": "to go in or put in"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In an article in the March 11, 2004 ____ of Nature, the investigators report that female mice retain the ability to make new egg cells well into adulthood.", "Opt_1": "hierarchy", "Opt_2": "figure", "Opt_3": "issue", "Opt_4": "hypothesis", "Answer": "issue", "Opt_1_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_2_def": "number", "Opt_3_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_4_def": "idea or prediction"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Students, staff and faculty have a right to privacy and neither reporters nor the public should be allowed to ____ classroom instruction.", "Opt_1": "disrupt", "Opt_2": "regulate", "Opt_3": "enlarge", "Opt_4": "interact", "Answer": "disrupt", "Opt_1_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_2_def": "to control", "Opt_3_def": "to make larger", "Opt_4_def": "to react, to affect and be affected"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The accident was clearly not the ____ of the employee or his supervisor.", "Opt_1": "bias", "Opt_2": "battle", "Opt_3": "assent", "Opt_4": "fault", "Answer": "fault", "Opt_1_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_2_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_3_def": "agreement", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is not the only method of teaching we use at the university; ____ we calibrate our teaching techniques to fit our abilities.", "Opt_1": "besides", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We believe that individuals who respect and support a ____ global society will prosper as leaders in schools, universities, businesses, and human service.", "Opt_1": "secure", "Opt_2": "instant", "Opt_3": "diverse", "Opt_4": "pure", "Answer": "diverse", "Opt_1_def": "safe", "Opt_2_def": "immediate", "Opt_3_def": "many and different", "Opt_4_def": "complete, 100%"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ of young men who walk around with large aggressive dogs is that they are from the working class and are criminals.", "Opt_1": "extract", "Opt_2": "stereotype", "Opt_3": "contrast", "Opt_4": "code", "Answer": "stereotype", "Opt_1_def": "to remove; to take out and use", "Opt_2_def": "a fixed idea about someone or something (often that is only partly true)", "Opt_3_def": "difference", "Opt_4_def": "a set of rules"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "A student whose total absences in a course, excused or unexcused, ____ ten per trimester is liable to fail the course.", "Opt_1": "exceed", "Opt_2": "allege", "Opt_3": "judge", "Opt_4": "permit", "Answer": "exceed", "Opt_1_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_2_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_3_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to allow"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "During the period of time that a student is on probation, any further instance of misconduct will cause the Board seriously to ____ requiring the student to withdraw from the College.", "Opt_1": "trade", "Opt_2": "transmit", "Opt_3": "manage", "Opt_4": "consider", "Answer": "consider", "Opt_1_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_2_def": "to send or convey", "Opt_3_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to think"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "This course list should ____ the number of credits and the grade option (grade, pass/fail, audit) for each enrolled student.", "Opt_1": "appoint", "Opt_2": "signify", "Opt_3": "enumerate", "Opt_4": "deduce", "Answer": "enumerate", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_3_def": "to list", "Opt_4_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The online instructor must ____ the best practices of traditional teaching without the benefit of face-to-face interaction.", "Opt_1": "accumulate", "Opt_2": "communicate", "Opt_3": "incorporate", "Opt_4": "warn", "Answer": "incorporate", "Opt_1_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_2_def": "to convey information", "Opt_3_def": "to include", "Opt_4_def": "to notify (of possible danger)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The Bush administration will not back down on pursuing new sanctions ____ Iran over its nuclear program despite questions about their effectiveness.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "against", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "against", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "An analysis of the historical causes of slavery is beyond the ____ of this course.", "Opt_1": "format", "Opt_2": "scope", "Opt_3": "formula", "Opt_4": "detail", "Answer": "scope", "Opt_1_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_2_def": "extent, range", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "a small piece of information"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government does not plan to ____ any more immigrants unless they can prove that their life is in danger in their own country.", "Opt_1": "reinforce", "Opt_2": "append", "Opt_3": "admit", "Opt_4": "lessen", "Answer": "admit", "Opt_1_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_2_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_3_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_4_def": "to reduce"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In my school district it is emphasized that teachers must differentiate ____ for students.", "Opt_1": "function", "Opt_2": "instruction", "Opt_3": "cycle", "Opt_4": "transition", "Answer": "instruction", "Opt_1_def": "job or role", "Opt_2_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_3_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_4_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "When societies ____ into violence the result is all too familiar: the destruction of life and infrastructure, gross abuses of human rights.", "Opt_1": "improve", "Opt_2": "sustain", "Opt_3": "adopt", "Opt_4": "collapse", "Answer": "collapse", "Opt_1_def": "to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_3_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_4_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In the face of the success of industrialization, individuals must ____ and form institutions that would be in line with this task.", "Opt_1": "force", "Opt_2": "apply", "Opt_3": "unite", "Opt_4": "ban", "Answer": "unite", "Opt_1_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_2_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_4_def": "to prohibit or forbid"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ area of Frankfurt is to the south east of the city center.", "Opt_1": "severe", "Opt_2": "firm", "Opt_3": "anonymous", "Opt_4": "commercial", "Answer": "commercial", "Opt_1_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_2_def": "strong, cannot be changed", "Opt_3_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_4_def": "to do with business"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government is thinking of passing a law that will ____ all house owners to exchange their oil heating system for one that runs on gas.", "Opt_1": "precede", "Opt_2": "align", "Opt_3": "require", "Opt_4": "tolerate", "Answer": "require", "Opt_1_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_3_def": "to need", "Opt_4_def": "to allow to happen; to bear"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some scientists believe that genetically modified food can ____ people's health.", "Opt_1": "exert", "Opt_2": "assess", "Opt_3": "harm", "Opt_4": "consent", "Answer": "harm", "Opt_1_def": "to use", "Opt_2_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_3_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_4_def": "to agree"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Groups should ____ the instructor if a member is unexpectedly absent and try to save materials for that person.", "Opt_1": "restrict", "Opt_2": "subsidize", "Opt_3": "adapt", "Opt_4": "advise", "Answer": "advise", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to support financially", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_4_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government failed to keep its promises and ____ was voted out of power at the next election.", "Opt_1": "generally", "Opt_2": "gradually", "Opt_3": "naturally", "Opt_4": "fairly", "Answer": "naturally", "Opt_1_def": "usually", "Opt_2_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_3_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_4_def": "quite, somewhat"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Your report is good, but you need to ____ a paragraph on the causes of the accident.", "Opt_1": "investigate", "Opt_2": "examine", "Opt_3": "involve", "Opt_4": "add", "Answer": "add", "Opt_1_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_2_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to include or mean", "Opt_4_def": "to include; to give or say extra"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government has increased the tax on petrol, ____ making itself very unpopular with motorists.", "Opt_1": "moreover", "Opt_2": "greatly", "Opt_3": "hardly", "Opt_4": "thereby", "Answer": "thereby", "Opt_1_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_2_def": "very much", "Opt_3_def": "not very much", "Opt_4_def": "by doing this"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A major defect in the proposal is that there is not sufficient money to ____ it.", "Opt_1": "service", "Opt_2": "quality", "Opt_3": "standard", "Opt_4": "finance", "Answer": "finance", "Opt_1_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_2_def": "worth or value", "Opt_3_def": "quality", "Opt_4_def": "to do with money and payment"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Everyone has the right to a standard of living ____ for the health and well-being of himself and of his family, including food, clothing, and shelter.", "Opt_1": "adequate", "Opt_2": "extraordinary", "Opt_3": "sole", "Opt_4": "complete", "Answer": "adequate", "Opt_1_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_2_def": "very unusual", "Opt_3_def": "only", "Opt_4_def": "full or finished"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In the heat of election campaigning, it is in no-one's interest to ____ an artificial crisis upon the economy.", "Opt_1": "discern", "Opt_2": "suppress", "Opt_3": "impose", "Opt_4": "release", "Answer": "impose", "Opt_1_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_2_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to force; to require to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to let go or let out"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government needs to use a more ____ approach to persuading people to eat less and keep fit.", "Opt_1": "subtle", "Opt_2": "utter", "Opt_3": "mobile", "Opt_4": "significant", "Answer": "subtle", "Opt_1_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_2_def": "complete, total", "Opt_3_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_4_def": "important, large"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "They have to stop and ask those questions because the internet is not the best ____ of all information.", "Opt_1": "device", "Opt_2": "source", "Opt_3": "gain", "Opt_4": "entity", "Answer": "source", "Opt_1_def": "object; method", "Opt_2_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_3_def": "to get; to increase in ..", "Opt_4_def": "thing; body; organization"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "While you may not admit to political pressure, you must be aware of its almost ____ presence; and you must recognize it and be prepared to deal with it.", "Opt_1": "constant", "Opt_2": "convenient", "Opt_3": "vague", "Opt_4": "previous", "Answer": "constant", "Opt_1_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_2_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_3_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_4_def": "the one before"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I suspect that difficulties at home ____ her recent poor performance in school.", "Opt_1": "underlie", "Opt_2": "edit", "Opt_3": "fare", "Opt_4": "acknowledge", "Answer": "underlie", "Opt_1_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_2_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_4_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Could you please ____ to our Christmas collection for flood victims in Bangladesh?", "Opt_1": "contribute", "Opt_2": "incorporate", "Opt_3": "inquire", "Opt_4": "circulate", "Answer": "contribute", "Opt_1_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_2_def": "to include", "Opt_3_def": "to ask", "Opt_4_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The system uses a ____ inference engine that does not require users to explicitly provide information about the start or ending points of their journeys.", "Opt_1": "likely", "Opt_2": "novel", "Opt_3": "efficient", "Opt_4": "ambiguous", "Answer": "novel", "Opt_1_def": "probable", "Opt_2_def": "new", "Opt_3_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_4_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It should be obvious that the consumption habits of the wealthy countries are the ____ cause of environmental problems.", "Opt_1": "valuable", "Opt_2": "prime", "Opt_3": "comprehensive", "Opt_4": "infinite", "Answer": "prime", "Opt_1_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "full, complete", "Opt_4_def": "without an end"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The wishes of parents must not always ____ the recommendations of the teachers about the course choices of the child.", "Opt_1": "degenerate", "Opt_2": "recommend", "Opt_3": "override", "Opt_4": "possess", "Answer": "override", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_3_def": "to take precedence over; to disregard", "Opt_4_def": "to have or own"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There are various ways that you can improve your English. Probably the best is to do ____ of reading.", "Opt_1": "controversy", "Opt_2": "choice", "Opt_3": "plenty", "Opt_4": "limit", "Answer": "plenty", "Opt_1_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_2_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_3_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_4_def": "extent, boundary"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The university has no ____ to refund the fee after the second week of the semester.", "Opt_1": "speed", "Opt_2": "obligation", "Opt_3": "treatment", "Opt_4": "justice", "Answer": "obligation", "Opt_1_def": "how quickly something moves or changes", "Opt_2_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_3_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_4_def": "fairness in law"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There were complications with the pregnancy, so she had to ____ starting school for a semester.", "Opt_1": "appoint", "Opt_2": "collaborate", "Opt_3": "connect", "Opt_4": "postpone", "Answer": "postpone", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_2_def": "to work together", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_4_def": "to put back in time"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You have received this e-mail in the ____ belief that its contents would be of interest to you.", "Opt_1": "overall", "Opt_2": "genuine", "Opt_3": "serious", "Opt_4": "contemporary", "Answer": "genuine", "Opt_1_def": "general", "Opt_2_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_3_def": "severe, large", "Opt_4_def": "of this time, happening now"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government announced that it was pleased with the ____ fall in unemployment during its term in office.", "Opt_1": "intense", "Opt_2": "subtle", "Opt_3": "immense", "Opt_4": "steady", "Answer": "steady", "Opt_1_def": "strong, extreme", "Opt_2_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The proponents of disability rights and design professionals have come to ____ that the concept of accessible design has to be rethought.", "Opt_1": "neglect", "Opt_2": "govern", "Opt_3": "migrate", "Opt_4": "realize", "Answer": "realize", "Opt_1_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_2_def": "to control or influence", "Opt_3_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_4_def": "to come to know or understand"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Omitting the transportation costs would ____ the company's financial position.", "Opt_1": "consume", "Opt_2": "clarify", "Opt_3": "distort", "Opt_4": "exhaust", "Answer": "distort", "Opt_1_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_2_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_3_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_4_def": "to use up"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The strategy used for the actual campaign was ____ different.", "Opt_1": "naturally", "Opt_2": "namely", "Opt_3": "fairly", "Opt_4": "somewhat", "Answer": "somewhat", "Opt_1_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_2_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_3_def": "quite, somewhat", "Opt_4_def": "quite, rather"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "She had a flash of ____ that she was going to fail her exams unless she started working.", "Opt_1": "society", "Opt_2": "support", "Opt_3": "citizen", "Opt_4": "insight", "Answer": "insight", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_2_def": "help", "Opt_3_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_4_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You need to try and ____ your thoughts a little more clearly. This does not make much sense to me.", "Opt_1": "donate", "Opt_2": "attach", "Opt_3": "accelerate", "Opt_4": "formulate", "Answer": "formulate", "Opt_1_def": "to give (usually money)", "Opt_2_def": "to put together with", "Opt_3_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_4_def": "to express"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The UN soldiers lost ____ of the village when it was invaded by terrorist fighters.", "Opt_1": "rise", "Opt_2": "item", "Opt_3": "pattern", "Opt_4": "command", "Answer": "command", "Opt_1_def": "to go up", "Opt_2_def": "thing, element", "Opt_3_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "control"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Most teachers are ____ to students wearing hats or chewing gum in the classroom.", "Opt_1": "forthcoming", "Opt_2": "vital", "Opt_3": "efficient", "Opt_4": "averse", "Answer": "averse", "Opt_1_def": "coming soon", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "working quickly and easily", "Opt_4_def": "against"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The word give is substituted for the word ____ to express more clearly the intent of the section.", "Opt_1": "lessen", "Opt_2": "master", "Opt_3": "protest", "Opt_4": "deliver", "Answer": "deliver", "Opt_1_def": "to reduce", "Opt_2_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_3_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_4_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Ours is the only generation that can prevent a ____ loss of biological diversity.", "Opt_1": "massive", "Opt_2": "numerous", "Opt_3": "trivial", "Opt_4": "moderate", "Answer": "massive", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "very many", "Opt_3_def": "not important", "Opt_4_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Many large companies employ people to analyze a ____ such as the way people spend their money on holiday, etc.", "Opt_1": "society", "Opt_2": "circumstances", "Opt_3": "image", "Opt_4": "trend", "Answer": "trend", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people; the entire group of people living in a country", "Opt_2_def": "situation", "Opt_3_def": "picture", "Opt_4_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Which activity are you going to ____ next time? - I think I'll try chess.", "Opt_1": "reinforce", "Opt_2": "select", "Opt_3": "reflect", "Opt_4": "manifest", "Answer": "select", "Opt_1_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_2_def": "to choose", "Opt_3_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_4_def": "show"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It's a bit surprising at first, how easy it is to measure such a huge ____ as the earth.", "Opt_1": "object", "Opt_2": "defeat", "Opt_3": "guide", "Opt_4": "quality", "Answer": "object", "Opt_1_def": "thing", "Opt_2_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_3_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_4_def": "worth or value"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Administrators and supervisors are expected to see that those who report to them are informed about, understand and ____ with regulations.", "Opt_1": "amend", "Opt_2": "comply", "Opt_3": "withdraw", "Opt_4": "signify", "Answer": "comply", "Opt_1_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_2_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_3_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to be a sign of"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There is not an ____ supply of oil and natural gas.", "Opt_1": "instant", "Opt_2": "rapid", "Opt_3": "sound", "Opt_4": "infinite", "Answer": "infinite", "Opt_1_def": "immediate", "Opt_2_def": "quick", "Opt_3_def": "good; strong", "Opt_4_def": "without an end"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is scheduled to begin at 3:30 p.m. A decision to ____ or postpone the match will be made later in the day, if necessary.", "Opt_1": "succeed", "Opt_2": "cancel", "Opt_3": "diminish", "Opt_4": "violate", "Answer": "cancel", "Opt_1_def": "to do well", "Opt_2_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller or less important", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or break"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Historically, there was ____ for crop and livestock losses, but the problem of estimating the damage and lack of funds for ____ programs has been significant.", "Opt_1": "defect", "Opt_2": "scope", "Opt_3": "formula", "Opt_4": "compensation", "Answer": "compensation", "Opt_1_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_2_def": "extent, range", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Strong families ____ the ability to manage both daily stressors and difficult life crises creatively and effectively.", "Opt_1": "notice", "Opt_2": "retreat", "Opt_3": "possess", "Opt_4": "commence", "Answer": "possess", "Opt_1_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_2_def": "to go back", "Opt_3_def": "to have or own", "Opt_4_def": "to start"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "One ____ of the essay is good, but the rest is of poor quality.", "Opt_1": "portion", "Opt_2": "commodity", "Opt_3": "record", "Opt_4": "duration", "Answer": "portion", "Opt_1_def": "part, amount", "Opt_2_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_3_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Most companies guarantee to ____ machines, like refrigerators or computers, if they break down in the first year.", "Opt_1": "attempt", "Opt_2": "replace", "Opt_3": "extend", "Opt_4": "confirm", "Answer": "replace", "Opt_1_def": "to try", "Opt_2_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_4_def": "to agree that something is correct"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Science and technology are driving explosive growth in the production of new knowledge, often with the power to ____ profound changes in society.", "Opt_1": "induce", "Opt_2": "deserve", "Opt_3": "disperse", "Opt_4": "ignore", "Answer": "induce", "Opt_1_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_2_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_3_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_4_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Oddly, however, the book is almost completely ____ in fictional representations of invalids.", "Opt_1": "deficient", "Opt_2": "reasonable", "Opt_3": "radical", "Opt_4": "numerous", "Answer": "deficient", "Opt_1_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_2_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_3_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_4_def": "very many"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "ESS is for students who envision getting involved in the social ____ in any capacity: as volunteer consultants, board members, managers, or entrepreneurs.", "Opt_1": "notion", "Opt_2": "sector", "Opt_3": "episode", "Opt_4": "opinion", "Answer": "sector", "Opt_1_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_2_def": "part; area", "Opt_3_def": "period of time", "Opt_4_def": "view; what you think about someone or something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "What is the correct key ____ on a calculator for working out a percentage from a fraction?", "Opt_1": "precaution", "Opt_2": "sequence", "Opt_3": "responsibility", "Opt_4": "influence", "Answer": "sequence", "Opt_1_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_2_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_3_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_4_def": "effect"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "My science teacher returned my homework and told me to do it again. She said I had to use the ____ format for lab reports.", "Opt_1": "standard", "Opt_2": "reluctance", "Opt_3": "hierarchy", "Opt_4": "legislation", "Answer": "standard", "Opt_1_def": "quality", "Opt_2_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_3_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_4_def": "governmental rule; law"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You can take any book ____ this one. I'm reading it.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "They taste good and ____ us with vitamin C, potassium, and other vitamins and minerals.", "Opt_1": "evidence", "Opt_2": "supply", "Opt_3": "generation", "Opt_4": "implication", "Answer": "supply", "Opt_1_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_2_def": "provision, store", "Opt_3_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_4_def": "result or consequence"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Spending months at a time in orbit, the scientists will be able to observe changes on the earth ____ them from day to day.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "You should write this again to ____ all the irrelevant details.", "Opt_1": "access", "Opt_2": "passage", "Opt_3": "attribute", "Opt_4": "extract", "Answer": "extract", "Opt_1_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_2_def": "a piece of written or spoken text", "Opt_3_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_4_def": "to remove; to take out and use"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A ____ in science or engineering usually pays more than one in manufacturing.", "Opt_1": "attack", "Opt_2": "status", "Opt_3": "means", "Opt_4": "career", "Answer": "career", "Opt_1_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_2_def": "position, standing", "Opt_3_def": "way", "Opt_4_def": "a long-term job"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The government reports a ____ decrease in unemployment in the last month.", "Opt_1": "smooth", "Opt_2": "regular", "Opt_3": "slight", "Opt_4": "subtle", "Answer": "slight", "Opt_1_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_2_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_3_def": "small", "Opt_4_def": "not clear or strong"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If I make a comparison of England and Germany, I have to say I ____ Germany. The weather is better and the people are more friendly.", "Opt_1": "propose", "Opt_2": "denote", "Opt_3": "invent", "Opt_4": "prefer", "Answer": "prefer", "Opt_1_def": "to suggest", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_3_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_4_def": "to like better"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It's always better to be overly ____ and to protect yourself by asking for a written contract.", "Opt_1": "cautious", "Opt_2": "genuine", "Opt_3": "compulsory", "Opt_4": "former", "Answer": "cautious", "Opt_1_def": "careful", "Opt_2_def": "real and authentic", "Opt_3_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_4_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The correct ____ of this text requires recovering certain implicit information that relies on commonsense knowledge.", "Opt_1": "contract", "Opt_2": "interpretation", "Opt_3": "circumstances", "Opt_4": "contrast", "Answer": "interpretation", "Opt_1_def": "a written agreement, binding in law", "Opt_2_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_3_def": "situation", "Opt_4_def": "difference"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The programme will include several basic creative thinking techniques and this theme will ____ in problem-solving mode in Part 2 of the programme.", "Opt_1": "approach", "Opt_2": "abandon", "Opt_3": "approve", "Opt_4": "recur", "Answer": "recur", "Opt_1_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_2_def": "to leave or give up", "Opt_3_def": "to agree to", "Opt_4_def": "to happen again"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The 7 Harry Potter books have been published at an ____ of about 2-3 years.", "Opt_1": "interval", "Opt_2": "process", "Opt_3": "resident", "Opt_4": "decade", "Answer": "interval", "Opt_1_def": "a period of time", "Opt_2_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_3_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_4_def": "a period of ten years"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "When used correctly and consistently, condoms are an ____ means of preventing pregnancy.", "Opt_1": "complex", "Opt_2": "brief", "Opt_3": "effective", "Opt_4": "liable", "Answer": "effective", "Opt_1_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_2_def": "short", "Opt_3_def": "good, working well", "Opt_4_def": "likely to happen; at risk of happening"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The optical characteristics of the new hardware will have a ____ implication on high-speed networking across the globe.", "Opt_1": "voluntary", "Opt_2": "profound", "Opt_3": "ultimate", "Opt_4": "poor", "Answer": "profound", "Opt_1_def": "done freely; from personal choice", "Opt_2_def": "deep; great; serious", "Opt_3_def": "final or most important", "Opt_4_def": "bad, unsatisfactory"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Access to the data network is both an essential tool for university life and work, and a ____ privilege.", "Opt_1": "valuable", "Opt_2": "initial", "Opt_3": "averse", "Opt_4": "superior", "Answer": "valuable", "Opt_1_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_2_def": "starting, first", "Opt_3_def": "against", "Opt_4_def": "better"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We must hope that her heavy involvement in the school's sporting programme will not be to the ____ of her studies.", "Opt_1": "factor", "Opt_2": "debate", "Opt_3": "detriment", "Opt_4": "doubt", "Answer": "detriment", "Opt_1_def": "an aspect to be considered", "Opt_2_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_3_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_4_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Picasso's ____ to draw found expression in a variety of forms.", "Opt_1": "impulse", "Opt_2": "object", "Opt_3": "sample", "Opt_4": "industry", "Answer": "impulse", "Opt_1_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_2_def": "thing", "Opt_3_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection", "Opt_4_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "We did an ____ in science class to see if salt water boils more quickly than fresh water.", "Opt_1": "generation", "Opt_2": "facilities", "Opt_3": "layer", "Opt_4": "experiment", "Answer": "experiment", "Opt_1_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_2_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_3_def": "level", "Opt_4_def": "test"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "A negative ____ toward yourself as a writer can make you anxious and lead you to \"block.\"", "Opt_1": "drawback", "Opt_2": "lack", "Opt_3": "theory", "Opt_4": "attitude", "Answer": "attitude", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_2_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_3_def": "idea or hypothesis", "Opt_4_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We have never in history needed to ____ of so much waste as we do today.", "Opt_1": "prepare", "Opt_2": "dispose", "Opt_3": "advocate", "Opt_4": "announce", "Answer": "dispose", "Opt_1_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_2_def": "to get rid of", "Opt_3_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to state (often in an official way)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Previous experience in such areas, ____ microscopy, would be an advantage but is not essential.", "Opt_1": "simply", "Opt_2": "especially", "Opt_3": "hence", "Opt_4": "predominantly", "Answer": "especially", "Opt_1_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_2_def": "particularly", "Opt_3_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "An even number multiplied by an ____ number will always yield an even number.", "Opt_1": "odd", "Opt_2": "distinct", "Opt_3": "urgent", "Opt_4": "exact", "Answer": "odd", "Opt_1_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_2_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_3_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_4_def": "precise, opposite of approximate"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We are in the middle of the most serious ____ with the governments of these peoples and nations.", "Opt_1": "conflict", "Opt_2": "fault", "Opt_3": "transition", "Opt_4": "assignment", "Answer": "conflict", "Opt_1_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_2_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_3_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_4_def": "a task; the giving of a task"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You must try to achieve a ____ between work and play. At the moment it's too much play!", "Opt_1": "balance", "Opt_2": "topic", "Opt_3": "exercise", "Opt_4": "opinion", "Answer": "balance", "Opt_1_def": "equalness", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_3_def": "a piece of work, activity", "Opt_4_def": "view; what you think about someone or something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Spending months at a time in orbit, the scientists will be able to observe changes on the earth ____ them from day to day.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "beneath", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "below"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "This was a ____ attempt at addressing the issue, and not a very scholarly or intellectual attempt.", "Opt_1": "spontaneous", "Opt_2": "perpetual", "Opt_3": "key", "Opt_4": "feasible", "Answer": "spontaneous", "Opt_1_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_2_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "possible"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Government troops continued to ____ human rights. Clashes between security and rebel forces caused civilian deaths.", "Opt_1": "criticize", "Opt_2": "enter", "Opt_3": "blame", "Opt_4": "abuse", "Answer": "abuse", "Opt_1_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_3_def": "to accuse", "Opt_4_def": "to treat someone or something badly"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The Roman Jewish population did not ____ during Sixtus' reign; indeed, there was always movement of Jews in and out of the region.", "Opt_1": "offend", "Opt_2": "retreat", "Opt_3": "increase", "Opt_4": "shrink", "Answer": "shrink", "Opt_1_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_2_def": "to go back", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Burning of coal is a ____ way to obtain energy, but it creates a serious amount of pollution.", "Opt_1": "capable", "Opt_2": "intrinsic", "Opt_3": "convenient", "Opt_4": "dense", "Answer": "convenient", "Opt_1_def": "able", "Opt_2_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_3_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_4_def": "thick; full; detailed"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Scientists ____ that most children born today in First World countries will see their 75th birthday.", "Opt_1": "encounter", "Opt_2": "exaggerate", "Opt_3": "occupy", "Opt_4": "estimate", "Answer": "estimate", "Opt_1_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_2_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_3_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_4_def": "to make an intelligent guess"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Burning of coal is a convenient way to ____ energy, but it creates a serious amount of pollution.", "Opt_1": "diverge", "Opt_2": "prove", "Opt_3": "dominate", "Opt_4": "obtain", "Answer": "obtain", "Opt_1_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_2_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_3_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If you are trying to understand the instructions of a new piece of ____ like a camera, it helps to have a diagram to look at.", "Opt_1": "site", "Opt_2": "limit", "Opt_3": "equipment", "Opt_4": "diagnosis", "Answer": "equipment", "Opt_1_def": "place", "Opt_2_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_3_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)", "Opt_4_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Some people ____ the USA of starting the war in Iraq in order to gain control of its oilfields.", "Opt_1": "define", "Opt_2": "add", "Opt_3": "transfer", "Opt_4": "accuse", "Answer": "accuse", "Opt_1_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_2_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_3_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_4_def": "to blame"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "I ____ one thing I cannot do is review the film as I wished it had been made.", "Opt_1": "prosper", "Opt_2": "prepare", "Opt_3": "suppose", "Opt_4": "allocate", "Answer": "suppose", "Opt_1_def": "to do well; to become rich", "Opt_2_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_3_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_4_def": "to give to (to promise to give)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Recent government IT initiatives focus narrowly on a specific technical problem, like enabling ____ data communication or Web-based transactions.", "Opt_1": "bold", "Opt_2": "mobile", "Opt_3": "sufficient", "Opt_4": "dense", "Answer": "mobile", "Opt_1_def": "brave", "Opt_2_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_3_def": "enough", "Opt_4_def": "thick; full; detailed"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It's usually possible for teachers to ____ quite closely what grades their students are going to get in tests.", "Opt_1": "speculate", "Opt_2": "predict", "Opt_3": "sustain", "Opt_4": "devote", "Answer": "predict", "Opt_1_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_2_def": "to say what will happen in the future", "Opt_3_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_4_def": "to give (time) to"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "As a solution to this problem I ____ that all negotiation parameters be delimited at the end.", "Opt_1": "amend", "Opt_2": "forego", "Opt_3": "propose", "Opt_4": "construct", "Answer": "propose", "Opt_1_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_2_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_3_def": "to suggest", "Opt_4_def": "to make"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Should the counselor attempt to identify him and ____ him that there is a risk to his future children?", "Opt_1": "threaten", "Opt_2": "descend", "Opt_3": "inform", "Opt_4": "assimilate", "Answer": "inform", "Opt_1_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_2_def": "to go down", "Opt_3_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_4_def": "to take in"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Nowadays nobody attempts to ____ that smoking is bad for the health.", "Opt_1": "sustain", "Opt_2": "refute", "Opt_3": "terminate", "Opt_4": "correspond", "Answer": "refute", "Opt_1_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_2_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_3_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_4_def": "to be related to"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "She was in conflict with her parents at home and this was having a negative ____ on her schoolwork.", "Opt_1": "decision", "Opt_2": "institution", "Opt_3": "effect", "Opt_4": "exponent", "Answer": "effect", "Opt_1_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_2_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Due to a rapid increase in the number of students the school needs to ____ 4 new teachers.", "Opt_1": "resist", "Opt_2": "appoint", "Opt_3": "convince", "Opt_4": "preserve", "Answer": "appoint", "Opt_1_def": "to fight against", "Opt_2_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_3_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something", "Opt_4_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon."}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "My ____ impression is that this plan describes a very ambitious attempt to address an important issue in a scientifically credible manner.", "Opt_1": "overall", "Opt_2": "adequate", "Opt_3": "characteristic", "Opt_4": "economic", "Answer": "overall", "Opt_1_def": "general", "Opt_2_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_3_def": "typical", "Opt_4_def": "financial; to do with money"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Though Sima and Codreanu both attempted to prevent the murder, it ____ took place, and produced harsh consequences.", "Opt_1": "recently", "Opt_2": "nevertheless", "Opt_3": "thus", "Opt_4": "naturally", "Answer": "nevertheless", "Opt_1_def": "in the near past", "Opt_2_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_3_def": "so", "Opt_4_def": "of course, obviously"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ authority in the country is the President.", "Opt_1": "conscious", "Opt_2": "mental", "Opt_3": "ultimate", "Opt_4": "consistent", "Answer": "ultimate", "Opt_1_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_2_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_3_def": "final or most important", "Opt_4_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The greatest challenge that we face is to reduce ____ warming.", "Opt_1": "frequent", "Opt_2": "global", "Opt_3": "consistent", "Opt_4": "sufficient", "Answer": "global", "Opt_1_def": "often", "Opt_2_def": "world", "Opt_3_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_4_def": "enough"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Teachers ____ to get annoyed if students do not pay attention in class.", "Opt_1": "approve", "Opt_2": "suffer", "Opt_3": "tend", "Opt_4": "supervise", "Answer": "tend", "Opt_1_def": "to agree to", "Opt_2_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_3_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_4_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A student should declare a Literature ____ by the first semester of his or her junior year.", "Opt_1": "minor", "Opt_2": "subjective", "Opt_3": "intrinsic", "Opt_4": "bold", "Answer": "minor", "Opt_1_def": "small, not important", "Opt_2_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_3_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_4_def": "brave"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Please ____ me a seat at the back of the school bus.", "Opt_1": "devise", "Opt_2": "compel", "Opt_3": "reserve", "Opt_4": "allocate", "Answer": "reserve", "Opt_1_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_2_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_3_def": "to keep", "Opt_4_def": "to give to (to promise to give)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The data is ____ as some analysts measure this figure according to different moments of the year, geographic regions and other variables.", "Opt_1": "straightforward", "Opt_2": "ambiguous", "Opt_3": "concise", "Opt_4": "efficient", "Answer": "ambiguous", "Opt_1_def": "easy", "Opt_2_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_3_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_4_def": "working quickly and easily"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "All of his projects ____ the idea of flexibility within different, changing environments.", "Opt_1": "tolerate", "Opt_2": "develop", "Opt_3": "exclude", "Opt_4": "embody", "Answer": "embody", "Opt_1_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_2_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_3_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_4_def": "to be a good example of .."}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If men and women do ____ jobs they should earn ____ pay.", "Opt_1": "subsequent", "Opt_2": "ambiguous", "Opt_3": "equivalent", "Opt_4": "proper", "Answer": "equivalent", "Opt_1_def": "next, following", "Opt_2_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation", "Opt_3_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_4_def": "correct, appropriate"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "History is filled with examples of military leaders who have suffered at the mercy of climate conditions that they failed to ____ adequately.", "Opt_1": "dismiss", "Opt_2": "absorb", "Opt_3": "contemplate", "Opt_4": "withdraw", "Answer": "contemplate", "Opt_1_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_2_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_3_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_4_def": "to go back or take away"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Did anyone manage to ____ question 11?", "Opt_1": "deteriorate", "Opt_2": "solve", "Opt_3": "alter", "Opt_4": "contact", "Answer": "solve", "Opt_1_def": "to get worse", "Opt_2_def": "to find an answer", "Opt_3_def": "to change", "Opt_4_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The heroes of the stories in this book are people who speak only with ____ about their tragic histories.", "Opt_1": "reluctance", "Opt_2": "component", "Opt_3": "formula", "Opt_4": "skill", "Answer": "reluctance", "Opt_1_def": "unwillingness; hesitation", "Opt_2_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_3_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ between the United States and Mexico represents one of the greatest divisions of wealth on Earth.", "Opt_1": "boundary", "Opt_2": "affair", "Opt_3": "distance", "Opt_4": "shift", "Answer": "boundary", "Opt_1_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_2_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_3_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_4_def": "change"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The dentist needed to ____ my back tooth. It had become badly infected.", "Opt_1": "fund", "Opt_2": "notion", "Opt_3": "credit", "Opt_4": "extract", "Answer": "extract", "Opt_1_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_2_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_3_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_4_def": "to remove; to take out and use"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some politicians ____ that too much immigration will result in fewer jobs for the people born in the country.", "Opt_1": "intervene", "Opt_2": "fear", "Opt_3": "consent", "Opt_4": "earn", "Answer": "fear", "Opt_1_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_2_def": "to be concerned or frightened about", "Opt_3_def": "to agree", "Opt_4_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The geographer urges upon his students that they first master those principles and then ____ the subsequent problems.", "Opt_1": "replace", "Opt_2": "allege", "Opt_3": "force", "Opt_4": "consider", "Answer": "consider", "Opt_1_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_2_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_3_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_4_def": "to think"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In the Fall of 1998, there was an ____ at a vehicle manufacturing plant involving a chemical shipment that was piped into the wrong tank.", "Opt_1": "incident", "Opt_2": "account", "Opt_3": "decision", "Opt_4": "authority", "Answer": "incident", "Opt_1_def": "happening; event", "Opt_2_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_3_def": "intention to do something, choice", "Opt_4_def": "control (right to control)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "An enormous amount of research has been conducted into the ____ by which young children learn to speak.", "Opt_1": "response", "Opt_2": "defeat", "Opt_3": "mechanism", "Opt_4": "circumstances", "Answer": "mechanism", "Opt_1_def": "answer or reply; reaction", "Opt_2_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_3_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_4_def": "situation"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Some people like to get up late and go to work late. Others ____ to be at work early so they have a long evening to enjoy.", "Opt_1": "harm", "Opt_2": "discover", "Opt_3": "alter", "Opt_4": "prefer", "Answer": "prefer", "Opt_1_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_2_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_3_def": "to change", "Opt_4_def": "to like better"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "What did Louis XIV hope to accomplish in his ____ and foreign policies?", "Opt_1": "ambitious", "Opt_2": "independent", "Opt_3": "obvious", "Opt_4": "domestic", "Answer": "domestic", "Opt_1_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_2_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_3_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_4_def": "home"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This piece of work is much ____ to your last one. I'm glad to see you are getting better.", "Opt_1": "outstanding", "Opt_2": "likely", "Opt_3": "superior", "Opt_4": "convenient", "Answer": "superior", "Opt_1_def": "excellent", "Opt_2_def": "probable", "Opt_3_def": "better", "Opt_4_def": "easy, not causing problems"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This project will ____ in a major research essay of 2000 words.", "Opt_1": "depart", "Opt_2": "collapse", "Opt_3": "culminate", "Opt_4": "transform", "Answer": "culminate", "Opt_1_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_2_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail", "Opt_3_def": "to end", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often completely)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Please ____ yourselves in groups of 3 or 4, and then do the problem in the middle of the table.", "Opt_1": "reveal", "Opt_2": "provide", "Opt_3": "arrange", "Opt_4": "manage", "Answer": "arrange", "Opt_1_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_2_def": "to give", "Opt_3_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_4_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is ____ impossible to get into university unless you have done well in school.", "Opt_1": "generally", "Opt_2": "barely", "Opt_3": "furthermore", "Opt_4": "hence", "Answer": "generally", "Opt_1_def": "usually", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_3_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_4_def": "so, therefore"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Your first piece of writing was very good, but the ____ ones have been of much lower quality.", "Opt_1": "sufficient", "Opt_2": "homogeneous", "Opt_3": "subsequent", "Opt_4": "stable", "Answer": "subsequent", "Opt_1_def": "enough", "Opt_2_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_3_def": "next, following", "Opt_4_def": "not changing; not easy to change"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If you can ____ your intelligence with hard work, you have a good chance of success.", "Opt_1": "overcome", "Opt_2": "combine", "Opt_3": "denote", "Opt_4": "correlate", "Answer": "combine", "Opt_1_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_2_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_4_def": "to have a close connection"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Many economists ____ the rise in prices with the government's decision to tax imports.", "Opt_1": "protest", "Opt_2": "introduce", "Opt_3": "associate", "Opt_4": "accelerate", "Answer": "associate", "Opt_1_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_2_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_3_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_4_def": "to get or make faster"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Under the new programme, employees will continue to ____ the same amount of paid time off as they did in the old programme.", "Opt_1": "associate", "Opt_2": "devise", "Opt_3": "accumulate", "Opt_4": "found", "Answer": "accumulate", "Opt_1_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_2_def": "to create or think up", "Opt_3_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_4_def": "to begin (often an organization)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The Internet is an ____ useful tool to look for housing, shops, restaurants, etc.", "Opt_1": "simultaneously", "Opt_2": "thus", "Opt_3": "extremely", "Opt_4": "eventually", "Answer": "extremely", "Opt_1_def": "at the same time", "Opt_2_def": "so", "Opt_3_def": "very", "Opt_4_def": "in the end"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If she told you she gave you her work, you can ____ her. She is very honest and reliable.", "Opt_1": "trust", "Opt_2": "exploit", "Opt_3": "contact", "Opt_4": "engage", "Answer": "trust", "Opt_1_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_2_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_3_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_4_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Many parents ____ their children to the bedroom when they behave badly.", "Opt_1": "confine", "Opt_2": "condemn", "Opt_3": "conserve", "Opt_4": "master", "Answer": "confine", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_4_def": "to (gain) control"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "If you are caught drinking and driving, this results in an ____ driving ban of at least 3 months.", "Opt_1": "automatic", "Opt_2": "comprehensive", "Opt_3": "moderate", "Opt_4": "deficient", "Answer": "automatic", "Opt_1_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_2_def": "full, complete", "Opt_3_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_4_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Many German companies have decided to ____ their factories to parts of the world where workers are cheaper.", "Opt_1": "incorporate", "Opt_2": "withdraw", "Opt_3": "transfer", "Opt_4": "derive", "Answer": "transfer", "Opt_1_def": "to include", "Opt_2_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_3_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_4_def": "to come from or get from"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "I ____ the linguists, for not insisting that anyone who claims to be an educated person needs elementary competence in describing and analyzing the sound, form and meaning of human language.", "Opt_1": "assure", "Opt_2": "blame", "Opt_3": "diverge", "Opt_4": "expand", "Answer": "blame", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_2_def": "to accuse", "Opt_3_def": "to move apart; to be different from", "Opt_4_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ of your writing is not at all clear to me.", "Opt_1": "structure", "Opt_2": "institution", "Opt_3": "resident", "Opt_4": "domain", "Answer": "structure", "Opt_1_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_2_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_3_def": "a person who lives in a place", "Opt_4_def": "area (of interest)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Whereas the origin of galactic magnetic fields has long posed a challenge for astrophysicists to explain, they ____ feel that they can say where they were not formed.", "Opt_1": "extremely", "Opt_2": "nevertheless", "Opt_3": "therefore", "Opt_4": "fairly", "Answer": "nevertheless", "Opt_1_def": "very", "Opt_2_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_3_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_4_def": "quite, somewhat"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The global trade agreements have failed to include meaningful, enforceable ____ or environmental standards.", "Opt_1": "concept", "Opt_2": "delay", "Opt_3": "labour", "Opt_4": "instance", "Answer": "labour", "Opt_1_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_2_def": "lateness", "Opt_3_def": "work", "Opt_4_def": "example"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It would not be ____ to deviate from our planned course of action.", "Opt_1": "consistent", "Opt_2": "superficial", "Opt_3": "adequate", "Opt_4": "wise", "Answer": "wise", "Opt_1_def": "regular or predictable; remaining the same", "Opt_2_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_3_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_4_def": "intelligent; sensible"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "If he is correct this would certainly be an ____ solution to an ancient problem.", "Opt_1": "elementary", "Opt_2": "uniform", "Opt_3": "complex", "Opt_4": "compatible", "Answer": "elementary", "Opt_1_def": "easy", "Opt_2_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_3_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_4_def": "able to work with someone or something else"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "After Iraq some people feel strongly that the USA should never again ____ in the affairs of other countries.", "Opt_1": "exchange", "Opt_2": "consent", "Opt_3": "intervene", "Opt_4": "owe", "Answer": "intervene", "Opt_1_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_2_def": "to agree", "Opt_3_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_4_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "With her ____ it is not surprising that she has had problems in her new school.", "Opt_1": "background", "Opt_2": "boundary", "Opt_3": "habit", "Opt_4": "purpose", "Answer": "background", "Opt_1_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_2_def": "limit, extent", "Opt_3_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_4_def": "reason, goal"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "For some observers, globalization is a terrible ____ and for others a wonderful world of possibilities and innovation.", "Opt_1": "disaster", "Opt_2": "profession", "Opt_3": "deal", "Opt_4": "deed", "Answer": "disaster", "Opt_1_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_2_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_3_def": "agreement", "Opt_4_def": "an action"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "And, further, he didn't ____ a lecture from one whose own morality has been deficient.", "Opt_1": "appreciate", "Opt_2": "hesitate", "Opt_3": "oppose", "Opt_4": "suspect", "Answer": "appreciate", "Opt_1_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_2_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_4_def": "to believe"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government is certain to ____ opposition to its proposal.", "Opt_1": "fail", "Opt_2": "encounter", "Opt_3": "dominate", "Opt_4": "correlate", "Answer": "encounter", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly", "Opt_2_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_3_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_4_def": "to have a close connection"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There is a ____ possibility that she will lose her job unless she becomes more reliable.", "Opt_1": "distinct", "Opt_2": "fortunate", "Opt_3": "wise", "Opt_4": "positive", "Answer": "distinct", "Opt_1_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_2_def": "lucky", "Opt_3_def": "intelligent; sensible", "Opt_4_def": "good; optimistic"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It only drew more attention to the 13-year-old Robertson panel report and the CIA's ____ in the investigation of UFOs.", "Opt_1": "technique", "Opt_2": "formula", "Opt_3": "role", "Opt_4": "proportion", "Answer": "role", "Opt_1_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "job or function", "Opt_4_def": "amount; number; percentage"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There is very little difference in the quality of learning received by ____ education students and regular students, according to a study.", "Opt_1": "precaution", "Opt_2": "distance", "Opt_3": "doubt", "Opt_4": "opportunity", "Answer": "distance", "Opt_1_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_2_def": "how far it is from one place to another", "Opt_3_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_4_def": "chance"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "There is not an ____ supply of oil and natural gas.", "Opt_1": "essential", "Opt_2": "fundamental", "Opt_3": "bold", "Opt_4": "infinite", "Answer": "infinite", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "brave", "Opt_4_def": "without an end"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Students are able to use basic communication and mathematics skills for purposes and situations they will ____ throughout their lives.", "Opt_1": "discern", "Opt_2": "reflect", "Opt_3": "illuminate", "Opt_4": "encounter", "Answer": "encounter", "Opt_1_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_2_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_3_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_4_def": "to meet or experience"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If you are interested in checking out any of the books in the ____ case, please inquire at Circulation.", "Opt_1": "obligation", "Opt_2": "formula", "Opt_3": "scheme", "Opt_4": "display", "Answer": "display", "Opt_1_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_2_def": "a method of doing something", "Opt_3_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_4_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There was not a big difference in the negative description of Saddam Hussein among the three newspapers, and these descriptions did not ____ much space.", "Opt_1": "precede", "Opt_2": "prevent", "Opt_3": "define", "Opt_4": "occupy", "Answer": "occupy", "Opt_1_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_3_def": "to state what something is or means", "Opt_4_def": "to up space or time"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "As a solution to this problem I ____ that all negotiation parameters be delimited at the end.", "Opt_1": "presume", "Opt_2": "achieve", "Opt_3": "propose", "Opt_4": "dispose", "Answer": "propose", "Opt_1_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_2_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_3_def": "to suggest", "Opt_4_def": "to get rid of"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The elders in the village are fighting to ____ their people's traditions, but the younger ones want to join the modern world of computers and mobile phones.", "Opt_1": "store", "Opt_2": "correlate", "Opt_3": "retain", "Opt_4": "expose", "Answer": "retain", "Opt_1_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_2_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_3_def": "to keep", "Opt_4_def": "to uncover, reveal"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "His current measurement results are not precise enough to identify exactly the ____ that the ball is sitting in.", "Opt_1": "role", "Opt_2": "pressure", "Opt_3": "minimum", "Opt_4": "surface", "Answer": "minimum", "Opt_1_def": "job or function", "Opt_2_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_3_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_4_def": "the outside layer of an object"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You are ____ of much better grades if you make more effort.", "Opt_1": "diverse", "Opt_2": "capable", "Opt_3": "typical", "Opt_4": "competent", "Answer": "capable", "Opt_1_def": "many and different", "Opt_2_def": "able", "Opt_3_def": "usual", "Opt_4_def": "good at something (often a job)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There is no trace of an ____ idea in this essay.", "Opt_1": "identical", "Opt_2": "original", "Opt_3": "inherent", "Opt_4": "probable", "Answer": "original", "Opt_1_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_2_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_3_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of", "Opt_4_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers."}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The best footballers can ____ many thousands of pounds every day.", "Opt_1": "prevent", "Opt_2": "earn", "Opt_3": "measure", "Opt_4": "deprive", "Answer": "earn", "Opt_1_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_2_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_3_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_4_def": "to take away (the opportunity)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Revenue from ____ tax is expected to be lower this year than in previous years.", "Opt_1": "income", "Opt_2": "minimum", "Opt_3": "concept", "Opt_4": "circumstances", "Answer": "income", "Opt_1_def": "money earned", "Opt_2_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_3_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_4_def": "situation"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government should spend money in its ____ country, but it chooses to fight wars in other countries instead.", "Opt_1": "dismiss", "Opt_2": "circulate", "Opt_3": "interfere", "Opt_4": "own", "Answer": "own", "Opt_1_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_2_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_3_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_4_def": "to have or possess"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "He has a heavy accent but this does not ____ with understanding what he means.", "Opt_1": "interfere", "Opt_2": "interact", "Opt_3": "manipulate", "Opt_4": "justify", "Answer": "interfere", "Opt_1_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_2_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_3_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_4_def": "to give a reason for doing something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Visit our Student Support page to see how you can set up a fund to give someone the opportunity to ____ higher education at Michigan Tech.", "Opt_1": "discuss", "Opt_2": "create", "Opt_3": "exchange", "Opt_4": "pursue", "Answer": "pursue", "Opt_1_def": "to talk about", "Opt_2_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_3_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_4_def": "to follow (or do)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The business manager could not ____ the anomaly in the company's finances, and was asked to resign.", "Opt_1": "explain", "Opt_2": "refer", "Opt_3": "evolve", "Opt_4": "abuse", "Answer": "explain", "Opt_1_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_3_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_4_def": "to treat someone or something badly"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If you want to ____ the chess club, please sign your name on the list below.", "Opt_1": "join", "Opt_2": "impose", "Opt_3": "maintain", "Opt_4": "exclude", "Answer": "join", "Opt_1_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_2_def": "to force; to require to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_4_def": "to leave out; opposite of include"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The Tower of Hanoi is an ancient puzzle involving three pegs, and an ____ number of circular discs, each of a different size, and with holes in their centers.", "Opt_1": "verbal", "Opt_2": "numerous", "Opt_3": "crucial", "Opt_4": "arbitrary", "Answer": "arbitrary", "Opt_1_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_2_def": "very many", "Opt_3_def": "extremely important", "Opt_4_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "European countries have decided to collaborate in an ____ to reduce illegal immigration.", "Opt_1": "credit", "Opt_2": "shift", "Opt_3": "effect", "Opt_4": "exhibit", "Answer": "effect", "Opt_1_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_2_def": "change", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "to show"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If a child consistently begs to stay home from school, has extreme fear of being away from a parent etc., there may be a cause for ____ about the child.", "Opt_1": "apparatus", "Opt_2": "region", "Opt_3": "doubt", "Opt_4": "concern", "Answer": "concern", "Opt_1_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "part of a place", "Opt_3_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_4_def": "worry, fear"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Turning in work completed by other students will only ____ you when it comes to the exams.", "Opt_1": "discuss", "Opt_2": "harm", "Opt_3": "implement", "Opt_4": "inquire", "Answer": "harm", "Opt_1_def": "to talk about", "Opt_2_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_3_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_4_def": "to ask"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ of this tutorial is to give you an idea of the sequence of events leading up to graduation.", "Opt_1": "fund", "Opt_2": "pattern", "Opt_3": "purpose", "Opt_4": "outline", "Answer": "purpose", "Opt_1_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_2_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_4_def": "plan or summary"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "That's the third time she's been late in the last week. I think I need to ____ the matter with her parents.", "Opt_1": "explore", "Opt_2": "pursue", "Opt_3": "replace", "Opt_4": "perceive", "Answer": "pursue", "Opt_1_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_2_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_3_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_4_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It was not a ____ of which he was particularly proud.", "Opt_1": "credit", "Opt_2": "delay", "Opt_3": "deed", "Opt_4": "task", "Answer": "deed", "Opt_1_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_2_def": "lateness", "Opt_3_def": "an action", "Opt_4_def": "job"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Participants will gain in-depth exposure to each ____ through classroom assignments and structured exercises within team environments.", "Opt_1": "comment", "Opt_2": "majority", "Opt_3": "topic", "Opt_4": "aspect", "Answer": "topic", "Opt_1_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_2_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_4_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain."}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The teacher had to ____ the boy from the rest of the class. His bad behaviour was disrupting their learning.", "Opt_1": "store", "Opt_2": "isolate", "Opt_3": "offend", "Opt_4": "focus", "Answer": "isolate", "Opt_1_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_2_def": "to separate something or someone from others", "Opt_3_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_4_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There will be no ____ or written personal attacks on any individual or group of individuals based on age, ancestry, color, disability or handicap.", "Opt_1": "faint", "Opt_2": "legal", "Opt_3": "verbal", "Opt_4": "pure", "Answer": "verbal", "Opt_1_def": "not strong", "Opt_2_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_3_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_4_def": "complete, 100%"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The siting and ____ are a typical characteristic of ancient buildings that belong to a self-enclosed precinct.", "Opt_1": "schedule", "Opt_2": "design", "Opt_3": "skill", "Opt_4": "substitute", "Answer": "design", "Opt_1_def": "timetable", "Opt_2_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_3_def": "ability (e.g. in sport or music)", "Opt_4_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Army leadership must ____ the importance of reducing energy demand to decrease costs.", "Opt_1": "approach", "Opt_2": "emphasize", "Opt_3": "encourage", "Opt_4": "verify", "Answer": "emphasize", "Opt_1_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_2_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_3_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_4_def": "to prove or claim the truth"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "We can conclude that China is unlikely to put significant ____ on Sudan, and that Sudan could and would easily resist such ____.", "Opt_1": "habit", "Opt_2": "bond", "Opt_3": "pressure", "Opt_4": "dispute", "Answer": "pressure", "Opt_1_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_2_def": "link; tie", "Opt_3_def": "force; influence; stress", "Opt_4_def": "argument; conflict"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The only goal of some people is to ____ as much money as possible.", "Opt_1": "succeed", "Opt_2": "exceed", "Opt_3": "yield", "Opt_4": "accumulate", "Answer": "accumulate", "Opt_1_def": "to do well", "Opt_2_def": "to be more than or better than", "Opt_3_def": "to produce", "Opt_4_def": "to grow; to gather together"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Shonekan was unable to reverse Nigeria's ever-growing ____ problems.", "Opt_1": "steady", "Opt_2": "sound", "Opt_3": "economic", "Opt_4": "latter", "Answer": "economic", "Opt_1_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_2_def": "good; strong", "Opt_3_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_4_def": "the second of two things mentioned"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Janice Walker wanted to ____ further ways to continue this great benefit to the company's staff as well as the company's productivity.", "Opt_1": "assemble", "Opt_2": "examine", "Opt_3": "suspect", "Opt_4": "constitute", "Answer": "examine", "Opt_1_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_2_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to believe", "Opt_4_def": "to be; to make up"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The lesson plans contained an incomplete description of learners, their background and ____ knowledge.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A significant ____ indicated that they enjoyed learning the course.", "Opt_1": "majority", "Opt_2": "liberty", "Opt_3": "counsel", "Opt_4": "propensity", "Answer": "majority", "Opt_1_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_2_def": "freedom", "Opt_3_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_4_def": "tendency; desire"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The former assumes a single step - that life originated on Earth - ahead of the more ____ idea that life formed elsewhere and was subsequently transported to Earth.", "Opt_1": "economic", "Opt_2": "dense", "Opt_3": "massive", "Opt_4": "elaborate", "Answer": "elaborate", "Opt_1_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_2_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_3_def": "very large", "Opt_4_def": "detailed; complex"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The trial court noted that the newspaper articles ____ reported events and provided no editorial comment.", "Opt_1": "merely", "Opt_2": "hence", "Opt_3": "eventually", "Opt_4": "approximately", "Answer": "merely", "Opt_1_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_2_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_3_def": "in the end", "Opt_4_def": "about; not exactly"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is ____ impossible to get into university unless you have done well in school.", "Opt_1": "nevertheless", "Opt_2": "furthermore", "Opt_3": "predominantly", "Opt_4": "generally", "Answer": "generally", "Opt_1_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_2_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_3_def": "mostly", "Opt_4_def": "usually"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If you ____ someone who is not qualified for the job, you cannot be surprised if they have problems.", "Opt_1": "focus", "Opt_2": "appoint", "Opt_3": "associate", "Opt_4": "confirm", "Answer": "appoint", "Opt_1_def": "to direct attention (on an issue)", "Opt_2_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_3_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_4_def": "to agree that something is correct"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The construction of the Interstate Highway System ran into serious financial problems because Congress did not ____ the cost of inflation.", "Opt_1": "anticipate", "Opt_2": "suggest", "Opt_3": "convey", "Opt_4": "invent", "Answer": "anticipate", "Opt_1_def": "to expect", "Opt_2_def": "to say an idea; to recommend", "Opt_3_def": "to pass on to another person (often by speaking)", "Opt_4_def": "to create (often a new object)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Most western countries want to ____ with China. It's the largest market in the world and its developing fast.", "Opt_1": "receive", "Opt_2": "regret", "Opt_3": "trade", "Opt_4": "provide", "Answer": "trade", "Opt_1_def": "to get", "Opt_2_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_3_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_4_def": "to give"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In addition to paying for the required tuition and fees, you will need to procure a variety of materials to ____ this class.", "Opt_1": "several", "Opt_2": "formal", "Opt_3": "harsh", "Opt_4": "complete", "Answer": "complete", "Opt_1_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_2_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_3_def": "hard, unfair", "Opt_4_def": "full or finished"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A ____ example of ambiguity is the sentence: \"I do not like visiting aunts.\"", "Opt_1": "verbal", "Opt_2": "constant", "Opt_3": "intrinsic", "Opt_4": "classic", "Answer": "classic", "Opt_1_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)", "Opt_2_def": "not changing; long-lasting", "Opt_3_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_4_def": "very good, the best or most used"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ information provides details on the spiking neuron model used in this work.", "Opt_1": "entire", "Opt_2": "slight", "Opt_3": "supplementary", "Opt_4": "key", "Answer": "supplementary", "Opt_1_def": "whole, all", "Opt_2_def": "small", "Opt_3_def": "extra; additional", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The Court determined, however, that evidence concerning Ms. Lewinsky was not ____ to the core issues in this case.", "Opt_1": "essential", "Opt_2": "medium", "Opt_3": "basic", "Opt_4": "ideal", "Answer": "essential", "Opt_1_def": "very important", "Opt_2_def": "in the middle", "Opt_3_def": "first or easy", "Opt_4_def": "best, optimal"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is too early to ____ whether the government's plan to reduce child poverty have been successful or not.", "Opt_1": "formulate", "Opt_2": "judge", "Opt_3": "entitle", "Opt_4": "implement", "Answer": "judge", "Opt_1_def": "to express", "Opt_2_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In an effective group, each person can ____ sufficient influence on the decisions of the group to prevent the group from setting unattainable goals.", "Opt_1": "present", "Opt_2": "mention", "Opt_3": "exert", "Opt_4": "deviate", "Answer": "exert", "Opt_1_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_2_def": "to say; state", "Opt_3_def": "to use", "Opt_4_def": "to be different"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "When the Powhatans did not want to trade with the settlers, Smith used force to ____ food.", "Opt_1": "depend", "Opt_2": "justify", "Opt_3": "acquire", "Opt_4": "decline", "Answer": "acquire", "Opt_1_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_2_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_4_def": "to go down or get worse"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ of the study is to examine the hypothesis that urban life is more stressful than rural life.", "Opt_1": "object", "Opt_2": "purpose", "Opt_3": "institution", "Opt_4": "section", "Answer": "purpose", "Opt_1_def": "thing", "Opt_2_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_3_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_4_def": "part"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "I assume his strange behaviour recently is the ____ of his parents' divorce.", "Opt_1": "state", "Opt_2": "summary", "Opt_3": "result", "Opt_4": "profit", "Answer": "result", "Opt_1_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_2_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_3_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_4_def": "money gained"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is surprising what you can ____ if you make an effort.", "Opt_1": "attend", "Opt_2": "blame", "Opt_3": "include", "Opt_4": "accomplish", "Answer": "accomplish", "Opt_1_def": "to go to, to be present at", "Opt_2_def": "to accuse", "Opt_3_def": "to put in; to have in", "Opt_4_def": "to do or achieve"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Could you please ____ the homework for me? I'm not sure I understand.", "Opt_1": "inspect", "Opt_2": "base", "Opt_3": "undergo", "Opt_4": "clarify", "Answer": "clarify", "Opt_1_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_3_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_4_def": "to make something clear, explain"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "They simply decided for various reasons that his age was not a drawback, that ____ (at that time and for that position) it was an advantage.", "Opt_1": "especially", "Opt_2": "perhaps", "Opt_3": "accordingly", "Opt_4": "gradually", "Answer": "perhaps", "Opt_1_def": "particularly", "Opt_2_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_3_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with", "Opt_4_def": "slowly; steadily"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "After these two periods of ____ work time that did not involve any teacher instruction, the students presented their work to the class.", "Opt_1": "individual", "Opt_2": "command", "Opt_3": "criterion", "Opt_4": "effort", "Answer": "individual", "Opt_1_def": "one person", "Opt_2_def": "control", "Opt_3_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_4_def": "hard work; attempt"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This is a very ____ example for demonstration purposes. However, the effect is similar for more complex cases.", "Opt_1": "characteristic", "Opt_2": "trivial", "Opt_3": "physical", "Opt_4": "ambiguous", "Answer": "trivial", "Opt_1_def": "typical", "Opt_2_def": "not important", "Opt_3_def": "of the body", "Opt_4_def": "not clear; open to more than one interpretation"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Please ____ Einstein to your list of famous scientists.", "Opt_1": "exclude", "Opt_2": "add", "Opt_3": "confront", "Opt_4": "manipulate", "Answer": "add", "Opt_1_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_2_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_3_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_4_def": "to (use and) change"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government's new proposals are too vague. They need to be ____ about what they expect people to do.", "Opt_1": "precise", "Opt_2": "instant", "Opt_3": "principal", "Opt_4": "formal", "Answer": "precise", "Opt_1_def": "exact", "Opt_2_def": "immediate", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "What steps do I take to draw a random ____ of a target audience in my county to do a needs assessment or gather baseline data?", "Opt_1": "apparatus", "Opt_2": "tradition", "Opt_3": "manner", "Opt_4": "sample", "Answer": "sample", "Opt_1_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_3_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "example; a smaller number of a larger collection"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Another well-known ____ of marijuana is its ability to increase appetite.", "Opt_1": "effect", "Opt_2": "evidence", "Opt_3": "doubt", "Opt_4": "site", "Answer": "effect", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_3_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_4_def": "place"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Be certain to answer the question in its entirety. Be certain to ____ how and why you came to a particular conclusion.", "Opt_1": "blame", "Opt_2": "manage", "Opt_3": "denote", "Opt_4": "explain", "Answer": "explain", "Opt_1_def": "to accuse", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to mean; to be a sign of", "Opt_4_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Starting during the 18th century, attempts have been made to classify the world's languages into one ____ genetic system of families.", "Opt_1": "obvious", "Opt_2": "smooth", "Opt_3": "particular", "Opt_4": "comprehensive", "Answer": "comprehensive", "Opt_1_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_2_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_3_def": "specific", "Opt_4_def": "full, complete"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Please ____ your disk, shut the disk drive and then click on 'Save'.", "Opt_1": "measure", "Opt_2": "owe", "Opt_3": "discuss", "Opt_4": "insert", "Answer": "insert", "Opt_1_def": "to find out how much there is of something", "Opt_2_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_3_def": "to talk about", "Opt_4_def": "to put in"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The school is planning to bring in an external tax expert to ____ its finance methods.", "Opt_1": "induce", "Opt_2": "halt", "Opt_3": "analyze", "Opt_4": "construct", "Answer": "analyze", "Opt_1_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_4_def": "to make"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Various approaches to environmental justice are discussed, along with steps in the planning process when ____ involvement is particularly effective.", "Opt_1": "procedure", "Opt_2": "authority", "Opt_3": "section", "Opt_4": "citizen", "Answer": "citizen", "Opt_1_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_2_def": "control (right to control)", "Opt_3_def": "part", "Opt_4_def": "person (member of a country)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Sports events such as the World Cup or the Olympic Games often ____ in an enormous firework display.", "Opt_1": "assess", "Opt_2": "culminate", "Opt_3": "illustrate", "Opt_4": "adapt", "Answer": "culminate", "Opt_1_def": "to judge or test", "Opt_2_def": "to end", "Opt_3_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There will be no verbal or written personal attacks on any ____ or group of ____s based on age, ancestry, color, disability or handicap.", "Opt_1": "rank", "Opt_2": "portion", "Opt_3": "individual", "Opt_4": "fund", "Answer": "individual", "Opt_1_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_2_def": "part, amount", "Opt_3_def": "one person", "Opt_4_def": "money collected for a particular purpose"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Kaiya reminds him that they have never been apart before, and it is ____ that Willow is experiencing feelings of guilt.", "Opt_1": "apparent", "Opt_2": "final", "Opt_3": "urgent", "Opt_4": "bold", "Answer": "apparent", "Opt_1_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_2_def": "last", "Opt_3_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_4_def": "brave"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "She said sorry to the teacher and ____ avoided a detention.", "Opt_1": "thereby", "Opt_2": "universally", "Opt_3": "furthermore", "Opt_4": "accordingly", "Answer": "thereby", "Opt_1_def": "by doing this", "Opt_2_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_3_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_4_def": "appropriate to; in compliance with"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is difficult for the government to ____ money fairly to all the organizations that need financial help.", "Opt_1": "address", "Opt_2": "participate", "Opt_3": "oppose", "Opt_4": "allocate", "Answer": "allocate", "Opt_1_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_2_def": "to take part", "Opt_3_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_4_def": "to give to (to promise to give)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The pharmacy does not have access to your medical record, ____ is unable to obtain insurance information from the health forms.", "Opt_1": "conversely", "Opt_2": "thus", "Opt_3": "somewhat", "Opt_4": "hence", "Answer": "thus", "Opt_1_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_2_def": "so", "Opt_3_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_4_def": "so, therefore"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "As migration is a spatial ____ process, it is important to comprehend how migrants perceive space and choose a destination in the space.", "Opt_1": "command", "Opt_2": "choice", "Opt_3": "programme", "Opt_4": "duration", "Answer": "choice", "Opt_1_def": "control", "Opt_2_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_3_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_4_def": "period of time"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The teaching profession is usually not attractive to those who are still pupils themselves. This ____ of career is normally made much later.", "Opt_1": "administration", "Opt_2": "choice", "Opt_3": "dispute", "Opt_4": "doubt", "Answer": "choice", "Opt_1_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school", "Opt_2_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_3_def": "argument; conflict", "Opt_4_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In the long run, democratic market capitalism has proved ____ to deterministic, command socialism.", "Opt_1": "superior", "Opt_2": "independent", "Opt_3": "anonymous", "Opt_4": "key", "Answer": "superior", "Opt_1_def": "better", "Opt_2_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_3_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It would not be wise to ____ from our planned course of action.", "Opt_1": "rotate", "Opt_2": "deviate", "Opt_3": "explain", "Opt_4": "intervene", "Answer": "deviate", "Opt_1_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_2_def": "to be different", "Opt_3_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The teachers ____ that the school administration is secretly planning to increase working hours.", "Opt_1": "submit", "Opt_2": "forego", "Opt_3": "allege", "Opt_4": "donate", "Answer": "allege", "Opt_1_def": "to give; to send", "Opt_2_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_3_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_4_def": "to give (usually money)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The court concluded that the order did not ____ from the essential requirements of law.", "Opt_1": "ruin", "Opt_2": "amend", "Opt_3": "confirm", "Opt_4": "depart", "Answer": "depart", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_2_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_3_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_4_def": "to leave; to be different from"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government claims that it invaded Iraq to bring democracy to that country. Many people, however, claim that this is not a ____ reason to go to war.", "Opt_1": "accurate", "Opt_2": "external", "Opt_3": "valid", "Opt_4": "anonymous", "Answer": "valid", "Opt_1_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_2_def": "outside", "Opt_3_def": "correct", "Opt_4_def": "having no name or known author"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Not everyone is fortunate enough to have internet ____ at home.", "Opt_1": "access", "Opt_2": "operation", "Opt_3": "shortage", "Opt_4": "forecast", "Answer": "access", "Opt_1_def": "the right to enter or use", "Opt_2_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_3_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_4_def": "prediction"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Furthermore, the text of the paragraph should ____ to the topic sentence.", "Opt_1": "correspond", "Opt_2": "observe", "Opt_3": "harm", "Opt_4": "enforce", "Answer": "correspond", "Opt_1_def": "to be related to", "Opt_2_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_4_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There have been several reviews done regarding the comparison of online ____ delivery tools that are on the market today.", "Opt_1": "concept", "Opt_2": "choice", "Opt_3": "course", "Opt_4": "notion", "Answer": "course", "Opt_1_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_2_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_3_def": "a subject or period of study", "Opt_4_def": "idea; concept"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Hopes continue to ____ that a peace treaty can be negotiated.", "Opt_1": "accompany", "Opt_2": "purchase", "Opt_3": "fade", "Opt_4": "join", "Answer": "fade", "Opt_1_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_2_def": "to buy", "Opt_3_def": "to disappear slowly", "Opt_4_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Could you use informal writing tasks to ____ thinking and learning?", "Opt_1": "precede", "Opt_2": "promote", "Opt_3": "displace", "Opt_4": "stipulate", "Answer": "promote", "Opt_1_def": "to go or be before someone or something", "Opt_2_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_3_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to require"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In my opinion the government's ____ for banning smoking is very weak. Surely they don't expect people to agree!", "Opt_1": "extent", "Opt_2": "revolution", "Opt_3": "command", "Opt_4": "argument", "Answer": "argument", "Opt_1_def": "size, amount", "Opt_2_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_3_def": "control", "Opt_4_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If men and women do ____ jobs they should earn ____ pay.", "Opt_1": "physical", "Opt_2": "accurate", "Opt_3": "equivalent", "Opt_4": "overall", "Answer": "equivalent", "Opt_1_def": "of the body", "Opt_2_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_3_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_4_def": "general"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The Supreme Court held that the free exercise of religion did not ____ an Orthodox Jew to wear a yarmulke when he was on duty as an officer of law.", "Opt_1": "entitle", "Opt_2": "suffer", "Opt_3": "stress", "Opt_4": "assess", "Answer": "entitle", "Opt_1_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_3_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_4_def": "to judge or test"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The recent conference about green energy failed to ____ the interest of the British public.", "Opt_1": "criticize", "Opt_2": "assure", "Opt_3": "praise", "Opt_4": "engage", "Answer": "engage", "Opt_1_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to make sure; to say that something will certainly happen", "Opt_3_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_4_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If you don't receive search results within that time frame or if this an ____ request, please contact the reference desk.", "Opt_1": "urgent", "Opt_2": "essential", "Opt_3": "original", "Opt_4": "explicit", "Answer": "urgent", "Opt_1_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_4_def": "clearly and openly expressed"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The last victim of the explosion is not expected to ____ his major injuries.", "Opt_1": "survive", "Opt_2": "examine", "Opt_3": "embody", "Opt_4": "elect", "Answer": "survive", "Opt_1_def": "to not die", "Opt_2_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_4_def": "to choose by voting"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Job applicants often find that their personal attributes match what a company values; when this occurs, you should ____ these attributes in your CV.", "Opt_1": "adopt", "Opt_2": "estimate", "Opt_3": "highlight", "Opt_4": "avoid", "Answer": "highlight", "Opt_1_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_2_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_3_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something or go somewhere"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Teachers must ____ students and supervise activities in the computer room.", "Opt_1": "accompany", "Opt_2": "explore", "Opt_3": "expand", "Opt_4": "disperse", "Answer": "accompany", "Opt_1_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_2_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_4_def": "to spread out; to move apart"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I ____ the idea of having a school uniform. I think it would cause a lot of unnecessary problems.", "Opt_1": "depend", "Opt_2": "increase", "Opt_3": "oppose", "Opt_4": "protect", "Answer": "oppose", "Opt_1_def": "be influenced (by)", "Opt_2_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_3_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_4_def": "to keep something out of danger"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The business manager could not explain the ____ in the company's finances, and was asked to resign.", "Opt_1": "doubt", "Opt_2": "profit", "Opt_3": "source", "Opt_4": "anomaly", "Answer": "anomaly", "Opt_1_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_2_def": "money gained", "Opt_3_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_4_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government plans to ____ farmers who grow crops that can be used to run cars.", "Opt_1": "subsidize", "Opt_2": "commit", "Opt_3": "assist", "Opt_4": "extend", "Answer": "subsidize", "Opt_1_def": "to support financially", "Opt_2_def": "to do (often an offense)", "Opt_3_def": "to help", "Opt_4_def": "to make longer in time or space"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The most ____ advice that you can give your children is: Be yourself.", "Opt_1": "equivalent", "Opt_2": "valuable", "Opt_3": "complete", "Opt_4": "loose", "Answer": "valuable", "Opt_1_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_2_def": "worth a lot of money; important", "Opt_3_def": "full or finished", "Opt_4_def": "not firm or finished"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The German government should have realized that it would ____ matters by allowing the different German states to have their own regulations about smoking in public buildings.", "Opt_1": "expel", "Opt_2": "unite", "Opt_3": "complicate", "Opt_4": "distort", "Answer": "complicate", "Opt_1_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_3_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_4_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Summarizing or paraphrasing is expressing the ____ idea or information in your own words.", "Opt_1": "original", "Opt_2": "spare", "Opt_3": "stable", "Opt_4": "intense", "Answer": "original", "Opt_1_def": "the first of its kind", "Opt_2_def": "not needed", "Opt_3_def": "not changing; not easy to change", "Opt_4_def": "strong, extreme"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If we learn to communicate effectively with others and are ____ to risk sharing our own feelings and respect other's feelings, many rewards will await us.", "Opt_1": "discrete", "Opt_2": "explicit", "Opt_3": "former", "Opt_4": "willing", "Answer": "willing", "Opt_1_def": "separate", "Opt_2_def": "clearly and openly expressed", "Opt_3_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_4_def": "happy or prepared to do something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The Health Minister has made the ____ request that parents make sure their children eat enough fruit and vegetables.", "Opt_1": "global", "Opt_2": "latter", "Opt_3": "various", "Opt_4": "reasonable", "Answer": "reasonable", "Opt_1_def": "world", "Opt_2_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_3_def": "several, of different kinds", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable, quite good"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You need to ____ your instinct as to whether he is the right man to marry.", "Opt_1": "encounter", "Opt_2": "trust", "Opt_3": "appoint", "Opt_4": "connect", "Answer": "trust", "Opt_1_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_2_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_3_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or put together"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Students are encouraged to discuss topics early on with the instructor, ____ in the case of an independent investigation.", "Opt_1": "naturally", "Opt_2": "especially", "Opt_3": "conversely", "Opt_4": "generally", "Answer": "especially", "Opt_1_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_2_def": "particularly", "Opt_3_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_4_def": "usually"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The army sent 2,000 of its soldiers to ____ clothing to the refugees driven out of their homes by fighting.", "Opt_1": "distribute", "Opt_2": "settle", "Opt_3": "encourage", "Opt_4": "regret", "Answer": "distribute", "Opt_1_def": "to give out", "Opt_2_def": "to solve a problem or dispute", "Opt_3_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_4_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "In response to these events, this study was initiated to define and investigate the ____ of the problem.", "Opt_1": "target", "Opt_2": "instruction", "Opt_3": "stage", "Opt_4": "extent", "Answer": "extent", "Opt_1_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_2_def": "advice or teaching how to do something; an order to do something", "Opt_3_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_4_def": "size, amount"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "His lungs were filled in an ____ with a great volume of driven air which he could not expel.", "Opt_1": "military", "Opt_2": "legal", "Opt_3": "considerable", "Opt_4": "instant", "Answer": "instant", "Opt_1_def": "to do with army", "Opt_2_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_3_def": "very big; very much", "Opt_4_def": "immediate"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I believe that people often ____ the hardships the parents experience if their child has a learning disability.", "Opt_1": "complicate", "Opt_2": "compile", "Opt_3": "neglect", "Opt_4": "require", "Answer": "neglect", "Opt_1_def": "to make things more complex or difficult", "Opt_2_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_3_def": "to not think about or care for", "Opt_4_def": "to need"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The proponents of disability rights and design professionals have come to realize that the ____ of accessible design has to be rethought.", "Opt_1": "intention", "Opt_2": "concept", "Opt_3": "lecture", "Opt_4": "limit", "Answer": "concept", "Opt_1_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_2_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_3_def": "a talk on a particular subject; talk criticizing unacceptable behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "extent, boundary"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The computer is an excellent ____ for language learning.", "Opt_1": "tool", "Opt_2": "obligation", "Opt_3": "figure", "Opt_4": "support", "Answer": "tool", "Opt_1_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_3_def": "number", "Opt_4_def": "help"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It explores the lives of a group of adolescent boys in the ____ between the departure of the Nazis and the arrival of the Communists.", "Opt_1": "interval", "Opt_2": "battle", "Opt_3": "forecast", "Opt_4": "outline", "Answer": "interval", "Opt_1_def": "a period of time", "Opt_2_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_3_def": "prediction", "Opt_4_def": "plan or summary"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "If we ____ your request to amend the information, we will make reasonable efforts to inform others, including people you have authorized, of the amendment.", "Opt_1": "trigger", "Opt_2": "discern", "Opt_3": "decline", "Opt_4": "accept", "Answer": "accept", "Opt_1_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_2_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_3_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to agree (to have)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She is so passive in German class. It's no wonder that she can ____ speak a word of the language.", "Opt_1": "largely", "Opt_2": "hardly", "Opt_3": "extremely", "Opt_4": "namely", "Answer": "hardly", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "not very much", "Opt_3_def": "very", "Opt_4_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "She should be able to ____ to take care of the children on \ufffd\ufffd200.00 per month.", "Opt_1": "launch", "Opt_2": "postpone", "Opt_3": "produce", "Opt_4": "manage", "Answer": "manage", "Opt_1_def": "to begin", "Opt_2_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_3_def": "to make or create", "Opt_4_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "What motives have ____ incited him to overcome all the hardships and temptations he encountered on his way from a miserable life to an honorable one.", "Opt_1": "thus", "Opt_2": "largely", "Opt_3": "naturally", "Opt_4": "recently", "Answer": "thus", "Opt_1_def": "so", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_4_def": "in the near past"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It is scheduled to begin at 3:30 p.m. A decision to cancel or ____ the match will be made later in the day, if necessary.", "Opt_1": "express", "Opt_2": "postpone", "Opt_3": "expand", "Opt_4": "fail", "Answer": "postpone", "Opt_1_def": "to say or mean", "Opt_2_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_4_def": "to not do something, or not work as expected; to do badly"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "In the USA and Germany the people ____ a new government every four years; in the UK it is every five years.", "Opt_1": "present", "Opt_2": "elect", "Opt_3": "supervise", "Opt_4": "enhance", "Answer": "elect", "Opt_1_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_2_def": "to choose by voting", "Opt_3_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to make something better"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A rich parent has made a large ____ so that the school can buy new computers.", "Opt_1": "guarantee", "Opt_2": "account", "Opt_3": "area", "Opt_4": "grant", "Answer": "grant", "Opt_1_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_2_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_3_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_4_def": "a sum of money given to a person or organization"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "History is filled with examples of military leaders who have suffered at the mercy of climate conditions that they failed to ____ adequately.", "Opt_1": "develop", "Opt_2": "commence", "Opt_3": "contemplate", "Opt_4": "estimate", "Answer": "contemplate", "Opt_1_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_2_def": "to start", "Opt_3_def": "to think about; to consider", "Opt_4_def": "to make an intelligent guess"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Survey show that women in American don't ____ their most serious health risk.", "Opt_1": "obey", "Opt_2": "recognize", "Opt_3": "contain", "Opt_4": "predict", "Answer": "recognize", "Opt_1_def": "to do as commanded or expected", "Opt_2_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_3_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_4_def": "to say what will happen in the future"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The director had to ____ the school play when 4 of the cast fell ill the day before the first performance.", "Opt_1": "accompany", "Opt_2": "cancel", "Opt_3": "refute", "Opt_4": "abuse", "Answer": "cancel", "Opt_1_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_2_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_3_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_4_def": "to treat someone or something badly"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The sorting of students into ____ ability and achievement groups is nearly as old as universal compulsory education in the United States.", "Opt_1": "legitimate", "Opt_2": "dynamic", "Opt_3": "dense", "Opt_4": "homogeneous", "Answer": "homogeneous", "Opt_1_def": "correct; allowed", "Opt_2_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_3_def": "thick; full; detailed", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The Supreme Court held that the free exercise of religion did not ____ an Orthodox Jew to wear a yarmulke when he was on duty as an officer of law.", "Opt_1": "verify", "Opt_2": "entitle", "Opt_3": "constitute", "Opt_4": "comprehend", "Answer": "entitle", "Opt_1_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_2_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_4_def": "to understand"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Do we have an ____ to help the poor?", "Opt_1": "obligation", "Opt_2": "instinct", "Opt_3": "mechanism", "Opt_4": "result", "Answer": "obligation", "Opt_1_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_2_def": "natural feeling or reaction", "Opt_3_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_4_def": "outcome, effect"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The company's ____ was to increase sales by 20%. Due to the high cost of oil in the past year, it was not successful.", "Opt_1": "victory", "Opt_2": "source", "Opt_3": "device", "Opt_4": "intention", "Answer": "intention", "Opt_1_def": "win", "Opt_2_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_3_def": "object; method", "Opt_4_def": "plan, aim"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The company's target for the year was to expand sales by \ufffd\ufffd2 million. Now they expect to exceed this ____ by 40%.", "Opt_1": "figure", "Opt_2": "prejudice", "Opt_3": "precaution", "Opt_4": "revolution", "Answer": "figure", "Opt_1_def": "number", "Opt_2_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background", "Opt_3_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_4_def": "a time of great change"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Although Katrina affected the material ____ of Louisiana, it did not diminish the great spirit of the people here.", "Opt_1": "stage", "Opt_2": "desire", "Opt_3": "environment", "Opt_4": "profit", "Answer": "environment", "Opt_1_def": "period of time, part of a process", "Opt_2_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_3_def": "the world around us", "Opt_4_def": "money gained"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The first ____ change in the business model came with Henry Ford's move toward standardization and applying the concepts of a production line to the car.", "Opt_1": "prompt", "Opt_2": "ideal", "Opt_3": "radical", "Opt_4": "permanent", "Answer": "radical", "Opt_1_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_2_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_3_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_4_def": "lasting for ever or for a very long time"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The Health Minister has made the ____ request that parents make sure their children eat enough fruit and vegetables.", "Opt_1": "principal", "Opt_2": "accurate", "Opt_3": "related", "Opt_4": "reasonable", "Answer": "reasonable", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_3_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable, quite good"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "By signing the pledge, students make a personal commitment to conserve energy and help ____ to Yale's goal of reducing greenhouse gases by 10 percent.", "Opt_1": "enlarge", "Opt_2": "respect", "Opt_3": "contribute", "Opt_4": "collaborate", "Answer": "contribute", "Opt_1_def": "to make larger", "Opt_2_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_3_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_4_def": "to work together"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Two thirds of the ____ of the earth are covered with water.", "Opt_1": "phrase", "Opt_2": "surface", "Opt_3": "demand", "Opt_4": "statement", "Answer": "surface", "Opt_1_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_2_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_3_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_4_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The new government has promised not to repeat the mistakes of the ____ one.", "Opt_1": "previous", "Opt_2": "frequent", "Opt_3": "temporary", "Opt_4": "outstanding", "Answer": "previous", "Opt_1_def": "the one before", "Opt_2_def": "often", "Opt_3_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_4_def": "excellent"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The police ____ set up a committee whose task was to investigate the reasons for the shooting of the wrong man.", "Opt_1": "outstanding", "Opt_2": "chief", "Opt_3": "commercial", "Opt_4": "pure", "Answer": "chief", "Opt_1_def": "excellent", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "to do with business", "Opt_4_def": "complete, 100%"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is a ____ to think that you can put off working until the week before the exam and still pass it.", "Opt_1": "fallacy", "Opt_2": "amount", "Opt_3": "surface", "Opt_4": "administration", "Answer": "fallacy", "Opt_1_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_2_def": "how much there is of something", "Opt_3_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_4_def": "the people responsible for running an organization such as the government or a school"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "In an effective group, each person can exert sufficient ____ on the decisions of the group to prevent the group from setting unattainable goals.", "Opt_1": "influence", "Opt_2": "goal", "Opt_3": "fund", "Opt_4": "object", "Answer": "influence", "Opt_1_def": "effect", "Opt_2_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_3_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_4_def": "thing"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We could not ____ any significant effect of our dietary recommendations in terms of birth weight and duration of pregnancy.", "Opt_1": "interfere", "Opt_2": "impress", "Opt_3": "blame", "Opt_4": "detect", "Answer": "detect", "Opt_1_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_2_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_3_def": "to accuse", "Opt_4_def": "to see, find or notice"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Since we can't ____ it directly, we need to infer it from the things we can ____.", "Opt_1": "observe", "Opt_2": "formulate", "Opt_3": "behave", "Opt_4": "qualify", "Answer": "observe", "Opt_1_def": "to watch carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to express", "Opt_3_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_4_def": "to become eligible"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "If we are to ____ in creating a true sense of citizenship in our students, we won't do so by offering an all-purpose, first-year global civics course.", "Opt_1": "conserve", "Opt_2": "succeed", "Opt_3": "append", "Opt_4": "train", "Answer": "succeed", "Opt_1_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_2_def": "to do well", "Opt_3_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_4_def": "to teach someone how to do a job"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The idea was to ____ the possibility of a local court or government treating a foreign investor unfairly.", "Opt_1": "remove", "Opt_2": "suffer", "Opt_3": "oppose", "Opt_4": "constitute", "Answer": "remove", "Opt_1_def": "to take away", "Opt_2_def": "to experience something bad or painful", "Opt_3_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_4_def": "to be; to make up"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "She had shown no ____ to engage in abusive conduct.", "Opt_1": "propensity", "Opt_2": "institution", "Opt_3": "purpose", "Opt_4": "influence", "Answer": "propensity", "Opt_1_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_2_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_3_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_4_def": "effect"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If we reflect just a little more, we will see that ____ is hardly the right adjective.", "Opt_1": "random", "Opt_2": "competent", "Opt_3": "unique", "Opt_4": "artificial", "Answer": "random", "Opt_1_def": "by chance; without any sequence", "Opt_2_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_3_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_4_def": "not real or natural"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Unidata is a ____ community of education and research institutions vested in the common goal of sharing data, tools to access the data, and software to use and visualize the data.", "Opt_1": "substantial", "Opt_2": "remote", "Opt_3": "ideal", "Opt_4": "diverse", "Answer": "diverse", "Opt_1_def": "large", "Opt_2_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_3_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_4_def": "many and different"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The explanation for this ____ decision lies in the immediate circumstances surrounding the creation of the United Nations.", "Opt_1": "available", "Opt_2": "subsequent", "Opt_3": "extraordinary", "Opt_4": "constant", "Answer": "extraordinary", "Opt_1_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_2_def": "next, following", "Opt_3_def": "very unusual", "Opt_4_def": "not changing; long-lasting"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The lawyer was acting on ____ of the two children who had lost their parents in a car accident.", "Opt_1": "behalf", "Opt_2": "transition", "Opt_3": "description", "Opt_4": "formula", "Answer": "behalf", "Opt_1_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_2_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_3_def": "an account of what something is like or looks like", "Opt_4_def": "a method of doing something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "We will not violate the personal ____ of co-workers and customers, and will respect their right to privacy.", "Opt_1": "property", "Opt_2": "summary", "Opt_3": "fault", "Opt_4": "amount", "Answer": "property", "Opt_1_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_2_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_3_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_4_def": "how much there is of something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ____ minister is today expected to announce the date of the next election.", "Opt_1": "complete", "Opt_2": "related", "Opt_3": "prime", "Opt_4": "rare", "Answer": "prime", "Opt_1_def": "full or finished", "Opt_2_def": "connected; having something to do with each other", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "unusual"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Copying from the internet has grown on a large ____ in recent years.", "Opt_1": "surplus", "Opt_2": "liberty", "Opt_3": "scale", "Opt_4": "industry", "Answer": "scale", "Opt_1_def": "to be, go or make all the way around", "Opt_2_def": "freedom", "Opt_3_def": "extent", "Opt_4_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Hence it is a challenging ____ for the employers to determine the factors that stimulate job satisfaction in its employees and act on it.", "Opt_1": "task", "Opt_2": "committee", "Opt_3": "interpretation", "Opt_4": "opinion", "Answer": "task", "Opt_1_def": "job", "Opt_2_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_3_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_4_def": "view; what you think about someone or something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The number of students in the school will continue to ____ in the next few years as Frankfurt increases in popularity.", "Opt_1": "exploit", "Opt_2": "fluctuate", "Opt_3": "multiply", "Opt_4": "formulate", "Answer": "multiply", "Opt_1_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_2_def": "to vary; to rise and fall", "Opt_3_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_4_def": "to express"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There is some ____ that she plagiarized her research essay.", "Opt_1": "responsibility", "Opt_2": "directions", "Opt_3": "intention", "Opt_4": "evidence", "Answer": "evidence", "Opt_1_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_2_def": "instructions", "Opt_3_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_4_def": "proof, signs"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The documentation must ____ of a comprehensive, typed report that states a specific, current diagnosis.", "Opt_1": "belong", "Opt_2": "exist", "Opt_3": "prove", "Opt_4": "consist", "Answer": "consist", "Opt_1_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_2_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_3_def": "to show to be true", "Opt_4_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There is usually a close ____ between students of the same nationality at an international school.", "Opt_1": "attention", "Opt_2": "commodity", "Opt_3": "bond", "Opt_4": "feature", "Answer": "bond", "Opt_1_def": "focus", "Opt_2_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_3_def": "link; tie", "Opt_4_def": "part, aspect"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "If submitted in other languages, an English version must ____ the submission.", "Opt_1": "suppress", "Opt_2": "risk", "Opt_3": "accompany", "Opt_4": "exclude", "Answer": "accompany", "Opt_1_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to act in a way that might lead to danger or failure", "Opt_3_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_4_def": "to leave out; opposite of include"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Without a filter on perceptual input, our brains would have the impossible task of sifting through an overload of information to ____ important from unimportant information.", "Opt_1": "rotate", "Opt_2": "store", "Opt_3": "separate", "Opt_4": "exert", "Answer": "separate", "Opt_1_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_2_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_3_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_4_def": "to use"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is too soon to ____ the success of the \"war on terror\".", "Opt_1": "correlate", "Opt_2": "abuse", "Opt_3": "receive", "Opt_4": "evaluate", "Answer": "evaluate", "Opt_1_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_2_def": "to treat someone or something badly", "Opt_3_def": "to get", "Opt_4_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Most of the school's ____ comes from the school fees paid by the companies who send their employees to work in Germany.", "Opt_1": "summary", "Opt_2": "consequence", "Opt_3": "sphere", "Opt_4": "revenue", "Answer": "revenue", "Opt_1_def": "a short account of the most important details", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest", "Opt_4_def": "money, income"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government announced that it was pleased with the ____ fall in unemployment during its term in office.", "Opt_1": "steady", "Opt_2": "significant", "Opt_3": "public", "Opt_4": "legal", "Answer": "steady", "Opt_1_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_2_def": "important, large", "Opt_3_def": "open to all; not private", "Opt_4_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The late bus will ____ at 5:30 today, not at 5:15 as usual.", "Opt_1": "engage", "Opt_2": "emphasize", "Opt_3": "depart", "Opt_4": "solve", "Answer": "depart", "Opt_1_def": "to participate in; to focus attention on", "Opt_2_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_3_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_4_def": "to find an answer"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "I asked for a ____ summary of what happened. So why have you given me a 20-page report?", "Opt_1": "probable", "Opt_2": "conscious", "Opt_3": "concise", "Opt_4": "independent", "Answer": "concise", "Opt_1_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers.", "Opt_2_def": "aware, knowing", "Opt_3_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_4_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "It is not always easy for teachers to differentiate poor work that is ____ to laziness and poor work that is ____ to inability.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The libraries are in a poor ____ and are in urgent need of restocking with new books and journals in both Arabic and English.", "Opt_1": "assignment", "Opt_2": "responsibility", "Opt_3": "condition", "Opt_4": "credit", "Answer": "condition", "Opt_1_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_2_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_3_def": "state", "Opt_4_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "There is a serious shortage of workers in the ____ of computer science. The government is hoping to attract qualified workers from overseas to fill the vacancies.", "Opt_1": "guide", "Opt_2": "profession", "Opt_3": "guarantee", "Opt_4": "magnitude", "Answer": "profession", "Opt_1_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_2_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_3_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen", "Opt_4_def": "size; amount"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ used for the actual campaign was somewhat different.", "Opt_1": "strategy", "Opt_2": "demand", "Opt_3": "location", "Opt_4": "issue", "Answer": "strategy", "Opt_1_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_2_def": "a need or desire for", "Opt_3_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_4_def": "a matter or problem"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Now that you have revised your work, the next stage of the writing ____ is to edit it for errors of grammar or spelling.", "Opt_1": "mixture", "Opt_2": "interpretation", "Opt_3": "process", "Opt_4": "counsel", "Answer": "process", "Opt_1_def": "combination", "Opt_2_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_3_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_4_def": "advice; advisor"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The government has succeeded in reducing unemployment ____ older people; conversely, young people are having ever more difficulty finding a job.", "Opt_1": "among", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "in, between", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Shonekan was unable to ____ Nigeria's ever-growing economic problems.", "Opt_1": "develop", "Opt_2": "devote", "Opt_3": "tolerate", "Opt_4": "reverse", "Answer": "reverse", "Opt_1_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_2_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_3_def": "to allow to happen; to bear", "Opt_4_def": "to turn back or go back"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It can take as much as a ____ or more of hard study in a foreign language to become as fluent as a native speaker of that language.", "Opt_1": "decade", "Opt_2": "topic", "Opt_3": "outcome", "Opt_4": "demand", "Answer": "decade", "Opt_1_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_2_def": "area of interest or discussion", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "a need or desire for"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We must find a way to ____ the new questioning skills along with the new curriculum when the funding is gone.", "Opt_1": "terminate", "Opt_2": "enable", "Opt_3": "sustain", "Opt_4": "supervise", "Answer": "sustain", "Opt_1_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_4_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government hopes that its new tax law will result ____ in a reduction in teenage pregnancy.", "Opt_1": "indirectly", "Opt_2": "thereby", "Opt_3": "nevertheless", "Opt_4": "therefore", "Answer": "indirectly", "Opt_1_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_2_def": "by doing this", "Opt_3_def": "however (although / despite that)", "Opt_4_def": "so, as a result"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The demand for oil is likely to increase as people in developing countries such as China and India ____ cars.", "Opt_1": "incorporate", "Opt_2": "attempt", "Opt_3": "specify", "Opt_4": "acquire", "Answer": "acquire", "Opt_1_def": "to include", "Opt_2_def": "to try", "Opt_3_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "For the first time, satellite imagery has allowed scientists to observe how icebergs in a remote corner of Antarctica can ____ an entire marine ecosystem.", "Opt_1": "disrupt", "Opt_2": "detect", "Opt_3": "promote", "Opt_4": "halt", "Answer": "disrupt", "Opt_1_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage", "Opt_2_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_3_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Google uses a ____ computer program to generate its lists of hits within a very short period of time.", "Opt_1": "former", "Opt_2": "remote", "Opt_3": "similar", "Opt_4": "unique", "Answer": "unique", "Opt_1_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_2_def": "far, distant, small", "Opt_3_def": "like, almost the same as", "Opt_4_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "They simply decided for ____ reasons that his age was not a drawback, that perhaps (at that time and for that position) it was an advantage.", "Opt_1": "adequate", "Opt_2": "average", "Opt_3": "regular", "Opt_4": "various", "Answer": "various", "Opt_1_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_2_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_3_def": "predictable, following a pattern; normal", "Opt_4_def": "several, of different kinds"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The Ruhrgebiet is a large urban ____ in north west Germany.", "Opt_1": "substitute", "Opt_2": "area", "Opt_3": "dimension", "Opt_4": "scheme", "Answer": "area", "Opt_1_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_2_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_3_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_4_def": "plan. idea, project"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Many German companies have decided to ____ their factories to parts of the world where workers are cheaper.", "Opt_1": "invent", "Opt_2": "consult", "Opt_3": "transfer", "Opt_4": "circulate", "Answer": "transfer", "Opt_1_def": "to create (often a new object)", "Opt_2_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_3_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_4_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government predicts that oil prices will not ____ as much this year as last year.", "Opt_1": "exhibit", "Opt_2": "finance", "Opt_3": "vary", "Opt_4": "survey", "Answer": "vary", "Opt_1_def": "to show", "Opt_2_def": "to do with money and payment", "Opt_3_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_4_def": "questionnaire; information gained by questioning people or data"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The world's largest film ____ is in Hollywood, Los Angeles.", "Opt_1": "debate", "Opt_2": "industry", "Opt_3": "notion", "Opt_4": "attitude", "Answer": "industry", "Opt_1_def": "formal discussion", "Opt_2_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_3_def": "idea; concept", "Opt_4_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is not ____ that he could have gained such a good grade without help from someone else.", "Opt_1": "visual", "Opt_2": "technical", "Opt_3": "credible", "Opt_4": "random", "Answer": "credible", "Opt_1_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_2_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_3_def": "believable", "Opt_4_def": "by chance; without any sequence"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The reduction in personal tax is intended to ____ spending because people will have more money in their pockets.", "Opt_1": "decrease", "Opt_2": "interact", "Opt_3": "interrupt", "Opt_4": "stimulate", "Answer": "stimulate", "Opt_1_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_2_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_3_def": "to stop something from happening", "Opt_4_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Doctors have found a connection between cannabis use and ____ illness. This is especially a danger for people who have started taking drugs at an early age.", "Opt_1": "effective", "Opt_2": "numerous", "Opt_3": "mental", "Opt_4": "inevitable", "Answer": "mental", "Opt_1_def": "good, working well", "Opt_2_def": "very many", "Opt_3_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ way of attacking the security of computer programs is to feed them unexpected and deceptive inputs.", "Opt_1": "classic", "Opt_2": "former", "Opt_3": "compulsory", "Opt_4": "mental", "Answer": "classic", "Opt_1_def": "very good, the best or most used", "Opt_2_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_3_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_4_def": "of the brain or mind"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Although most universities say they place a high value on teaching, faculty often feel that teaching is somehow ____ to the administration.", "Opt_1": "invisible", "Opt_2": "brief", "Opt_3": "scarce", "Opt_4": "intrinsic", "Answer": "invisible", "Opt_1_def": "cannot be seen", "Opt_2_def": "short", "Opt_3_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_4_def": "belonging to; inherent in"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The website shows how schools ____ and use their resources.", "Opt_1": "fare", "Opt_2": "allocate", "Opt_3": "strive", "Opt_4": "connect", "Answer": "allocate", "Opt_1_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_2_def": "to give to (to promise to give)", "Opt_3_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_4_def": "to bring or put together"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You will ____ many difficulties but if you persist in your efforts, you will succeed.", "Opt_1": "recognize", "Opt_2": "manipulate", "Opt_3": "encounter", "Opt_4": "sustain", "Answer": "encounter", "Opt_1_def": "to know or understand (who someone is or what something is)", "Opt_2_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_3_def": "to meet or experience", "Opt_4_def": "to keep going; to maintain"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If you ____ against the school's computer use policy, you will not be permitted to use the computer labs.", "Opt_1": "stipulate", "Opt_2": "specify", "Opt_3": "offend", "Opt_4": "induce", "Answer": "offend", "Opt_1_def": "to require", "Opt_2_def": "to state exactly", "Opt_3_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_4_def": "to make happen; to force"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The continued presence of a huge military force in the Gulf area provides the necessary element of pressure to ____ implementation of obligations.", "Opt_1": "ensure", "Opt_2": "imply", "Opt_3": "deteriorate", "Opt_4": "restrict", "Answer": "ensure", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_3_def": "to get worse", "Opt_4_def": "to limit"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "That ____ data that is consistent, easy to manipulate, and repeatable.", "Opt_1": "means", "Opt_2": "disaster", "Opt_3": "concept", "Opt_4": "belief", "Answer": "means", "Opt_1_def": "way", "Opt_2_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_3_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_4_def": "what you think; what you believe in"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We can only ____ that Fulton was already too deeply committed to his own plan to consider alternative ideas.", "Opt_1": "ensure", "Opt_2": "review", "Opt_3": "suppose", "Opt_4": "arrange", "Answer": "suppose", "Opt_1_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_2_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_3_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_4_def": "to plan to happen; to group together"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The army sent 2,000 of its soldiers to ____ clothing to the refugees driven out of their homes by fighting.", "Opt_1": "contribute", "Opt_2": "distribute", "Opt_3": "reject", "Opt_4": "master", "Answer": "distribute", "Opt_1_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_2_def": "to give out", "Opt_3_def": "to refuse", "Opt_4_def": "to (gain) control"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "FAQ > How do I ____ for free health services?", "Opt_1": "presume", "Opt_2": "estimate", "Opt_3": "oppose", "Opt_4": "qualify", "Answer": "qualify", "Opt_1_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_2_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_3_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_4_def": "to become eligible"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "A Parisian mob broke into the palace killing many of the guards, while searching for the ____ family.", "Opt_1": "royal", "Opt_2": "previous", "Opt_3": "outstanding", "Opt_4": "uniform", "Answer": "royal", "Opt_1_def": "of kings and queens", "Opt_2_def": "the one before", "Opt_3_def": "excellent", "Opt_4_def": "having the same qualities"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The last ____ has seen a major transformation of the Indian car industry.", "Opt_1": "balance", "Opt_2": "exhibit", "Opt_3": "experiment", "Opt_4": "decade", "Answer": "decade", "Opt_1_def": "equalness", "Opt_2_def": "to show", "Opt_3_def": "test", "Opt_4_def": "a period of ten years"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Teachers fear that the problems in the Middle East may strain the ____ between some of the Arab and Israeli students at the school.", "Opt_1": "trait", "Opt_2": "alternative", "Opt_3": "format", "Opt_4": "relationship", "Answer": "relationship", "Opt_1_def": "characteristic; aspect", "Opt_2_def": "other possibility", "Opt_3_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_4_def": "the way to things are connected"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If the demonstrations ____ much longer, they will force the government to change its plans.", "Opt_1": "continue", "Opt_2": "exhaust", "Opt_3": "consume", "Opt_4": "discern", "Answer": "continue", "Opt_1_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_2_def": "to use up", "Opt_3_def": "to use, or use up", "Opt_4_def": "to see; to perceive"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Many prisons cannot ____ with this law due to lack of space and inadequate facilities.", "Opt_1": "trade", "Opt_2": "force", "Opt_3": "comply", "Opt_4": "diverge", "Answer": "comply", "Opt_1_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_2_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_3_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_4_def": "to move apart; to be different from"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Is this a ____ picture by Picasso or is it a fake?", "Opt_1": "valid", "Opt_2": "latter", "Opt_3": "several", "Opt_4": "genuine", "Answer": "genuine", "Opt_1_def": "correct", "Opt_2_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_3_def": "many (about 6 or seven)", "Opt_4_def": "real and authentic"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The demonstrators failed to ____ the progress of the Olympic torch through the city streets.", "Opt_1": "alter", "Opt_2": "motivate", "Opt_3": "stress", "Opt_4": "interrupt", "Answer": "interrupt", "Opt_1_def": "to change", "Opt_2_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_4_def": "to stop something from happening"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is very satisfying as a teacher to see the growth in the ____ of your students.", "Opt_1": "region", "Opt_2": "ability", "Opt_3": "expert", "Opt_4": "property", "Answer": "ability", "Opt_1_def": "part of a place", "Opt_2_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_3_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_4_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Although there are a number of credible strategies for trying to retain employees, money appears to be the most powerful retention tool with ____ to top performers.", "Opt_1": "amend", "Opt_2": "prohibit", "Opt_3": "regard", "Opt_4": "embody", "Answer": "regard", "Opt_1_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_2_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_3_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to be a good example of .."}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The libraries are in a ____ condition and are in urgent need of restocking with new books and journals in both Arabic and English.", "Opt_1": "extraordinary", "Opt_2": "authentic", "Opt_3": "poor", "Opt_4": "vital", "Answer": "poor", "Opt_1_def": "very unusual", "Opt_2_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_3_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The school is planning to bring in an ____ tax expert to analyze its finance methods.", "Opt_1": "anonymous", "Opt_2": "external", "Opt_3": "unique", "Opt_4": "political", "Answer": "external", "Opt_1_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_2_def": "outside", "Opt_3_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_4_def": "to do government and politics"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "They failed to publicly ____ the message that climate change will having a direct negative impact on global security.", "Opt_1": "reinforce", "Opt_2": "differentiate", "Opt_3": "accompany", "Opt_4": "continue", "Answer": "reinforce", "Opt_1_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_2_def": "to make different; to see the difference", "Opt_3_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together", "Opt_4_def": "to carry on, not stop"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "I find it quite hard to understand why anyone would attempt to ____ or ignore these accomplishments.", "Opt_1": "refute", "Opt_2": "reform", "Opt_3": "combine", "Opt_4": "blame", "Answer": "refute", "Opt_1_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny", "Opt_2_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_3_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_4_def": "to accuse"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is a ____ at the school for teachers to share a cake or cookies with their colleagues when it is their birthday.", "Opt_1": "structure", "Opt_2": "tool", "Opt_3": "community", "Opt_4": "tradition", "Answer": "tradition", "Opt_1_def": "the way something is made or organized", "Opt_2_def": "something used to do a job", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people", "Opt_4_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The study of Growth and Development can help us to know a person more thoroughly and ____ be better doctors.", "Opt_1": "universally", "Opt_2": "barely", "Opt_3": "gradually", "Opt_4": "thereby", "Answer": "thereby", "Opt_1_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_3_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_4_def": "by doing this"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government said that it had no ____ to give the reasons for its decision.", "Opt_1": "issue", "Opt_2": "experiment", "Opt_3": "obligation", "Opt_4": "forecast", "Answer": "obligation", "Opt_1_def": "a matter or problem", "Opt_2_def": "test", "Opt_3_def": "a requirement to do something", "Opt_4_def": "prediction"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The school's ____ were told that they would not be getting an increase of pay in the new year.", "Opt_1": "scope", "Opt_2": "fee", "Opt_3": "fund", "Opt_4": "staff", "Answer": "staff", "Opt_1_def": "extent, range", "Opt_2_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)", "Opt_3_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_4_def": "people working at a particular place (particularly an office or school)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In a densely populated area, an earthquake may do far more damage than one of greater ____ that occurs in a remote area.", "Opt_1": "magnitude", "Opt_2": "episode", "Opt_3": "scope", "Opt_4": "evidence", "Answer": "magnitude", "Opt_1_def": "size; amount", "Opt_2_def": "period of time", "Opt_3_def": "extent, range", "Opt_4_def": "proof, signs"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The group work done during these workshops will culminate in a ____ of papers, presented by project participants, at a one-day conference.", "Opt_1": "counsel", "Opt_2": "series", "Opt_3": "guide", "Opt_4": "device", "Answer": "series", "Opt_1_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_2_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_4_def": "object; method"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The experiment resulted in a ____ that did not seem correct.", "Opt_1": "criterion", "Opt_2": "statistic", "Opt_3": "shortage", "Opt_4": "role", "Answer": "statistic", "Opt_1_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_2_def": "mathematical number", "Opt_3_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_4_def": "job or function"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If you are in constant pain you should ____ a doctor.", "Opt_1": "add", "Opt_2": "explain", "Opt_3": "appeal", "Opt_4": "consult", "Answer": "consult", "Opt_1_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_2_def": "to give the reason for something or say how to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_4_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Hence it is a challenging task for the employers to determine the factors that ____ job satisfaction in its employees and act on it.", "Opt_1": "stimulate", "Opt_2": "decrease", "Opt_3": "attach", "Opt_4": "align", "Answer": "stimulate", "Opt_1_def": "to interest, make grow or encourage", "Opt_2_def": "to get smaller, to go down", "Opt_3_def": "to put together with", "Opt_4_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "I need to ____ the importance of meeting the project deadlines.", "Opt_1": "participate", "Opt_2": "infer", "Opt_3": "create", "Opt_4": "emphasize", "Answer": "emphasize", "Opt_1_def": "to take part", "Opt_2_def": "to come to a conclusion about something", "Opt_3_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_4_def": "to stress, to say something strongly"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "When morality comes up against ____, it is seldom ____ that loses.", "Opt_1": "truth", "Opt_2": "profit", "Opt_3": "level", "Opt_4": "research", "Answer": "profit", "Opt_1_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_2_def": "money gained", "Opt_3_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_4_def": "study; the finding of information"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "To include an ____ on your website, you will need to insert the ____ into your webpage using an HTML editor.", "Opt_1": "schedule", "Opt_2": "facilities", "Opt_3": "image", "Opt_4": "assignment", "Answer": "image", "Opt_1_def": "timetable", "Opt_2_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_3_def": "picture", "Opt_4_def": "a task; the giving of a task"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government's election ____ is a classic case of failure to learn from past mistakes.", "Opt_1": "citizen", "Opt_2": "result", "Opt_3": "defeat", "Opt_4": "interior", "Answer": "defeat", "Opt_1_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_2_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_3_def": "a loss (often in a battle or sports event)", "Opt_4_def": "inside"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "As the number of old people increases, so has the concern that there is not enough money in the health system to take ____ care of them.", "Opt_1": "appropriate", "Opt_2": "characteristic", "Opt_3": "radical", "Opt_4": "proper", "Answer": "proper", "Opt_1_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable", "Opt_2_def": "typical", "Opt_3_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_4_def": "correct, appropriate"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "During various stages of a planning process, ____ and crosscheck the goals and objectives in the plan elements so that they do not contradict one another.", "Opt_1": "suppress", "Opt_2": "reflect", "Opt_3": "lessen", "Opt_4": "review", "Answer": "review", "Opt_1_def": "to hold back; to not allow to happen", "Opt_2_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_3_def": "to reduce", "Opt_4_def": "to check over (and make changes)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We hoped to find ____ data on why certain people donate time and money and others don't.", "Opt_1": "relevant", "Opt_2": "suitable", "Opt_3": "flexible", "Opt_4": "optional", "Answer": "relevant", "Opt_1_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_2_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "can be changed or bent", "Opt_4_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There is an obvious ____ to her absences from school: Monday mornings and Friday afternoons!", "Opt_1": "field", "Opt_2": "sector", "Opt_3": "pattern", "Opt_4": "alternative", "Answer": "pattern", "Opt_1_def": "area of interest or study", "Opt_2_def": "part; area", "Opt_3_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "other possibility"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If you want to ____ in school you will have to study hard!", "Opt_1": "stress", "Opt_2": "evolve", "Opt_3": "succeed", "Opt_4": "expose", "Answer": "succeed", "Opt_1_def": "to emphasize; to say what is important", "Opt_2_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_3_def": "to do well", "Opt_4_def": "to uncover, reveal"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Teachers can suggest that students get a minimum of 8 hours sleep per night, but they cannot ____ it.", "Opt_1": "dictate", "Opt_2": "investigate", "Opt_3": "deserve", "Opt_4": "dedicate", "Answer": "dictate", "Opt_1_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_2_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_3_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_4_def": "to devote (time and attention)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Spending months at a time in orbit, the scientists will be able to observe changes on the earth ____ them from day to day.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "beneath", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The school is planning to ____ its lunchtime sports program after hearing a request from the student council.", "Opt_1": "constitute", "Opt_2": "control", "Opt_3": "gather", "Opt_4": "revive", "Answer": "revive", "Opt_1_def": "to be; to make up", "Opt_2_def": "to have and exercise power over something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_4_def": "to bring back (to life)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I do not feel that the possible applications of a line of research should be allowed to ____ the directions of research in my laboratory.", "Opt_1": "possess", "Opt_2": "dictate", "Opt_3": "conform", "Opt_4": "denote", "Answer": "dictate", "Opt_1_def": "to have or own", "Opt_2_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_3_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to be a sign of"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The ambassador seems to have failed in his duty to correctly ____ the government he serves.", "Opt_1": "demonstrate", "Opt_2": "inform", "Opt_3": "highlight", "Opt_4": "acquire", "Answer": "inform", "Opt_1_def": "to show", "Opt_2_def": "to say, give information", "Opt_3_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_4_def": "to get or obtain"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The trial court noted that the newspaper articles ____ reported events and provided no editorial comment.", "Opt_1": "universally", "Opt_2": "greatly", "Opt_3": "merely", "Opt_4": "virtually", "Answer": "merely", "Opt_1_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_2_def": "very much", "Opt_3_def": "only, just, simply", "Opt_4_def": "almost"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In closing, I want to assert that I know that our community is up to meeting these challenges and I know that the ____ and inspiring decisions that will be made.", "Opt_1": "principal", "Opt_2": "diverse", "Opt_3": "accurate", "Opt_4": "bold", "Answer": "bold", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "many and different", "Opt_3_def": "exact, containing no mistakes", "Opt_4_def": "brave"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "He said that any art teacher who did not ____ students to ten thousand years of art was \"criminal.\"", "Opt_1": "expose", "Opt_2": "participate", "Opt_3": "preserve", "Opt_4": "adopt", "Answer": "expose", "Opt_1_def": "to uncover, reveal", "Opt_2_def": "to take part", "Opt_3_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_4_def": "to take in; to start"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Teachers need to regularly ____ the quality of their student's work.", "Opt_1": "evaluate", "Opt_2": "edit", "Opt_3": "overcome", "Opt_4": "impose", "Answer": "evaluate", "Opt_1_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something", "Opt_2_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_3_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_4_def": "to force; to require to happen"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "But his son, who had hoped to occupy the throne of Armenia, could not ____ his discontent.", "Opt_1": "regulate", "Opt_2": "conceal", "Opt_3": "violate", "Opt_4": "found", "Answer": "conceal", "Opt_1_def": "to control", "Opt_2_def": "to hide", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_4_def": "to begin (often an organization)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Many economists ____ the rise in prices with the government's decision to tax imports.", "Opt_1": "associate", "Opt_2": "overcome", "Opt_3": "exist", "Opt_4": "repeat", "Answer": "associate", "Opt_1_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_2_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_3_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_4_def": "to do or say again"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It can take as much as a ____ or more of hard study in a foreign language to become as fluent as a native speaker of that language.", "Opt_1": "decade", "Opt_2": "area", "Opt_3": "debt", "Opt_4": "profit", "Answer": "decade", "Opt_1_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_2_def": "field, sphere", "Opt_3_def": "something owed to another person (often money)", "Opt_4_def": "money gained"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The court concluded that schools could not ____ disabled students whose disability causes their disruptive conduct.", "Opt_1": "strain", "Opt_2": "expel", "Opt_3": "contradict", "Opt_4": "organize", "Answer": "expel", "Opt_1_def": "to put under stress or make difficult", "Opt_2_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_3_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_4_def": "to put into (its proper) place"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This year you cannot choose which science course to do, but when you are in grade 9 you can ____ chemistry, physics or biology.", "Opt_1": "restrict", "Opt_2": "trade", "Opt_3": "force", "Opt_4": "select", "Answer": "select", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to exchange products or services", "Opt_3_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something", "Opt_4_def": "to choose"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "They faced problems for which they did not have the ____ or the training.", "Opt_1": "account", "Opt_2": "domain", "Opt_3": "challenge", "Opt_4": "equipment", "Answer": "equipment", "Opt_1_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_2_def": "area (of interest)", "Opt_3_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_4_def": "the things you need (to do a job or play sport, etc.)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I think your ____ is wrong. You should be in science class now, not ESL.", "Opt_1": "community", "Opt_2": "expert", "Opt_3": "schedule", "Opt_4": "quantity", "Answer": "schedule", "Opt_1_def": "a group of people", "Opt_2_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_3_def": "timetable", "Opt_4_def": "amount"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Less than 10% of students who need ____ skills education and don't get it survive in college.", "Opt_1": "rigid", "Opt_2": "smooth", "Opt_3": "identical", "Opt_4": "basic", "Answer": "basic", "Opt_1_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_2_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_3_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_4_def": "first or easy"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The business manager could not explain the ____ in the company's finances, and was asked to resign.", "Opt_1": "shortage", "Opt_2": "plenty", "Opt_3": "anomaly", "Opt_4": "prejudice", "Answer": "anomaly", "Opt_1_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_2_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_3_def": "an unexpected happening or piece of data", "Opt_4_def": "bias, discrimination, beliefs or feelings influenced by one's own background"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The Bush administration has failed to ____ the matter urgently, spending only \ufffd\ufffd1.3 billion per year.", "Opt_1": "disturb", "Opt_2": "block", "Opt_3": "disperse", "Opt_4": "address", "Answer": "address", "Opt_1_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_2_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent", "Opt_3_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_4_def": "to give attention to (an issue)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In proof of this, we may note that slavery did not ____ immediately on the reception of Christianity.", "Opt_1": "deliver", "Opt_2": "cease", "Opt_3": "arrange", "Opt_4": "expose", "Answer": "cease", "Opt_1_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_4_def": "to uncover, reveal"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The research addresses teacher attitudes toward the ____ of homework.", "Opt_1": "feature", "Opt_2": "order", "Opt_3": "assignment", "Opt_4": "district", "Answer": "assignment", "Opt_1_def": "part, aspect", "Opt_2_def": "sequence, place", "Opt_3_def": "a task; the giving of a task", "Opt_4_def": "region of a city"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Each programme is designed to give students the opportunity to ____ significant social, political and environmental issues using an innovative comparative model.", "Opt_1": "explore", "Opt_2": "culminate", "Opt_3": "select", "Opt_4": "prosper", "Answer": "explore", "Opt_1_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_2_def": "to end", "Opt_3_def": "to choose", "Opt_4_def": "to do well; to become rich"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "According to him migrants and refugees do not ____ enough in Dutch society.", "Opt_1": "manage", "Opt_2": "integrate", "Opt_3": "interact", "Opt_4": "launch", "Answer": "integrate", "Opt_1_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_2_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_3_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_4_def": "to begin"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Abortion is not a fundamental right; it can be limited if the ____ wishes.", "Opt_1": "quality", "Opt_2": "state", "Opt_3": "event", "Opt_4": "magnitude", "Answer": "state", "Opt_1_def": "worth or value", "Opt_2_def": "condition, situation", "Opt_3_def": "a happening", "Opt_4_def": "size; amount"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "While we must ____ all terrorism, and we have many local enemies in various parts of the world.", "Opt_1": "suspend", "Opt_2": "separate", "Opt_3": "retire", "Opt_4": "oppose", "Answer": "oppose", "Opt_1_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_2_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_3_def": "to stop working", "Opt_4_def": "to be against or fight against something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "And, further, he didn't ____ a lecture from one whose own morality has been deficient.", "Opt_1": "appreciate", "Opt_2": "contain", "Opt_3": "govern", "Opt_4": "accumulate", "Answer": "appreciate", "Opt_1_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_2_def": "to have in it; to hold inside", "Opt_3_def": "to control or influence", "Opt_4_def": "to grow; to gather together"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "He has made ____ progress all year and should have no trouble passing his exams.", "Opt_1": "smooth", "Opt_2": "current", "Opt_3": "perpetual", "Opt_4": "elementary", "Answer": "smooth", "Opt_1_def": "easy, unproblematic", "Opt_2_def": "happening now", "Opt_3_def": "continuing for ever; never disappearing", "Opt_4_def": "easy"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Emma was ____ of these various and strongly held opinions, through professional periodicals.", "Opt_1": "substantial", "Opt_2": "average", "Opt_3": "physical", "Opt_4": "conscious", "Answer": "conscious", "Opt_1_def": "large", "Opt_2_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_3_def": "of the body", "Opt_4_def": "aware, knowing"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Furthermore, as an educational institution, the College cannot ignore the ____ and perspectives of its students and must attempt to promote teaching practices and a campus atmosphere that benefits and ensures the success of all of its learners.", "Opt_1": "background", "Opt_2": "fault", "Opt_3": "error", "Opt_4": "status", "Answer": "background", "Opt_1_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_2_def": "responsibility for a mistake or other problem", "Opt_3_def": "a mistake", "Opt_4_def": "position, standing"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The Commission was unable to estimate the cost of complying with new requirements ____ data recording.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "regarding", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "about, concerning, with respect to"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The principal made no ____ on the reasons for asking the student to leave the school.", "Opt_1": "duty", "Opt_2": "comment", "Opt_3": "category", "Opt_4": "commodity", "Answer": "comment", "Opt_1_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_2_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_3_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_4_def": "a product; something you can buy"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Furthermore, as an educational institution, the College cannot ____ the background and perspectives of its students and must attempt to promote teaching practices and a campus atmosphere that benefits and ensures the success of all of its learners.", "Opt_1": "ignore", "Opt_2": "conform", "Opt_3": "integrate", "Opt_4": "enlarge", "Answer": "ignore", "Opt_1_def": "to take no notice of; to leave out (of consideration)", "Opt_2_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_3_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_4_def": "to make larger"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If mobile phones ____ any further, the keys will be too small to use.", "Opt_1": "harm", "Opt_2": "append", "Opt_3": "shrink", "Opt_4": "compete", "Answer": "shrink", "Opt_1_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_2_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_4_def": "to try and win against someone or something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The main ____ of living in the city is that you are close to good shopping and entertainment. Of course, city life has many dis____s too.", "Opt_1": "objective", "Opt_2": "advantage", "Opt_3": "experiment", "Opt_4": "interval", "Answer": "advantage", "Opt_1_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_2_def": "benefit", "Opt_3_def": "test", "Opt_4_def": "a period of time"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The police ____ found it difficult to explain why the wrong man had been arrested.", "Opt_1": "chief", "Opt_2": "intrinsic", "Opt_3": "eligible", "Opt_4": "discrete", "Answer": "chief", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_3_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_4_def": "separate"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Although the patient was in pain, the doctor did not ____ the problem as serious.", "Opt_1": "regard", "Opt_2": "reflect", "Opt_3": "interrupt", "Opt_4": "distinguish", "Answer": "regard", "Opt_1_def": "to think or have an opinion about something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to think or consider", "Opt_3_def": "to stop something from happening", "Opt_4_def": "to make clear the differences between two things"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You may have learned the steps of the scientific method but, in your preparation, failed to ____ each step with an example.", "Opt_1": "resist", "Opt_2": "accumulate", "Opt_3": "illustrate", "Opt_4": "edit", "Answer": "illustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to fight against", "Opt_2_def": "to grow; to gather together", "Opt_3_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_4_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "This was a ____ attempt at addressing the issue, and not a very scholarly or intellectual attempt.", "Opt_1": "moderate", "Opt_2": "spontaneous", "Opt_3": "infinite", "Opt_4": "political", "Answer": "spontaneous", "Opt_1_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_2_def": "happening without warning or planning", "Opt_3_def": "without an end", "Opt_4_def": "to do government and politics"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Please note that section 5 is the most important, and hence it should constitute the ____ of your journal entry.", "Opt_1": "scale", "Opt_2": "perspective", "Opt_3": "hypothesis", "Opt_4": "majority", "Answer": "majority", "Opt_1_def": "extent", "Opt_2_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_3_def": "idea or prediction", "Opt_4_def": "more than 50%"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "A common task in the English classroom is to ____ the parts of speech into nouns, adjectives, verbs, etc.", "Opt_1": "fare", "Opt_2": "employ", "Opt_3": "classify", "Opt_4": "cooperate", "Answer": "classify", "Opt_1_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_2_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_3_def": "to put into a category or class", "Opt_4_def": "to work (well) with another person"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Does this report ____ to this year or last year?", "Opt_1": "refer", "Opt_2": "resign", "Opt_3": "frustrate", "Opt_4": "prohibit", "Answer": "refer", "Opt_1_def": "to direct (attention) to; to mean", "Opt_2_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_3_def": "to stop or prevent", "Opt_4_def": "to ban, disallow"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The United Mine Workers was the recognized bargaining ____ for the coal miners in Illinois, Indiana, Ohio, and Pennsylvania.", "Opt_1": "circumstances", "Opt_2": "habit", "Opt_3": "agent", "Opt_4": "substitute", "Answer": "agent", "Opt_1_def": "situation", "Opt_2_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_3_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_4_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "For financial reasons the government had to cut the ____ to help prisoners on their release from jail.", "Opt_1": "treatment", "Opt_2": "service", "Opt_3": "programme", "Opt_4": "conflict", "Answer": "programme", "Opt_1_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_2_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_3_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_4_def": "problem, struggle or battle"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "I would set my classes up for failure if I did not ____ this very clear, but often overlooked, fact.", "Opt_1": "consult", "Opt_2": "assert", "Opt_3": "acknowledge", "Opt_4": "emerge", "Answer": "acknowledge", "Opt_1_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_2_def": "to claim, to say strongly", "Opt_3_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_4_def": "to come out; to become known"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Science and technology are driving explosive growth in the production of new knowledge, often with the power to ____ profound changes in society.", "Opt_1": "include", "Opt_2": "induce", "Opt_3": "associate", "Opt_4": "solve", "Answer": "induce", "Opt_1_def": "to put in; to have in", "Opt_2_def": "to make happen; to force", "Opt_3_def": "to link to; to make a connection to", "Opt_4_def": "to find an answer"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "He alleged that the state had adopted the policy of attacking the entire independent media rather than targeting ____ journalists as in the past.", "Opt_1": "behalf", "Opt_2": "individual", "Opt_3": "agent", "Opt_4": "career", "Answer": "individual", "Opt_1_def": "as a representative of; for the benefit of", "Opt_2_def": "one person", "Opt_3_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_4_def": "a long-term job"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We believe that individuals who respect and support a ____ global society will prosper as leaders in schools, universities, businesses, and human service.", "Opt_1": "suitable", "Opt_2": "elaborate", "Opt_3": "relevant", "Opt_4": "diverse", "Answer": "diverse", "Opt_1_def": "good for a particular job or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_3_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_4_def": "many and different"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You have a ____ chance of passing your exams if you work really hard for the rest of the term.", "Opt_1": "military", "Opt_2": "steady", "Opt_3": "faint", "Opt_4": "numerous", "Answer": "faint", "Opt_1_def": "to do with army", "Opt_2_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_3_def": "not strong", "Opt_4_def": "very many"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Infinity is an ____ idea that many students find difficult to understand.", "Opt_1": "abstract", "Opt_2": "elaborate", "Opt_3": "contemporary", "Opt_4": "smooth", "Answer": "abstract", "Opt_1_def": "not specific or concrete", "Opt_2_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_3_def": "of this time, happening now", "Opt_4_def": "easy, unproblematic"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It was bold of him to ____ the boss in front of all the workers.", "Opt_1": "oppose", "Opt_2": "exchange", "Opt_3": "append", "Opt_4": "criticize", "Answer": "criticize", "Opt_1_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_2_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_3_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)", "Opt_4_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Under these treaties, US warships did not have to ____ the nature of the weapons they carried.", "Opt_1": "comply", "Opt_2": "circulate", "Opt_3": "enable", "Opt_4": "declare", "Answer": "declare", "Opt_1_def": "to do what someone asks or orders", "Opt_2_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_3_def": "to make something or someone able to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to state"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Blair will need to ____ the Americans that Europeans will no longer permit Saddam to play games with the inspectors.", "Opt_1": "confront", "Opt_2": "base", "Opt_3": "persuade", "Opt_4": "judge", "Answer": "persuade", "Opt_1_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)", "Opt_2_def": "to use as a way of doing or deciding something", "Opt_3_def": "to try and make someone do something or agree to something", "Opt_4_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Curiously absent from the report is any ____ of the type of action that the State would have taken against the diverse sources of TCE.", "Opt_1": "represent", "Opt_2": "admit", "Opt_3": "mention", "Opt_4": "add", "Answer": "mention", "Opt_1_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_2_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_3_def": "to say; state", "Opt_4_def": "to include; to give or say extra"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Our focus is to motivate each student to achieve their full potential as they ____ for success in our five cornerstones of Academic Excellence.", "Opt_1": "seek", "Opt_2": "afford", "Opt_3": "strive", "Opt_4": "suffer", "Answer": "strive", "Opt_1_def": "to look for or want", "Opt_2_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_3_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_4_def": "to experience something bad or painful"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government is bringing in a new law to ____ food manufacturers to label their products as high-, low- or medium fat.", "Opt_1": "claim", "Opt_2": "oppose", "Opt_3": "overlap", "Opt_4": "require", "Answer": "require", "Opt_1_def": "to state to be true", "Opt_2_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_3_def": "to have in common; to cover part of", "Opt_4_def": "to need"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Consequently, the percentages will not ____ to 100% because many students were neutral on the questions in the survey.", "Opt_1": "quantity", "Opt_2": "doubt", "Opt_3": "ignorance", "Opt_4": "sum", "Answer": "sum", "Opt_1_def": "amount", "Opt_2_def": "a feeling of uncertainty (whether something is true)", "Opt_3_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_4_def": "an amount of money, total"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The school can recommend that parents communicate by email, but they cannot ____ on it.", "Opt_1": "transfer", "Opt_2": "view", "Opt_3": "demonstrate", "Opt_4": "insist", "Answer": "insist", "Opt_1_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_2_def": "to have an opinion", "Opt_3_def": "to show", "Opt_4_def": "to demand; to make a strong claim"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The ____ from Frankfurt to Oberursel is about 12 kilometers.", "Opt_1": "influence", "Opt_2": "battle", "Opt_3": "fragment", "Opt_4": "distance", "Answer": "distance", "Opt_1_def": "effect", "Opt_2_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_3_def": "part of something", "Opt_4_def": "how far it is from one place to another"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "An analysis of the historical causes of slavery is beyond the ____ of this course.", "Opt_1": "scope", "Opt_2": "victory", "Opt_3": "phrase", "Opt_4": "battle", "Answer": "scope", "Opt_1_def": "extent, range", "Opt_2_def": "win", "Opt_3_def": "one achieves best success through constantly applied pressure.", "Opt_4_def": "fight, part of a war"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The ____ of a soccer player in one week is many times higher than what most people earn in a whole year.", "Opt_1": "level", "Opt_2": "facilities", "Opt_3": "point", "Opt_4": "income", "Answer": "income", "Opt_1_def": "standard; layer; amount", "Opt_2_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_3_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_4_def": "money earned"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The main ____ of the school is the teaching of science and mathematics.", "Opt_1": "attention", "Opt_2": "series", "Opt_3": "method", "Opt_4": "province", "Answer": "province", "Opt_1_def": "focus", "Opt_2_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "area (of interest)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There's no need to give an ____ answer, Two or three short sentences will be enough.", "Opt_1": "imaginary", "Opt_2": "moderate", "Opt_3": "elaborate", "Opt_4": "essential", "Answer": "elaborate", "Opt_1_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; not very strong; not extreme", "Opt_3_def": "detailed; complex", "Opt_4_def": "very important"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "When a district court heard the case, it found the policy did not ____ students' free-speech rights.", "Opt_1": "retire", "Opt_2": "trust", "Opt_3": "exchange", "Opt_4": "violate", "Answer": "violate", "Opt_1_def": "to stop working", "Opt_2_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_3_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or break"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There was also no ____ record of an attempt to measure the relationship between individual differences in facial shape.", "Opt_1": "subjective", "Opt_2": "apparent", "Opt_3": "minor", "Opt_4": "initial", "Answer": "apparent", "Opt_1_def": "based on personal opinion or feeling", "Opt_2_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_3_def": "small, not important", "Opt_4_def": "starting, first"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "He's having a lot of problems learning English, ____ in grammar and spelling.", "Opt_1": "conversely", "Opt_2": "especially", "Opt_3": "extremely", "Opt_4": "namely", "Answer": "especially", "Opt_1_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_2_def": "particularly", "Opt_3_def": "very", "Opt_4_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It must have been about this time that Stalin took the most extraordinary decision of his ____ in order to assure his political survival.", "Opt_1": "expert", "Opt_2": "career", "Opt_3": "transition", "Opt_4": "belief", "Answer": "career", "Opt_1_def": "someone with great knowledge in a particular field", "Opt_2_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_3_def": "a move from one (place, time, etc.) to another", "Opt_4_def": "what you think; what you believe in"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "They ____ decided for various reasons that his age was not a drawback, that perhaps (at that time and for that position) it was an advantage.", "Opt_1": "thereby", "Opt_2": "simply", "Opt_3": "moreover", "Opt_4": "fairly", "Answer": "simply", "Opt_1_def": "by doing this", "Opt_2_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_3_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_4_def": "quite, somewhat"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Many people say that he does not ____ the qualities to become president of this country.", "Opt_1": "exclude", "Opt_2": "obtain", "Opt_3": "possess", "Opt_4": "prefer", "Answer": "possess", "Opt_1_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_2_def": "to get", "Opt_3_def": "to have or own", "Opt_4_def": "to like better"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "This document explains why it is important to ____ a community assessment during a sustainability project.", "Opt_1": "raise", "Opt_2": "decline", "Opt_3": "conduct", "Opt_4": "seek", "Answer": "conduct", "Opt_1_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_2_def": "to go down or get worse", "Opt_3_def": "to do or perform; to behave", "Opt_4_def": "to look for or want"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government failed to understand why the people were so unhappy with its policies, and ____ was voted out at the next election.", "Opt_1": "thus", "Opt_2": "indeed", "Opt_3": "universally", "Opt_4": "generally", "Answer": "thus", "Opt_1_def": "so", "Opt_2_def": "used in confirmation or emphasis; really", "Opt_3_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_4_def": "usually"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The death of Princess Diana was an ____ that shocked the whole world.", "Opt_1": "result", "Opt_2": "event", "Opt_3": "challenge", "Opt_4": "exponent", "Answer": "event", "Opt_1_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_2_def": "a happening", "Opt_3_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_4_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ function of the committee is to recommend a plan for future development.", "Opt_1": "relevant", "Opt_2": "major", "Opt_3": "main", "Opt_4": "appropriate", "Answer": "main", "Opt_1_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_2_def": "important, large", "Opt_3_def": "most important", "Opt_4_def": "right (for the occasion; suitable"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The Birth Control Pill may have modernized society, but it tore ____ a nation and created many social problems that did not exist before its invention.", "Opt_1": "apart", "Opt_2": "annual", "Opt_3": "broad", "Opt_4": "sane", "Answer": "apart", "Opt_1_def": "not together, separate", "Opt_2_def": "yearly", "Opt_3_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_4_def": "reasonable; not mad"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "A records check was unable to verify his claim that he possessed a ____ license.", "Opt_1": "prime", "Opt_2": "ambitious", "Opt_3": "valid", "Opt_4": "extraordinary", "Answer": "valid", "Opt_1_def": "most important", "Opt_2_def": "having high goals (especially in a career; challenging", "Opt_3_def": "correct", "Opt_4_def": "very unusual"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Please remember to ____ any rented vehicle before driving it and note any scratches or other damage to the vehicle on the rental form.", "Opt_1": "advance", "Opt_2": "inspect", "Opt_3": "appoint", "Opt_4": "reward", "Answer": "inspect", "Opt_1_def": "to go or move forward; to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_4_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The main reason for not responding to terrorism was not an external issue, but an internal one: the government failed to ____ its duties.", "Opt_1": "amend", "Opt_2": "consult", "Opt_3": "present", "Opt_4": "fulfill", "Answer": "fulfill", "Opt_1_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_2_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_3_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_4_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "After the war, Turing joined the National Physical Laboratory to work on the ____ of a computer.", "Opt_1": "account", "Opt_2": "design", "Opt_3": "surface", "Opt_4": "support", "Answer": "design", "Opt_1_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_2_def": "planning (drawing)", "Opt_3_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_4_def": "help"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The value of books would certainly ____ if they could simply be produced and reproduced in cyberspace at an extremely minimal cost.", "Opt_1": "occur", "Opt_2": "separate", "Opt_3": "shrink", "Opt_4": "degenerate", "Answer": "degenerate", "Opt_1_def": "to happen; take place", "Opt_2_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_4_def": "to get worse"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Even the older ____ does have some command of the Indonesian language.", "Opt_1": "lack", "Opt_2": "disaster", "Opt_3": "generation", "Opt_4": "figure", "Answer": "generation", "Opt_1_def": "absence of a thing", "Opt_2_def": "a huge problem or failure", "Opt_3_def": "group of people all born around the same time", "Opt_4_def": "number"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "This page contains a sample outline to be used as a ____ for the creation of a strong outline.", "Opt_1": "defect", "Opt_2": "guide", "Opt_3": "committee", "Opt_4": "hierarchy", "Answer": "guide", "Opt_1_def": "problem; mistake", "Opt_2_def": "someone or something that helps people (to understand or find their way)", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue", "Opt_4_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The demand for oil is likely to increase as people in developing countries such as China and India ____ cars.", "Opt_1": "accelerate", "Opt_2": "acquire", "Opt_3": "behave", "Opt_4": "emphasize", "Answer": "acquire", "Opt_1_def": "to get or make faster", "Opt_2_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_3_def": "to act or do things in a certain way", "Opt_4_def": "to stress, to say something strongly"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The work involves some lifting and bending, and ____ requires travel away from the normal duty station.", "Opt_1": "namely", "Opt_2": "universally", "Opt_3": "occasionally", "Opt_4": "eventually", "Answer": "occasionally", "Opt_1_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_2_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_3_def": "indicating they only occasionally asked questions.", "Opt_4_def": "in the end"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "We would probably become engaged in discussions from which we could not extract ourselves and ____ our freedom of action would be limited.", "Opt_1": "indirectly", "Opt_2": "therefore", "Opt_3": "dramatically", "Opt_4": "respectively", "Answer": "therefore", "Opt_1_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_2_def": "so, as a result", "Opt_3_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_4_def": "an expression used to refer to two things, one after the other"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It's not ____ asking him. He doesn't know enough about computers.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "If the student refuses to leave after being requested to do so, the instructor may summon University Police to ____ the student.", "Opt_1": "restore", "Opt_2": "expand", "Opt_3": "offend", "Opt_4": "remove", "Answer": "remove", "Opt_1_def": "to put back, create again", "Opt_2_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_3_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_4_def": "to take away"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Game reasoning is simply moral reasoning that occurs in the context of competitive sports, and ____ elsewhere as well.", "Opt_1": "perhaps", "Opt_2": "furthermore", "Opt_3": "moreover", "Opt_4": "dramatically", "Answer": "perhaps", "Opt_1_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_2_def": "also, in addition", "Opt_3_def": "also .., what is more ..", "Opt_4_def": "very strongly, significantly"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The school is in a very good ____ to the north of Frankfurt and on the edge of the beautiful Taunus forest.", "Opt_1": "location", "Opt_2": "interpretation", "Opt_3": "resource", "Opt_4": "speed", "Answer": "location", "Opt_1_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_2_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_3_def": "a source of information or material", "Opt_4_def": "how quickly something moves or changes"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The practice test materials will become available just ____ to the class.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "prior", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "before", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "You are making ____ progress in learning English.", "Opt_1": "equivalent", "Opt_2": "willing", "Opt_3": "external", "Opt_4": "steady", "Answer": "steady", "Opt_1_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_2_def": "happy or prepared to do something", "Opt_3_def": "outside", "Opt_4_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The profession of social work is based on the values of service, social and economic justice, dignity and ____ of the person, importance of human relationships, and integrity and competence in practice.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "worth", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A ____ to save life has recently been waged at the Kwangtze Hospital in Shanghai. This ____ is not yet over, but it has already caused a great sensation.", "Opt_1": "battle", "Opt_2": "symptom", "Opt_3": "supply", "Opt_4": "potential", "Answer": "battle", "Opt_1_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_2_def": "sign (often of a disease or other problem)", "Opt_3_def": "provision, store", "Opt_4_def": "good possibility"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some people claim that the growth of the internet has been to the ____ of students' ability and willingness to read.", "Opt_1": "detriment", "Opt_2": "contrast", "Opt_3": "majority", "Opt_4": "advantage", "Answer": "detriment", "Opt_1_def": "disadvantage", "Opt_2_def": "difference", "Opt_3_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_4_def": "benefit"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Chapter 6 gives a sketchy and rather incomplete ____ of molecular genetics.", "Opt_1": "criterion", "Opt_2": "account", "Opt_3": "atmosphere", "Opt_4": "occasion", "Answer": "account", "Opt_1_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_2_def": "a written or spoken report of a happening", "Opt_3_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_4_def": "time (opportunity)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Some young people ____ their lives when they become addicted to drugs..", "Opt_1": "reinforce", "Opt_2": "destroy", "Opt_3": "migrate", "Opt_4": "depart", "Answer": "destroy", "Opt_1_def": "to make something stronger", "Opt_2_def": "to break or damage completely", "Opt_3_def": "to go to another place", "Opt_4_def": "to leave; to be different from"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The best remedy is to change the nutrient solution every week ____ of every two weeks.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "His lungs were filled in an instant with a great ____ of driven air which he could not expel.", "Opt_1": "advantage", "Opt_2": "fragment", "Opt_3": "volume", "Opt_4": "cycle", "Answer": "volume", "Opt_1_def": "benefit", "Opt_2_def": "part of something", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "a complete series of events or processes"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "In tomorrow's TV ____ the government will declare its intention to reduce taxes during its time in office.", "Opt_1": "add", "Opt_2": "entitle", "Opt_3": "judge", "Opt_4": "broadcast", "Answer": "broadcast", "Opt_1_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_2_def": "to give the right to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to give an opinion about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "By signing the pledge, students make a personal commitment to ____ energy and help contribute to Yale's goal of reducing greenhouse gases by 10 percent.", "Opt_1": "conserve", "Opt_2": "dedicate", "Opt_3": "include", "Opt_4": "append", "Answer": "conserve", "Opt_1_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_2_def": "to devote (time and attention)", "Opt_3_def": "to put in; to have in", "Opt_4_def": "to add to the end (of a piece of writing)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "An aspect of this war is the ____ of a large anti-war movement in the US.", "Opt_1": "counsel", "Opt_2": "asset", "Opt_3": "attribute", "Opt_4": "rise", "Answer": "rise", "Opt_1_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_2_def": "advantage", "Opt_3_def": "characteristic; property", "Opt_4_def": "to go up"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "A geography graduate produces a piece of geographic research and analyzes, synthesizes, and evaluates the ____ information.", "Opt_1": "poor", "Opt_2": "relevant", "Opt_3": "independent", "Opt_4": "technical", "Answer": "relevant", "Opt_1_def": "bad, unsatisfactory", "Opt_2_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_3_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_4_def": "to do with machines or the way things work"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Certain questions must be answered before it becomes politically feasible, or even necessary, to ____ cellular phones.", "Opt_1": "accept", "Opt_2": "ban", "Opt_3": "suppose", "Opt_4": "afford", "Answer": "ban", "Opt_1_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_2_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_3_def": "to think, imagine", "Opt_4_def": "to be able to pay for something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The priests of this ____ did not give their answers by inspiration, but occupied themselves chiefly with the interpretation of dreams", "Opt_1": "contrary", "Opt_2": "institution", "Opt_3": "source", "Opt_4": "motive", "Answer": "institution", "Opt_1_def": "opposite", "Opt_2_def": "a large organization; an important system or custom", "Opt_3_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_4_def": "reason"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "At no point in our deliberations are numbers employed in a way that would trigger an automatic decision to offer or ____ admission.", "Opt_1": "deny", "Opt_2": "adapt", "Opt_3": "address", "Opt_4": "confirm", "Answer": "deny", "Opt_1_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_3_def": "to give attention to (an issue)", "Opt_4_def": "to agree that something is correct"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If there is a group that we have paid no ____ to, it's old women, says Hawkes.", "Opt_1": "attention", "Opt_2": "gap", "Opt_3": "event", "Opt_4": "period", "Answer": "attention", "Opt_1_def": "focus", "Opt_2_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_3_def": "a happening", "Opt_4_def": "a length of time (e.g. a lesson)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It was agriculture that allowed civilizations to ____ growth.", "Opt_1": "sustain", "Opt_2": "transfer", "Opt_3": "appreciate", "Opt_4": "indicate", "Answer": "sustain", "Opt_1_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_2_def": "to move to a different place or job", "Opt_3_def": "to understand (the value of someone or something)", "Opt_4_def": "to show or convey"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The lesson plans contained an incomplete description of learners, their background and ____ knowledge.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "except", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "but (not)", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The failures of the national soccer and tennis teams ____ all that is wrong with British sport.", "Opt_1": "embody", "Opt_2": "adapt", "Opt_3": "absorb", "Opt_4": "undertake", "Answer": "embody", "Opt_1_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_3_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_4_def": "to (plan to) do"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Government agencies and aid organizations often failed to ____ people in affected communities about aid distribution and reconstruction.", "Opt_1": "consult", "Opt_2": "depart", "Opt_3": "adapt", "Opt_4": "suppose", "Answer": "consult", "Opt_1_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_2_def": "to leave; to be different from", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_4_def": "to think, imagine"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Campuses must publish an annual security report detailing statistics ____ crimes committed on campus and at affiliated locations.", "Opt_1": "beyond", "Opt_2": "worth", "Opt_3": "regarding", "Opt_4": "against", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "further than: past", "Opt_2_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_3_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_4_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "An enormous amount of research has been conducted into the ____ by which young children learn to speak.", "Opt_1": "function", "Opt_2": "location", "Opt_3": "sphere", "Opt_4": "mechanism", "Answer": "mechanism", "Opt_1_def": "job or role", "Opt_2_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_3_def": "area of interest", "Opt_4_def": "procedure, process"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Dogs keep dying: Too many owners ____ unaware of toxic dog food.", "Opt_1": "remain", "Opt_2": "undertake", "Opt_3": "formulate", "Opt_4": "require", "Answer": "remain", "Opt_1_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_2_def": "to (plan to) do", "Opt_3_def": "to express", "Opt_4_def": "to need"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "You will need to ____ the images and present them as a narrative or the story of destruction in New Orleans after Katrina.", "Opt_1": "demonstrate", "Opt_2": "presume", "Opt_3": "maintain", "Opt_4": "annotate", "Answer": "annotate", "Opt_1_def": "to show", "Opt_2_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_3_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_4_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Asia is our closest ____ and essentially I feel that we need more understanding and exchange culturally to make sense of where we all are'.", "Opt_1": "strategy", "Opt_2": "region", "Opt_3": "shortage", "Opt_4": "statement", "Answer": "region", "Opt_1_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_2_def": "part of a place", "Opt_3_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_4_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Van Haarlem also said the team had found a large ____ of what may have been a ceramic baboon statue.", "Opt_1": "duty", "Opt_2": "criterion", "Opt_3": "profession", "Opt_4": "fragment", "Answer": "fragment", "Opt_1_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do", "Opt_2_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_3_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_4_def": "part of something"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This is an artificial example to ____ how the method works. In real data, the sequences are much longer, and there's no mistaking a match.", "Opt_1": "interfere", "Opt_2": "drain", "Opt_3": "illustrate", "Opt_4": "produce", "Answer": "illustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to prevent; to harm", "Opt_2_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_3_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_4_def": "to make or create"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "I ____ you to spend part of the summer vacation reading. This is an excellent way to improve your English.", "Opt_1": "suspend", "Opt_2": "multiply", "Opt_3": "disperse", "Opt_4": "encourage", "Answer": "encourage", "Opt_1_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_2_def": "to increase greatly", "Opt_3_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_4_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The police were unable to ____ the demonstrators from the town square.", "Opt_1": "expel", "Opt_2": "manipulate", "Opt_3": "rotate", "Opt_4": "cover", "Answer": "expel", "Opt_1_def": "to drive or push out", "Opt_2_def": "to (use and) change", "Opt_3_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_4_def": "to do; to complete"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Students and non-students alike can be criminally charged if they don't comply with police orders to ____ from riot or crowd situations.", "Opt_1": "suggest", "Opt_2": "justify", "Opt_3": "disperse", "Opt_4": "suspect", "Answer": "disperse", "Opt_1_def": "to say an idea; to recommend", "Opt_2_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_4_def": "to believe"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The university advises female students to follow their instinct whether it is safe to ____ a ride home from a man they have just met.", "Opt_1": "trigger", "Opt_2": "accept", "Opt_3": "postpone", "Opt_4": "intervene", "Answer": "accept", "Opt_1_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_2_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_3_def": "to put back in time", "Opt_4_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The OCC provides counsel and ____ advice in the development of policy, procedures, and strategy related to the management and operation of the UC Riverside campus.", "Opt_1": "legal", "Opt_2": "diverse", "Opt_3": "current", "Opt_4": "dense", "Answer": "legal", "Opt_1_def": "acceptable in law (to do with the law)", "Opt_2_def": "many and different", "Opt_3_def": "happening now", "Opt_4_def": "thick; full; detailed"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Computers are a much more ____ way of storing and retrieving large amounts of data than keeping it on paper in huge cabinets.", "Opt_1": "apparent", "Opt_2": "effective", "Opt_3": "imaginary", "Opt_4": "efficient", "Answer": "efficient", "Opt_1_def": "clear; obvious", "Opt_2_def": "good, working well", "Opt_3_def": "not real; from the imagination", "Opt_4_def": "working quickly and easily"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "I ____ the idea of having a school uniform. I think it would cause a lot of unnecessary problems.", "Opt_1": "oppose", "Opt_2": "separate", "Opt_3": "contact", "Opt_4": "dismiss", "Answer": "oppose", "Opt_1_def": "to be against or fight against something", "Opt_2_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_3_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_4_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The current program review ____ is not very valuable because there are neither rewards nor punishments for outcomes.", "Opt_1": "liberty", "Opt_2": "process", "Opt_3": "impact", "Opt_4": "conflict", "Answer": "process", "Opt_1_def": "freedom", "Opt_2_def": "a series of steps", "Opt_3_def": "effect", "Opt_4_def": "problem, struggle or battle"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The use of gender- ____ language may seem unnecessary to some writers, but the consistent use of masculine pronouns leaves the impression that women could not be among the group to which the writer is referring.", "Opt_1": "available", "Opt_2": "neutral", "Opt_3": "average", "Opt_4": "diverse", "Answer": "neutral", "Opt_1_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_2_def": "neither for nor against; neither positive nor negative", "Opt_3_def": "ordinary, typical", "Opt_4_def": "many and different"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This situation is certain to improve over the next few years, given the ____ of research now being done on the effectiveness of complementary medicine.", "Opt_1": "directions", "Opt_2": "quantity", "Opt_3": "programme", "Opt_4": "credit", "Answer": "quantity", "Opt_1_def": "instructions", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_4_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Due to the money ____ in schools, teachers are now being charged a high fee for training.", "Opt_1": "shortage", "Opt_2": "category", "Opt_3": "interior", "Opt_4": "power", "Answer": "shortage", "Opt_1_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_2_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_3_def": "inside", "Opt_4_def": "the right or authority to do something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ of the aid money that has been allocated to Afghanistan has been wasted.", "Opt_1": "goal", "Opt_2": "diagnosis", "Opt_3": "bulk", "Opt_4": "experiment", "Answer": "bulk", "Opt_1_def": "aim or intention", "Opt_2_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_3_def": "majority; largest part", "Opt_4_def": "test"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Van Haarlem also said the team had found a large ____ of what may have been a ceramic baboon statue.", "Opt_1": "district", "Opt_2": "perspective", "Opt_3": "fragment", "Opt_4": "contrast", "Answer": "fragment", "Opt_1_def": "region of a city", "Opt_2_def": "view; opinion; way of thinking", "Opt_3_def": "part of something", "Opt_4_def": "difference"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "In western countries most people ____ at the age of 65.", "Opt_1": "praise", "Opt_2": "connect", "Opt_3": "employ", "Opt_4": "retire", "Answer": "retire", "Opt_1_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_3_def": "to give a job to someone; to use", "Opt_4_def": "to stop working"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "I ____ that at least 80% of the students will pass with the top grade.", "Opt_1": "estimate", "Opt_2": "correlate", "Opt_3": "dictate", "Opt_4": "supervise", "Answer": "estimate", "Opt_1_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_2_def": "to have a close connection", "Opt_3_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_4_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "It is difficult to change an unhealthy eating ____ that has developed from a very early age.", "Opt_1": "challenge", "Opt_2": "habit", "Opt_3": "objection", "Opt_4": "trace", "Answer": "habit", "Opt_1_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_2_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_3_def": "a statement of disagreement or disapproval", "Opt_4_def": "sign; indication; evidence"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Our teacher showed us an ____ of The Simpsons in ESL class yesterday.", "Opt_1": "episode", "Opt_2": "research", "Opt_3": "penalty", "Opt_4": "attitude", "Answer": "episode", "Opt_1_def": "period of time", "Opt_2_def": "study; the finding of information", "Opt_3_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_4_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "If we want to maintain support for an open and ____ economy, our programs need to become as flexible and adaptable as the economy itself.", "Opt_1": "abnormal", "Opt_2": "dynamic", "Opt_3": "essential", "Opt_4": "ancient", "Answer": "dynamic", "Opt_1_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_2_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_3_def": "very important", "Opt_4_def": "very old"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "My parents will ____ that I did this work without help.", "Opt_1": "train", "Opt_2": "verify", "Opt_3": "suspend", "Opt_4": "retain", "Answer": "verify", "Opt_1_def": "to teach someone how to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_3_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_4_def": "to keep"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Students who are awarded an International Student Scholarship must ____ the following requirements each semester in order to continue receiving this award.", "Opt_1": "reveal", "Opt_2": "ruin", "Opt_3": "fulfill", "Opt_4": "receive", "Answer": "fulfill", "Opt_1_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_3_def": "to do; to carry out (completely)", "Opt_4_def": "to get"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Metals ____ when heated.", "Opt_1": "absorb", "Opt_2": "imply", "Opt_3": "conform", "Opt_4": "expand", "Answer": "expand", "Opt_1_def": "to take in; to take up", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_3_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_4_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Sufficient progress has been made with regard to drinking water to place within reach the target of halving the ____ of the population without access to safe drinking water between 1990 and 2015.", "Opt_1": "command", "Opt_2": "effect", "Opt_3": "proportion", "Opt_4": "duty", "Answer": "proportion", "Opt_1_def": "control", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "amount; number; percentage", "Opt_4_def": "responsibility, or job that you are required to do"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government decided to ____ their plans after thousands of people demonstrated on the streets of the capital city.", "Opt_1": "interact", "Opt_2": "coordinate", "Opt_3": "modify", "Opt_4": "expose", "Answer": "modify", "Opt_1_def": "to react, to affect and be affected", "Opt_2_def": "to bring things or people together so that they work well", "Opt_3_def": "to change", "Opt_4_def": "to uncover, reveal"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Most scientists are more interested in the ____ of winning the Nobel Prize than the money they get for doing so.", "Opt_1": "battle", "Opt_2": "target", "Opt_3": "volume", "Opt_4": "prestige", "Answer": "prestige", "Opt_1_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_2_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "fame and respect"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The school chose not to ____ news of the teacher's accident.", "Opt_1": "hesitate", "Opt_2": "broadcast", "Opt_3": "collaborate", "Opt_4": "explore", "Answer": "broadcast", "Opt_1_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_3_def": "to work together", "Opt_4_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The result will be an immediate and substantial ____ in the number of faculty of color who are tenured at this institution.", "Opt_1": "perceive", "Opt_2": "violate", "Opt_3": "increase", "Opt_4": "respect", "Answer": "increase", "Opt_1_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_4_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Experts believe that the problem will ____ until the government takes it more seriously.", "Opt_1": "restrict", "Opt_2": "assemble", "Opt_3": "recur", "Opt_4": "consult", "Answer": "recur", "Opt_1_def": "to limit", "Opt_2_def": "to get, put or bring together", "Opt_3_def": "to happen again", "Opt_4_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Recent research shows ____ against African American mothers of any class who don't work.", "Opt_1": "bias", "Opt_2": "friction", "Opt_3": "portion", "Opt_4": "environment", "Answer": "bias", "Opt_1_def": "favouring one more than another, prejudice", "Opt_2_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups", "Opt_3_def": "part, amount", "Opt_4_def": "the world around us"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Germany is no longer a ____ society. Between 15 - 20% of its population is non-German.", "Opt_1": "arbitrary", "Opt_2": "homogeneous", "Opt_3": "rigid", "Opt_4": "necessary", "Answer": "homogeneous", "Opt_1_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_2_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_3_def": "strict, unbending", "Opt_4_def": "needed; very important"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "University staff will notice the new look and feel because information will be presented on Web pages ____ of on bulletin boards.", "Opt_1": "due", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Shonekan was unable to ____ Nigeria's ever-growing economic problems.", "Opt_1": "reverse", "Opt_2": "consent", "Opt_3": "motivate", "Opt_4": "embody", "Answer": "reverse", "Opt_1_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_2_def": "to agree", "Opt_3_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something", "Opt_4_def": "to be a good example of .."}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The final event of the day was an ____ tour of the Single Sisters House, which is in the process of restoration.", "Opt_1": "initial", "Opt_2": "visual", "Opt_3": "optional", "Opt_4": "enormous", "Answer": "optional", "Opt_1_def": "starting, first", "Opt_2_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_3_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_4_def": "very big"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "She expects to complete her education and ____ her doctorate between 2012 and 2015, after which she intends to become a mathematics professor.", "Opt_1": "estimate", "Opt_2": "earn", "Opt_3": "integrate", "Opt_4": "organize", "Answer": "earn", "Opt_1_def": "to make an intelligent guess", "Opt_2_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_3_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_4_def": "to put into (its proper) place"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Please ____ me a seat at the back of the school bus.", "Opt_1": "continue", "Opt_2": "reserve", "Opt_3": "affect", "Opt_4": "occupy", "Answer": "reserve", "Opt_1_def": "to carry on, not stop", "Opt_2_def": "to keep", "Opt_3_def": "to have an influence on", "Opt_4_def": "to up space or time"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "What would you ____ the patient so that the injury not recur?", "Opt_1": "disperse", "Opt_2": "demonstrate", "Opt_3": "belong", "Opt_4": "advise", "Answer": "advise", "Opt_1_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_2_def": "to show", "Opt_3_def": "to be part of something or owned by someone", "Opt_4_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Most companies guarantee to ____ machines, like refrigerators or computers, if they break down in the first year.", "Opt_1": "stipulate", "Opt_2": "harm", "Opt_3": "review", "Opt_4": "replace", "Answer": "replace", "Opt_1_def": "to require", "Opt_2_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_3_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_4_def": "to put in or take the place of .."}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The technology to ____ carbon monoxide into liquid fuel has been around a long time.", "Opt_1": "harm", "Opt_2": "achieve", "Opt_3": "protest", "Opt_4": "convert", "Answer": "convert", "Opt_1_def": "to damage or injure", "Opt_2_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_3_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_4_def": "to change from one thing to another"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The union leaders promised to ____ for a longer lunch break for the employees.", "Opt_1": "earn", "Opt_2": "eliminate", "Opt_3": "strive", "Opt_4": "mention", "Answer": "strive", "Opt_1_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)", "Opt_2_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_3_def": "to work or try hard", "Opt_4_def": "to say; state"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "A ____ problem for most western societies is how to integrate immigrants with different cultures and religious beliefs.", "Opt_1": "major", "Opt_2": "instant", "Opt_3": "aware", "Opt_4": "severe", "Answer": "major", "Opt_1_def": "important, large", "Opt_2_def": "immediate", "Opt_3_def": "knowing", "Opt_4_def": "serious, harsh"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Frankfurt International School has invited the local ____ to its Open Day.", "Opt_1": "apparatus", "Opt_2": "truth", "Opt_3": "community", "Opt_4": "sum", "Answer": "community", "Opt_1_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_2_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_3_def": "a group of people", "Opt_4_def": "an amount of money, total"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The new teacher has been away quite often this year. I ____ that she will not be given a permanent job at the school.", "Opt_1": "speculate", "Opt_2": "tend", "Opt_3": "yield", "Opt_4": "force", "Answer": "speculate", "Opt_1_def": "to think and talk about (often future events)", "Opt_2_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_3_def": "to produce", "Opt_4_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Individuals with communication disorders have ____ difficulty making themselves clearly understood.", "Opt_1": "latter", "Opt_2": "enormous", "Opt_3": "superficial", "Opt_4": "considerable", "Answer": "considerable", "Opt_1_def": "the second of two things mentioned", "Opt_2_def": "very big", "Opt_3_def": "done quickly and without enough thought; not thorough; trivial", "Opt_4_def": "very big; very much"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "His advice was to ____ short-term temptation when investing in stocks.", "Opt_1": "resist", "Opt_2": "cease", "Opt_3": "prevent", "Opt_4": "decrease", "Answer": "resist", "Opt_1_def": "to fight against", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to stop from doing or happening", "Opt_4_def": "to get smaller, to go down"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "There will be a ____ of Chinese art, literature, instruments, calligraphy, and fashion from noon to 4 p.m. on Wednesday, February 27.", "Opt_1": "display", "Opt_2": "policy", "Opt_3": "plenty", "Opt_4": "remedy", "Answer": "display", "Opt_1_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_2_def": "formal rules", "Opt_3_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_4_def": "cure (often for an illness)"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "On December 4, 1955, the ____ decision was made to boycott the bus system until they were treated with courtesy and black drivers could be hired.", "Opt_1": "pure", "Opt_2": "anonymous", "Opt_3": "obvious", "Opt_4": "global", "Answer": "anonymous", "Opt_1_def": "complete, 100%", "Opt_2_def": "having no name or known author", "Opt_3_def": "clear, evident", "Opt_4_def": "world"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The government neither intends to ____ on the event nor even to admit that it actually happened.", "Opt_1": "comment", "Opt_2": "career", "Opt_3": "opportunity", "Opt_4": "aspect", "Answer": "comment", "Opt_1_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_2_def": "a long-term job", "Opt_3_def": "chance", "Opt_4_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain."}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "McCready said she could not ____ anything in the New York Daily News story about her.", "Opt_1": "connect", "Opt_2": "manage", "Opt_3": "distinguish", "Opt_4": "refute", "Answer": "refute", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed in doing something; to be able to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to make clear the differences between two things", "Opt_4_def": "to prove to be untrue; to deny"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The Euro has taken on a dimension far greater than its ____ substance.", "Opt_1": "minor", "Opt_2": "economic", "Opt_3": "severe", "Opt_4": "prime", "Answer": "economic", "Opt_1_def": "small, not important", "Opt_2_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_3_def": "serious, harsh", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The company director decided to ____ his son as the new head of marketing.", "Opt_1": "strain", "Opt_2": "suspect", "Opt_3": "install", "Opt_4": "consult", "Answer": "install", "Opt_1_def": "to put under stress or make difficult", "Opt_2_def": "to believe", "Opt_3_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_4_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Oddly, however, the book is almost completely ____ in fictional representations of invalids.", "Opt_1": "complete", "Opt_2": "deficient", "Opt_3": "economic", "Opt_4": "secure", "Answer": "deficient", "Opt_1_def": "full or finished", "Opt_2_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_3_def": "financial; to do with money", "Opt_4_def": "safe"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The strategy failed to persuade workers themselves to ____ domestic service as anything other than a temporary transition.", "Opt_1": "clarify", "Opt_2": "consider", "Opt_3": "introduce", "Opt_4": "donate", "Answer": "consider", "Opt_1_def": "to make something clear, explain", "Opt_2_def": "to think", "Opt_3_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_4_def": "to give (usually money)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The ____ in the price of oil is set to accelerate in future years due to increased demand in countries such as China and India.", "Opt_1": "record", "Opt_2": "rise", "Opt_3": "interior", "Opt_4": "detail", "Answer": "rise", "Opt_1_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_2_def": "to go up", "Opt_3_def": "inside", "Opt_4_def": "a small piece of information"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Be sure to ask if this is a good time to ____ the professor for your specific need.", "Opt_1": "approach", "Opt_2": "violate", "Opt_3": "evolve", "Opt_4": "conceal", "Answer": "approach", "Opt_1_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_2_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_3_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_4_def": "to hide"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Germany had to ____ a harsh peace treaty after being defeated in the first world war.", "Opt_1": "accept", "Opt_2": "facilitate", "Opt_3": "adhere", "Opt_4": "harm", "Answer": "accept", "Opt_1_def": "to agree (to have)", "Opt_2_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_3_def": "to keep to; to follow", "Opt_4_def": "to damage or injure"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "In order to match you up with the most ____ roommate we can, please fill out the Housing Intake Questionaire.", "Opt_1": "compatible", "Opt_2": "positive", "Opt_3": "ideal", "Opt_4": "main", "Answer": "compatible", "Opt_1_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_2_def": "good; optimistic", "Opt_3_def": "best, optimal", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Its plot centers on how the ____ between two female \"mates\" is almost broken because both love the same man.", "Opt_1": "effect", "Opt_2": "bond", "Opt_3": "advantage", "Opt_4": "exercise", "Answer": "bond", "Opt_1_def": "result", "Opt_2_def": "link; tie", "Opt_3_def": "benefit", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of work, activity"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The ____ was unclear. It had been hand-drawn and then copied using weak ink.", "Opt_1": "manner", "Opt_2": "ignorance", "Opt_3": "diagram", "Opt_4": "rate", "Answer": "diagram", "Opt_1_def": "way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_3_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_4_def": "quantity; proportion; speed"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "You will ____ your chances of success if you are absent from school so often.", "Opt_1": "lessen", "Opt_2": "respect", "Opt_3": "dismiss", "Opt_4": "evaluate", "Answer": "lessen", "Opt_1_def": "to reduce", "Opt_2_def": "to think positively about someone; to tolerate or avoid interfering with something", "Opt_3_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_4_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Here you can ____ areas for investment of resources to advance the University in its health sciences, education, research, service and outreach missions.", "Opt_1": "recommend", "Opt_2": "justify", "Opt_3": "ensure", "Opt_4": "donate", "Answer": "recommend", "Opt_1_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_2_def": "to give a reason for doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to make sure (of)", "Opt_4_def": "to give (usually money)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Headaches and sleeplessness are ____ problems of a student who has just moved here from a different country.", "Opt_1": "evident", "Opt_2": "inevitable", "Opt_3": "preliminary", "Opt_4": "typical", "Answer": "typical", "Opt_1_def": "clear", "Opt_2_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_3_def": "first; initial", "Opt_4_def": "usual"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We will also tell you how the ____ to take if you decide to use email as an official means of communication.", "Opt_1": "industry", "Opt_2": "precaution", "Opt_3": "task", "Opt_4": "decision", "Answer": "precaution", "Opt_1_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_2_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_3_def": "job", "Opt_4_def": "intention to do something, choice"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Teachers should not ____ the discussion or act as the last word on a student's artwork.", "Opt_1": "highlight", "Opt_2": "dominate", "Opt_3": "admit", "Opt_4": "supervise", "Answer": "dominate", "Opt_1_def": "to show (the important features of something)", "Opt_2_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_3_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_4_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "So, what's the ____ of all this hindsight and what do we stand to gain from it?", "Opt_1": "controversy", "Opt_2": "point", "Opt_3": "responsibility", "Opt_4": "fee", "Answer": "point", "Opt_1_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_2_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_3_def": "job, duty to do something", "Opt_4_def": "money for a service (e.g. a baking service)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "These poems ____ a good grade, but because you gave them in late I have to give you a 0.", "Opt_1": "terminate", "Opt_2": "deduce", "Opt_3": "qualify", "Opt_4": "deserve", "Answer": "deserve", "Opt_1_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_4_def": "to have the right to something"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Because southern Christian churches benefited financially from slave-based plantations they did nothing to ____ the practice of slavery.", "Opt_1": "ruin", "Opt_2": "halt", "Opt_3": "encourage", "Opt_4": "afford", "Answer": "halt", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_2_def": "to stop", "Opt_3_def": "to move someone to do something by positive talk; support or help", "Opt_4_def": "to be able to pay for something"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "What steps do I take to draw a random sample of a ____ audience in my county to do a needs assessment or gather baseline data?", "Opt_1": "target", "Opt_2": "quality", "Opt_3": "operation", "Opt_4": "atmosphere", "Answer": "target", "Opt_1_def": "aim, goal", "Opt_2_def": "worth or value", "Opt_3_def": "procedure; happening; process", "Opt_4_def": "mood among people or groups"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Errors in grammar and vocabulary may, but do not always, ____ with comprehensibility.", "Opt_1": "modify", "Opt_2": "embody", "Opt_3": "confine", "Opt_4": "interfere", "Answer": "interfere", "Opt_1_def": "to change", "Opt_2_def": "to be a good example of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to limit", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent; to harm"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Medical scientists have shown it to be a ____ that lying in bed is the best way to heal a bad back.", "Opt_1": "site", "Opt_2": "conflict", "Opt_3": "apparatus", "Opt_4": "fallacy", "Answer": "fallacy", "Opt_1_def": "place", "Opt_2_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_3_def": "equipment; things you need to do a job", "Opt_4_def": "mistake; false belief"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The course will develop the knowledge base ____ the finance of community education programs.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "beneath", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "regarding", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "below", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "You are recommended to ____ quickly throughout the classroom to make sure that everyone understands the task, then return to help students who are having difficulty.", "Opt_1": "prepare", "Opt_2": "amend", "Opt_3": "circulate", "Opt_4": "compile", "Answer": "circulate", "Opt_1_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)", "Opt_2_def": "to change (usually to improve something)", "Opt_3_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_4_def": "to put together (often in a list"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "We wanted to ____ a long-term relationship that could grow with our company.", "Opt_1": "protest", "Opt_2": "establish", "Opt_3": "receive", "Opt_4": "deduce", "Answer": "establish", "Opt_1_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_2_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_3_def": "to get", "Opt_4_def": "to come to a conclusion about someone or something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The government does not plan to admit any more immigrants unless they can prove that their life is in danger in their ____ country.", "Opt_1": "defend", "Opt_2": "own", "Opt_3": "analyze", "Opt_4": "violate", "Answer": "own", "Opt_1_def": "to give reasons for", "Opt_2_def": "to have or possess", "Opt_3_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or break"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "You will ____ many difficulties but if you persist in your efforts, you will succeed.", "Opt_1": "promote", "Opt_2": "develop", "Opt_3": "expand", "Opt_4": "encounter", "Answer": "encounter", "Opt_1_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_2_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_3_def": "to get bigger; to move into new areas", "Opt_4_def": "to meet or experience"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The latest ____ of his bad behaviour was to lock another student in the toilet.", "Opt_1": "diagram", "Opt_2": "instance", "Opt_3": "attitude", "Opt_4": "point", "Answer": "instance", "Opt_1_def": "a type of picture or chart", "Opt_2_def": "example", "Opt_3_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_4_def": "purpose; reason; value"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Good teachers must engage their students as they find them, as they ____ themselves, walking in the door.", "Opt_1": "present", "Opt_2": "deserve", "Opt_3": "attempt", "Opt_4": "fear", "Answer": "present", "Opt_1_def": "to give or show; to make a presentation", "Opt_2_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_3_def": "to try", "Opt_4_def": "to be concerned or frightened about"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We had disagreed strongly over politics before, and while these arguments did not strain our friendship in the least, I wished to ____ potential conflict.", "Opt_1": "avoid", "Opt_2": "prevail", "Opt_3": "reveal", "Opt_4": "require", "Answer": "avoid", "Opt_1_def": "to not do something or go somewhere", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_3_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_4_def": "to need"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Very ____ water does not conduct electricity well compared with contaminated water because it contains no inorganic ions.", "Opt_1": "credible", "Opt_2": "averse", "Opt_3": "infinite", "Opt_4": "pure", "Answer": "pure", "Opt_1_def": "believable", "Opt_2_def": "against", "Opt_3_def": "without an end", "Opt_4_def": "complete, 100%"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "There is a growing ____ to use the cell phone as the primary phone, without any need for landlines.", "Opt_1": "innovation", "Opt_2": "purpose", "Opt_3": "insight", "Opt_4": "trend", "Answer": "trend", "Opt_1_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_2_def": "reason, goal", "Opt_3_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_4_def": "pattern of continuing behaviour"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Oddly, however, the book is almost completely ____ in fictional representations of invalids.", "Opt_1": "deficient", "Opt_2": "current", "Opt_3": "available", "Opt_4": "infinite", "Answer": "deficient", "Opt_1_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_2_def": "happening now", "Opt_3_def": "can be had (bought or obtained)", "Opt_4_def": "without an end"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The writer clearly did not perform the experiment, but gave us what her very great ____ expected would happen.", "Opt_1": "method", "Opt_2": "ignorance", "Opt_3": "intention", "Opt_4": "course", "Answer": "ignorance", "Opt_1_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_2_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_3_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_4_def": "a subject or period of study"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "No program has developed an approach that is ____ successful in working with the types of problems that we try to solve.", "Opt_1": "indirectly", "Opt_2": "largely", "Opt_3": "universally", "Opt_4": "simply", "Answer": "universally", "Opt_1_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_2_def": "mostly", "Opt_3_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_4_def": "completely; just; only"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Yet there were conflicts there too, and the immigrants did not ____ easily and completely into Israeli culture.", "Opt_1": "derive", "Opt_2": "condemn", "Opt_3": "exaggerate", "Opt_4": "assimilate", "Answer": "assimilate", "Opt_1_def": "to come from or get from", "Opt_2_def": "to express strong disapproval", "Opt_3_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is", "Opt_4_def": "to take in"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Photoshop provides you with techniques used to ____ the quality of graphics and photographs.", "Opt_1": "release", "Opt_2": "supervise", "Opt_3": "shrink", "Opt_4": "adjust", "Answer": "adjust", "Opt_1_def": "to let go or let out", "Opt_2_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "During various stages of a planning process, ____ and crosscheck the goals and objectives in the plan elements so that they do not contradict one another.", "Opt_1": "acknowledge", "Opt_2": "review", "Opt_3": "descend", "Opt_4": "exaggerate", "Answer": "review", "Opt_1_def": "to agree with; admit to; give credit to", "Opt_2_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_3_def": "to go down", "Opt_4_def": "to \"overstate\" the truth; to say something is bigger or better than it really is"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Dairy farmers have led the latest in a long series of protests by agricultural associations, ____ the record high prices for farm products.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "instead", "Opt_3": "despite", "Opt_4": "prior", "Answer": "despite", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_3_def": "although", "Opt_4_def": "before"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A lasting peace in Iraq will remain but a ____ hope.", "Opt_1": "temporary", "Opt_2": "faint", "Opt_3": "technical", "Opt_4": "necessary", "Answer": "faint", "Opt_1_def": "for a short or limited time", "Opt_2_def": "not strong", "Opt_3_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_4_def": "needed; very important"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Prices have risen by ____ 4% over the last 10 years.", "Opt_1": "universally", "Opt_2": "conversely", "Opt_3": "approximately", "Opt_4": "virtually", "Answer": "approximately", "Opt_1_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_2_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_3_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_4_def": "almost"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This page contains a sample ____ to be used as a guide for the creation of a strong ____.", "Opt_1": "outline", "Opt_2": "propensity", "Opt_3": "controversy", "Opt_4": "agent", "Answer": "outline", "Opt_1_def": "plan or summary", "Opt_2_def": "tendency; desire", "Opt_3_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_4_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The students worked together to ____ a poster about the dangers of nuclear power.", "Opt_1": "produce", "Opt_2": "conceal", "Opt_3": "approach", "Opt_4": "combine", "Answer": "produce", "Opt_1_def": "to make or create", "Opt_2_def": "to hide", "Opt_3_def": "to near; to get closer", "Opt_4_def": "to put or go together"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Mild pain and inflammation can often ____ an otherwise rewarding day of skiing.", "Opt_1": "ruin", "Opt_2": "prevail", "Opt_3": "shrink", "Opt_4": "restore", "Answer": "ruin", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or damage", "Opt_2_def": "to succeed; to overcome", "Opt_3_def": "to get smaller", "Opt_4_def": "to put back, create again"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "My father's company is going to facilitate our move to Germany by employing an ____ to help us find a house here.", "Opt_1": "agent", "Opt_2": "pattern", "Opt_3": "section", "Opt_4": "finance", "Answer": "agent", "Opt_1_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_2_def": "clear and consistent behaviour", "Opt_3_def": "part", "Opt_4_def": "to do with money and payment"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "To include an ____ on your website, you will need to insert the ____ into your webpage using an HTML editor.", "Opt_1": "image", "Opt_2": "entity", "Opt_3": "attitude", "Opt_4": "result", "Answer": "image", "Opt_1_def": "picture", "Opt_2_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_3_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)", "Opt_4_def": "outcome, effect"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If you decide to apply, you will need to ____ a full application including: cover sheet, goals and plan letter, and project statement.", "Opt_1": "compile", "Opt_2": "discern", "Opt_3": "spread", "Opt_4": "accumulate", "Answer": "compile", "Opt_1_def": "to put together (often in a list", "Opt_2_def": "to see; to perceive", "Opt_3_def": "to move (over a wider area)", "Opt_4_def": "to grow; to gather together"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Imagine a bridge that can self - diagnose cracks or a building able to ____ its own health after an earthquake without any help from humans.", "Opt_1": "fare", "Opt_2": "drain", "Opt_3": "violate", "Opt_4": "assess", "Answer": "assess", "Opt_1_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_2_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_4_def": "to judge or test"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The sorting of students into ____ ability and achievement groups is nearly as old as universal compulsory education in the United States.", "Opt_1": "final", "Opt_2": "homogeneous", "Opt_3": "steady", "Opt_4": "original", "Answer": "homogeneous", "Opt_1_def": "last", "Opt_2_def": "having the same qualities or characteristics", "Opt_3_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_4_def": "the first of its kind"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Bulgaria is to face a severe ____ of teachers within the next three years, education experts declared.", "Opt_1": "compensation", "Opt_2": "object", "Opt_3": "shortage", "Opt_4": "effect", "Answer": "shortage", "Opt_1_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_2_def": "thing", "Opt_3_def": "lack; an amount which is less than needed", "Opt_4_def": "result"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "In the mid-1930s, when she was back at Vogue as fashion editor, Nast declined to ____ her to editor of the magazine, once again because of the morality issue.", "Opt_1": "promote", "Opt_2": "forego", "Opt_3": "attain", "Opt_4": "denote", "Answer": "promote", "Opt_1_def": "to encourage; to raise to a higher position in a job", "Opt_2_def": "to do without; to give up", "Opt_3_def": "to get, achieve", "Opt_4_def": "to mean; to be a sign of"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "It is to the government's credit that they refused to ____ in the invasion of Iraq.", "Opt_1": "increase", "Opt_2": "participate", "Opt_3": "replace", "Opt_4": "mention", "Answer": "participate", "Opt_1_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_2_def": "to take part", "Opt_3_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_4_def": "to say; state"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The department may admit students of superior promise but ____ preparation, provided that such students correct their deficiencies.", "Opt_1": "deficient", "Opt_2": "vital", "Opt_3": "identical", "Opt_4": "flexible", "Answer": "deficient", "Opt_1_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_2_def": "very important", "Opt_3_def": "exactly the same", "Opt_4_def": "can be changed or bent"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "We will not be able to ____ additional copies of the guide until the printers strike is ended.", "Opt_1": "master", "Opt_2": "deserve", "Opt_3": "distribute", "Opt_4": "settle", "Answer": "distribute", "Opt_1_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_2_def": "to have the right to something", "Opt_3_def": "to give out", "Opt_4_def": "to solve a problem or dispute"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Although his letter did not stipulate Atlanta as the ____ of the new school, the Educational Commission quickly decided the matter.", "Opt_1": "location", "Opt_2": "interval", "Opt_3": "tradition", "Opt_4": "debate", "Answer": "location", "Opt_1_def": "place, where something or someone is", "Opt_2_def": "a period of time", "Opt_3_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_4_def": "formal discussion"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "These results ____ that substantial numbers of students attending the school are not attaining minimum levels of literacy and mathematical competency.", "Opt_1": "obtain", "Opt_2": "trigger", "Opt_3": "react", "Opt_4": "indicate", "Answer": "indicate", "Opt_1_def": "to get", "Opt_2_def": "to (cause to) start", "Opt_3_def": "to respond", "Opt_4_def": "to show or convey"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "When you employ an electrician to do a job in your house, you hope they will be ____ at their job.", "Opt_1": "infinite", "Opt_2": "credible", "Opt_3": "averse", "Opt_4": "competent", "Answer": "competent", "Opt_1_def": "without an end", "Opt_2_def": "believable", "Opt_3_def": "against", "Opt_4_def": "good at something (often a job)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We believe that individuals who respect and support a ____ global society will prosper as leaders in schools, universities, businesses, and human service.", "Opt_1": "fortunate", "Opt_2": "urgent", "Opt_3": "diverse", "Opt_4": "extraordinary", "Answer": "diverse", "Opt_1_def": "lucky", "Opt_2_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_3_def": "many and different", "Opt_4_def": "very unusual"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Your low grades will ____ you of the chance of taking part in sports trips.", "Opt_1": "impress", "Opt_2": "deviate", "Opt_3": "adapt", "Opt_4": "deprive", "Answer": "deprive", "Opt_1_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_2_def": "to be different", "Opt_3_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_4_def": "to take away (the opportunity)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "But you are forgetting one thing, gentlemen of the law, you are driving a horse to water but you cannot ____ him to drink.", "Opt_1": "protect", "Opt_2": "compel", "Opt_3": "culminate", "Opt_4": "reform", "Answer": "compel", "Opt_1_def": "to keep something out of danger", "Opt_2_def": "to force or make happen", "Opt_3_def": "to end", "Opt_4_def": "to change and improve"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "London is becoming more and more unpleasant. The government needs to drastically ____ the penalty for dropping litter.", "Opt_1": "regulate", "Opt_2": "increase", "Opt_3": "occupy", "Opt_4": "donate", "Answer": "increase", "Opt_1_def": "to control", "Opt_2_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_3_def": "to up space or time", "Opt_4_def": "to give (usually money)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The Committee is concerned that children dropping out of school during the compulsory stage of ____ have insufficient alternative ____al opportunities.", "Opt_1": "conflict", "Opt_2": "habit", "Opt_3": "education", "Opt_4": "contrary", "Answer": "education", "Opt_1_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_2_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_3_def": "schooling", "Opt_4_def": "opposite"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "If you want to be successful in business, it is certainly an ____ to be able to speak more than one language.", "Opt_1": "format", "Opt_2": "impulse", "Opt_3": "advantage", "Opt_4": "committee", "Answer": "advantage", "Opt_1_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_2_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_3_def": "benefit", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Many large companies are trying to ____ operations in China. This is the key market of the future.", "Opt_1": "assist", "Opt_2": "establish", "Opt_3": "block", "Opt_4": "attach", "Answer": "establish", "Opt_1_def": "to help", "Opt_2_def": "to begin or set up", "Opt_3_def": "to not allow; to stop or prevent", "Opt_4_def": "to put together with"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The ____ of social work is based on the values of service, social and economic justice, dignity and worth of the person, importance of human relationships, and integrity and competence in practice.", "Opt_1": "profession", "Opt_2": "industry", "Opt_3": "advantage", "Opt_4": "design", "Answer": "profession", "Opt_1_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_2_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_3_def": "benefit", "Opt_4_def": "planning (drawing)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "To learn a new word, it often helps to make an ____ of it in your mind.", "Opt_1": "image", "Opt_2": "drawback", "Opt_3": "site", "Opt_4": "insight", "Answer": "image", "Opt_1_def": "picture", "Opt_2_def": "disadvantage, problem", "Opt_3_def": "place", "Opt_4_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Please ____ the Timetable for class times and locations.", "Opt_1": "deliver", "Opt_2": "collapse", "Opt_3": "consult", "Opt_4": "earn", "Answer": "consult", "Opt_1_def": "to provide (often by bringing to people)", "Opt_2_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail", "Opt_3_def": "to get the advice of someone ( often an expert)", "Opt_4_def": "to get money or another reward (usually by working for it)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The ____ between the workers and the management improved when flexible working time was introduced.", "Opt_1": "atmosphere", "Opt_2": "benefit", "Opt_3": "ignorance", "Opt_4": "situation", "Answer": "atmosphere", "Opt_1_def": "mood among people or groups", "Opt_2_def": "advantage", "Opt_3_def": "lack of knowledge", "Opt_4_def": "circumstances"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "There are various ways that you can improve your English. Probably the best is to do ____ of reading.", "Opt_1": "display", "Opt_2": "plenty", "Opt_3": "effect", "Opt_4": "friction", "Answer": "plenty", "Opt_1_def": "a show, demonstration, illustration", "Opt_2_def": "many, lots of", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The teachers are not ____ in favour of the school's plan to introduce flexible working times.", "Opt_1": "somewhat", "Opt_2": "universally", "Opt_3": "simultaneously", "Opt_4": "perhaps", "Answer": "universally", "Opt_1_def": "quite, rather", "Opt_2_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_3_def": "at the same time", "Opt_4_def": "maybe, possibly"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Although the mountain was not steep, the raging river could not ____ with sufficient rapidity to prevent its overflowing its banks.", "Opt_1": "descend", "Opt_2": "adopt", "Opt_3": "contribute", "Opt_4": "include", "Answer": "descend", "Opt_1_def": "to go down", "Opt_2_def": "to take in; to start", "Opt_3_def": "to give (for example: money, help or ideas); to play a part in", "Opt_4_def": "to put in; to have in"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "My overall ____ of him since he joined the class is very positive.", "Opt_1": "vary", "Opt_2": "compensation", "Opt_3": "opinion", "Opt_4": "controversy", "Answer": "opinion", "Opt_1_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_2_def": "money (or some other reward) given to someone who has suffered a loss or injustice", "Opt_3_def": "view; what you think about someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Financial ____ is the term we use to describe a variety of funds available to help students and their families finance the cost of a Berry College education.", "Opt_1": "impulse", "Opt_2": "aid", "Opt_3": "result", "Opt_4": "committee", "Answer": "aid", "Opt_1_def": "reason or motivation to do something", "Opt_2_def": "help (often financial help)", "Opt_3_def": "outcome, effect", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Dogs keep dying: Too many owners ____ unaware of toxic dog food.", "Opt_1": "remain", "Opt_2": "publish", "Opt_3": "intervene", "Opt_4": "identify", "Answer": "remain", "Opt_1_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_2_def": "to make available in paper or online form", "Opt_3_def": "to step into a situation (in order to stop or change something)", "Opt_4_def": "to know or say who or what something is"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Your first piece of writing was very good, but the ____ ones have been of much lower quality.", "Opt_1": "actual", "Opt_2": "equivalent", "Opt_3": "eligible", "Opt_4": "subsequent", "Answer": "subsequent", "Opt_1_def": "real", "Opt_2_def": "equal to; the same as", "Opt_3_def": "being entitled or qualified to do something", "Opt_4_def": "next, following"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is predicted that Off-campus study programs will shrink ____ to the problematic financial situation.", "Opt_1": "worth", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "besides", "Answer": "due", "Opt_1_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "in addition to; as well as"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The government has introduced a ____ language course for immigrants who cannot speak English.", "Opt_1": "scarce", "Opt_2": "compulsory", "Opt_3": "infinite", "Opt_4": "obvious", "Answer": "compulsory", "Opt_1_def": "rare, not abundant", "Opt_2_def": "required, must be done", "Opt_3_def": "without an end", "Opt_4_def": "clear, evident"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The results are not at all satisfactory, and considerable discontent has arisen ____ the Indians on account of the issues that are being made.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "besides", "Opt_3": "worth", "Opt_4": "among", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_3_def": "useful; having a point or purpose", "Opt_4_def": "in, between"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Doing so will probably ____ a strong negative response from the group's normal readership.", "Opt_1": "notice", "Opt_2": "provoke", "Opt_3": "prohibit", "Opt_4": "cease", "Answer": "provoke", "Opt_1_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_2_def": "to cause to happen", "Opt_3_def": "to ban, disallow", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "With winter weather comes the need to ____ your home, automobile and family to deal with the colder temperatures.", "Opt_1": "integrate", "Opt_2": "analyze", "Opt_3": "owe", "Opt_4": "prepare", "Answer": "prepare", "Opt_1_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_2_def": "to look at something in detail in order to understand it", "Opt_3_def": "to be in someone's debt (especially money)", "Opt_4_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Doctors these days are not averse to advising patients about poor lifestyle choices such as smoking or ____ of exercise.", "Opt_1": "command", "Opt_2": "figure", "Opt_3": "background", "Opt_4": "lack", "Answer": "lack", "Opt_1_def": "control", "Opt_2_def": "number", "Opt_3_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_4_def": "absence of a thing"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Why are most intellectuals and education theorists so ____ to allowing ordinary parents to choose which school their children will attend?", "Opt_1": "hostile", "Opt_2": "valid", "Opt_3": "initial", "Opt_4": "common", "Answer": "hostile", "Opt_1_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_2_def": "correct", "Opt_3_def": "starting, first", "Opt_4_def": "often seen or happening"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "It is an ____ for a politician to be able to give a clear but concise statement of what he or she believes in.", "Opt_1": "attack", "Opt_2": "advantage", "Opt_3": "decade", "Opt_4": "comment", "Answer": "advantage", "Opt_1_def": "to criticize; to attempt to harm or damage", "Opt_2_def": "benefit", "Opt_3_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_4_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government was unable to ____ that it was considering invading North Korea.", "Opt_1": "deny", "Opt_2": "conserve", "Opt_3": "pursue", "Opt_4": "reject", "Answer": "deny", "Opt_1_def": "to refuse ( responsibility for doing or saying something); to say that something is not correct", "Opt_2_def": "to preserve; to not use", "Opt_3_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_4_def": "to refuse"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Among male baboons, dominance ____ is independent of maternal ____, and changes markedly with age; males reach their highest ____ between 8 and 10 years of age.", "Opt_1": "rank", "Opt_2": "format", "Opt_3": "profession", "Opt_4": "habit", "Answer": "rank", "Opt_1_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_2_def": "appearance, layout, way of presenting", "Opt_3_def": "job; occupation", "Opt_4_def": "something you do regularly"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "You are advised to undertake serious language study both before and during the course of the program but ____ language study is not a criterion for selection.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "prior", "Opt_3": "beyond", "Opt_4": "instead", "Answer": "prior", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "before", "Opt_3_def": "further than: past", "Opt_4_def": "in place of; rather than"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A major defect in the proposal is that there is not ____ money to finance it.", "Opt_1": "immense", "Opt_2": "competent", "Opt_3": "sufficient", "Opt_4": "invisible", "Answer": "sufficient", "Opt_1_def": "very large", "Opt_2_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_3_def": "enough", "Opt_4_def": "cannot be seen"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The school offers Latin but there is no demand for the subject ____ teachers and parents.", "Opt_1": "instead", "Opt_2": "among", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "among", "Opt_1_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_2_def": "in, between", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The professor meets with each student for a half-hour private tutorial ____ three times during the semester.", "Opt_1": "approximately", "Opt_2": "naturally", "Opt_3": "eventually", "Opt_4": "overly", "Answer": "approximately", "Opt_1_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_2_def": "of course, obviously", "Opt_3_def": "in the end", "Opt_4_def": "too"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Financial aid is the ____ we use to describe a variety of funds available to help students and their families finance the cost of a Berry College education.", "Opt_1": "industry", "Opt_2": "minimum", "Opt_3": "term", "Opt_4": "scale", "Answer": "term", "Opt_1_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_2_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_3_def": "a word or expression", "Opt_4_def": "extent"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "For the purposes of this study, then, increasing the testing strength did not ____ more accurate results.", "Opt_1": "undergo", "Opt_2": "yield", "Opt_3": "supervise", "Opt_4": "comprise", "Answer": "yield", "Opt_1_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_2_def": "to produce", "Opt_3_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to be made up of; to include"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The government plans to offer ____ parenting classes for young, unemployed couples.", "Opt_1": "optional", "Opt_2": "odd", "Opt_3": "logical", "Opt_4": "main", "Answer": "optional", "Opt_1_def": "not necessary or compulsory; can do it if you want", "Opt_2_def": "strange, unusual", "Opt_3_def": "making sense", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The developing world does not ____ many industrial wastes; thus it has had little opportunity to develop proper disposal techniques.", "Opt_1": "subsidize", "Opt_2": "create", "Opt_3": "resist", "Opt_4": "amend", "Answer": "create", "Opt_1_def": "to support financially", "Opt_2_def": "to make; to use your imagination to make something new", "Opt_3_def": "to fight against", "Opt_4_def": "to change (usually to improve something)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "He was unable to ____ his plans for an industrial area, which he purchased from the Israel Land Administration.", "Opt_1": "implement", "Opt_2": "consist", "Opt_3": "discover", "Opt_4": "evaluate", "Answer": "implement", "Opt_1_def": "to start or put into practice (something that has been planned)", "Opt_2_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it", "Opt_3_def": "to find out; to find something for the first time (esp. land or scientific knowledge)", "Opt_4_def": "to decide on the value, quality or importance of something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government's new proposals are too vague. They need to be ____ about what they expect people to do.", "Opt_1": "serious", "Opt_2": "unique", "Opt_3": "entire", "Opt_4": "precise", "Answer": "precise", "Opt_1_def": "severe, large", "Opt_2_def": "single, unusual, one of a kind", "Opt_3_def": "whole, all", "Opt_4_def": "exact"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Students gain professional experience before graduation so that they enter the job market with a ____ advantage.", "Opt_1": "secure", "Opt_2": "rapid", "Opt_3": "distinct", "Opt_4": "frequent", "Answer": "distinct", "Opt_1_def": "safe", "Opt_2_def": "quick", "Opt_3_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_4_def": "often"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Most language teachers use ____ aids in the classroom, such as pictures or objects.", "Opt_1": "effective", "Opt_2": "visual", "Opt_3": "subtle", "Opt_4": "commercial", "Answer": "visual", "Opt_1_def": "good, working well", "Opt_2_def": "to do with sight and seeing", "Opt_3_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_4_def": "to do with business"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Students should not ____ others of cheating unless there is clear evidence.", "Opt_1": "accuse", "Opt_2": "dominate", "Opt_3": "remove", "Opt_4": "utilize", "Answer": "accuse", "Opt_1_def": "to blame", "Opt_2_def": "to be much better, to play the most important part", "Opt_3_def": "to take away", "Opt_4_def": "to use"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "It can take as much as a ____ or more of hard study in a foreign language to become as fluent as a native speaker of that language.", "Opt_1": "comment", "Opt_2": "decade", "Opt_3": "surface", "Opt_4": "generation", "Answer": "decade", "Opt_1_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_2_def": "a period of ten years", "Opt_3_def": "the outside layer of an object", "Opt_4_def": "group of people all born around the same time"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The links between ____ price declines and food prices are not easy to discern.", "Opt_1": "commodity", "Opt_2": "vary", "Opt_3": "instance", "Opt_4": "pressure", "Answer": "commodity", "Opt_1_def": "a product; something you can buy", "Opt_2_def": "to change or be different", "Opt_3_def": "example", "Opt_4_def": "force; influence; stress"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Lebanese security officials said the soldiers' tank drove over a mine, but Israel said it could not ____ that.", "Opt_1": "invest", "Opt_2": "offer", "Opt_3": "confirm", "Opt_4": "request", "Answer": "confirm", "Opt_1_def": "to put money into something", "Opt_2_def": "to ask if someone would like something (e.g. food or help)", "Opt_3_def": "to agree that something is correct", "Opt_4_def": "to ask politely"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "She finally was able to ____ her true ability with an excellent score in the end of year test.", "Opt_1": "survive", "Opt_2": "reveal", "Opt_3": "exclude", "Opt_4": "advocate", "Answer": "reveal", "Opt_1_def": "to not die", "Opt_2_def": "to show or uncover", "Opt_3_def": "to leave out; opposite of include", "Opt_4_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "There are ____ reasons for his academic success. The most important one is his willingness to work very hard.", "Opt_1": "mental", "Opt_2": "diverse", "Opt_3": "independent", "Opt_4": "visual", "Answer": "diverse", "Opt_1_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_2_def": "many and different", "Opt_3_def": "free; not needing anyone or anything else", "Opt_4_def": "to do with sight and seeing"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "It may well be that the two towers on Boynton Hill will soon become a familiar ____ of innovation to educators and students across the country.", "Opt_1": "agent", "Opt_2": "entity", "Opt_3": "diagnosis", "Opt_4": "symbol", "Answer": "symbol", "Opt_1_def": "a person who is paid to do a job for someone", "Opt_2_def": "thing; body; organization", "Opt_3_def": "assessment of a situation (particularly of a problem)", "Opt_4_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "There is no ____ of him passing the course. He has been away too many times this year.", "Opt_1": "prospect", "Opt_2": "procedure", "Opt_3": "section", "Opt_4": "detriment", "Answer": "prospect", "Opt_1_def": "chance, likelihood", "Opt_2_def": "the way to do something", "Opt_3_def": "part", "Opt_4_def": "disadvantage"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The private ____ offers many opportunities for students with a history or liberal arts background.", "Opt_1": "sector", "Opt_2": "credit", "Opt_3": "majority", "Opt_4": "decision", "Answer": "sector", "Opt_1_def": "part; area", "Opt_2_def": "gained on completing a course of study; praise", "Opt_3_def": "more than 50%", "Opt_4_def": "intention to do something, choice"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Al Gore ____ did not deserve the Nobel peace prize. On a personal level, he has not reduced his own carbon dioxide emissions.", "Opt_1": "absolutely", "Opt_2": "recently", "Opt_3": "simply", "Opt_4": "largely", "Answer": "absolutely", "Opt_1_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_2_def": "in the near past", "Opt_3_def": "completely; just; only", "Opt_4_def": "mostly"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The student was hardly active with the ____ and did not attempt to contribute.", "Opt_1": "scheme", "Opt_2": "support", "Opt_3": "experiment", "Opt_4": "magnitude", "Answer": "experiment", "Opt_1_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_2_def": "help", "Opt_3_def": "test", "Opt_4_def": "size; amount"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He is an American citizen which obviously puts him in a different ____ from the kinds of individuals that the president has suggested might be suitable.", "Opt_1": "potential", "Opt_2": "remedy", "Opt_3": "category", "Opt_4": "contrary", "Answer": "category", "Opt_1_def": "good possibility", "Opt_2_def": "cure (often for an illness)", "Opt_3_def": "group of similar items", "Opt_4_def": "opposite"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "As large and difficult as it was, it was not the ____ problem. The deeper problem was conceptual.", "Opt_1": "local", "Opt_2": "chief", "Opt_3": "steady", "Opt_4": "valuable", "Answer": "chief", "Opt_1_def": "in the area where you live or work", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm", "Opt_4_def": "worth a lot of money; important"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The purpose of this tutorial is to give you an idea of the ____ of events leading up to graduation.", "Opt_1": "programme", "Opt_2": "sequence", "Opt_3": "intention", "Opt_4": "precaution", "Answer": "sequence", "Opt_1_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_2_def": "the order in which things are arranged or happen", "Opt_3_def": "plan, aim", "Opt_4_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "To accommodate the great power ____ now rapidly occurring in Asia, the United States needs vigorous preparation by its executive branch and Congress.", "Opt_1": "shift", "Opt_2": "dimension", "Opt_3": "ability", "Opt_4": "symbol", "Answer": "shift", "Opt_1_def": "change", "Opt_2_def": "importance; amount", "Opt_3_def": "ableness to do something; a skill for doing something well", "Opt_4_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "For my next step I would propose to the students certain distinctions that might at first glance seem to be completely ____ or valueless.", "Opt_1": "reasonable", "Opt_2": "arbitrary", "Opt_3": "sound", "Opt_4": "inherent", "Answer": "arbitrary", "Opt_1_def": "acceptable, quite good", "Opt_2_def": "not planned or thought-out; not considering the wishes of others", "Opt_3_def": "good; strong", "Opt_4_def": "part of; a fundamental characteristic of"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Dr. Carpenter told the jury that Hinckley was unable to ____ reality from fiction.", "Opt_1": "extend", "Opt_2": "regret", "Opt_3": "ban", "Opt_4": "separate", "Answer": "separate", "Opt_1_def": "to make longer in time or space", "Opt_2_def": "to feel sorry (for doing or saying something)", "Opt_3_def": "to prohibit or forbid", "Opt_4_def": "to pull or put apart"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You are making ____ progress in learning English.", "Opt_1": "prompt", "Opt_2": "complex", "Opt_3": "hostile", "Opt_4": "steady", "Answer": "steady", "Opt_1_def": "quick; on or before time", "Opt_2_def": "difficult, complicated", "Opt_3_def": "unfriendly; dangerous; strongly opposed to", "Opt_4_def": "gradual; without interruptions; firm"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The proposal is unlikely to ____ the tension between them.", "Opt_1": "lessen", "Opt_2": "prefer", "Opt_3": "omit", "Opt_4": "alter", "Answer": "lessen", "Opt_1_def": "to reduce", "Opt_2_def": "to like better", "Opt_3_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_4_def": "to change"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The UCLA Philharmonia, however, is bridging the ____ between North and South campuses with two concerts that combine symphony with science and history.", "Opt_1": "fragment", "Opt_2": "consequence", "Opt_3": "treatment", "Opt_4": "gap", "Answer": "gap", "Opt_1_def": "part of something", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_4_def": "space, opening or time between"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The police were not ____ of controlling the street demonstrations. They had to call in the army.", "Opt_1": "uniform", "Opt_2": "deficient", "Opt_3": "capable", "Opt_4": "prime", "Answer": "capable", "Opt_1_def": "having the same qualities", "Opt_2_def": "poor, lacking in quantity or quality", "Opt_3_def": "able", "Opt_4_def": "most important"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The University of Washington has agreed to ____ a class-action lawsuit over faculty salaries.", "Opt_1": "settle", "Opt_2": "connect", "Opt_3": "permit", "Opt_4": "emerge", "Answer": "settle", "Opt_1_def": "to solve a problem or dispute", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or put together", "Opt_3_def": "to allow", "Opt_4_def": "to come out; to become known"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Abnormal results do not diagnose birth defects, they just ____ that follow-up tests are necessary for further clarification.", "Opt_1": "circulate", "Opt_2": "eliminate", "Opt_3": "suggest", "Opt_4": "frustrate", "Answer": "suggest", "Opt_1_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_2_def": "to dispose of", "Opt_3_def": "to say an idea; to recommend", "Opt_4_def": "to stop or prevent"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "The percentage of online adults who say they ____ ever or never search for health information has dropped to 39 percent.", "Opt_1": "hardly", "Opt_2": "barely", "Opt_3": "thereby", "Opt_4": "gradually", "Answer": "hardly", "Opt_1_def": "not very much", "Opt_2_def": "not very much; hardly", "Opt_3_def": "by doing this", "Opt_4_def": "slowly; steadily"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Testing personnel will not ____ any tester who is cheating, but will complete the Testing Incident Report and submit to the supervisor.", "Opt_1": "illuminate", "Opt_2": "accomplish", "Opt_3": "arise", "Opt_4": "confront", "Answer": "confront", "Opt_1_def": "to show clearly; to light up", "Opt_2_def": "to do or achieve", "Opt_3_def": "to happen", "Opt_4_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Some of the key personal resources that you will draw from include your own academic background, teaching style, life experience, and ____ experience.", "Opt_1": "technical", "Opt_2": "relevant", "Opt_3": "faint", "Opt_4": "suitable", "Answer": "technical", "Opt_1_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_2_def": "connected to the topic of discussion or consideration", "Opt_3_def": "not strong", "Opt_4_def": "good for a particular job or purpose"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government is thinking of extending compulsory ____ by two years.", "Opt_1": "precaution", "Opt_2": "service", "Opt_3": "component", "Opt_4": "education", "Answer": "education", "Opt_1_def": "something done to avoid danger, harm or problems", "Opt_2_def": "work done for others; help", "Opt_3_def": "part of; an element of", "Opt_4_def": "schooling"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The most important ____ for selecting a research topic is that you are really interested in it!", "Opt_1": "controversy", "Opt_2": "criterion", "Opt_3": "outcome", "Opt_4": "state", "Answer": "criterion", "Opt_1_def": "an issue on which their are strong and conflicting opinions", "Opt_2_def": "a way to judge the value or importance of something", "Opt_3_def": "result", "Opt_4_def": "condition, situation"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "We engage outside ____ to work on particular matters when considerations such as cost and highly specialized subject matter make it appropriate to do so.", "Opt_1": "counsel", "Opt_2": "mechanism", "Opt_3": "concept", "Opt_4": "attitude", "Answer": "counsel", "Opt_1_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_2_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_3_def": "idea; understanding", "Opt_4_def": "what someone thinks about something (and how their behaviour is influenced by their thinking)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The results represented an unusual ____ of old and modern practices.", "Opt_1": "mixture", "Opt_2": "outcome", "Opt_3": "method", "Opt_4": "extract", "Answer": "mixture", "Opt_1_def": "combination", "Opt_2_def": "result", "Opt_3_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to remove; to take out and use"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "And ____ failing to reduce unemployment, the government has also increased the tax on food.", "Opt_1": "except", "Opt_2": "despite", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "besides", "Opt_1_def": "but (not)", "Opt_2_def": "although", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Please ____ me a seat at the back of the school bus.", "Opt_1": "contact", "Opt_2": "investigate", "Opt_3": "reserve", "Opt_4": "install", "Answer": "reserve", "Opt_1_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_2_def": "to find out what has happened or why something has happened", "Opt_3_def": "to keep", "Opt_4_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We further believe that the general quality of student writing will not ____ unless we as a department are willing to state explicitly the standards we require.", "Opt_1": "improve", "Opt_2": "exploit", "Opt_3": "disperse", "Opt_4": "appeal", "Answer": "improve", "Opt_1_def": "to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to use (sometimes in a negative way)", "Opt_3_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_4_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Your group will need to investigate the ____ characteristics of your city (such as mountains and lakes).", "Opt_1": "previous", "Opt_2": "adequate", "Opt_3": "physical", "Opt_4": "willing", "Answer": "physical", "Opt_1_def": "the one before", "Opt_2_def": "good enough; ok", "Opt_3_def": "of the body", "Opt_4_def": "happy or prepared to do something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Recent research has investigated the traits that may ____ the development of drug addiction.", "Opt_1": "underlie", "Opt_2": "replace", "Opt_3": "contact", "Opt_4": "expose", "Answer": "underlie", "Opt_1_def": "to be the reason for or cause of something", "Opt_2_def": "to put in or take the place of ..", "Opt_3_def": "to get in touch (e.g. by phone or email)", "Opt_4_def": "to uncover, reveal"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Many buildings ____ during earthquakes and kill the people inside.", "Opt_1": "drain", "Opt_2": "possess", "Opt_3": "collapse", "Opt_4": "transform", "Answer": "collapse", "Opt_1_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_2_def": "to have or own", "Opt_3_def": "to fall down completely and heavily; to fail", "Opt_4_def": "to change (often completely)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "This is an excellent piece of work. You forgot just one ____ - your name at the top!", "Opt_1": "detail", "Opt_2": "rank", "Opt_3": "fallacy", "Opt_4": "guarantee", "Answer": "detail", "Opt_1_def": "a small piece of information", "Opt_2_def": "position (in a list or hierarchy)", "Opt_3_def": "mistake; false belief", "Opt_4_def": "to promise or assure that something will or will not happen"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The school is planning to revive its lunchtime sports program after hearing a ____ from the student council.", "Opt_1": "adjust", "Opt_2": "request", "Opt_3": "join", "Opt_4": "import", "Answer": "request", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often in order to make something work properly)", "Opt_2_def": "to ask politely", "Opt_3_def": "to become a member (of an organization; to get together with others", "Opt_4_def": "to bring in (to a country)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "It is not ____ that he could have gained such a good grade without help from someone else.", "Opt_1": "rare", "Opt_2": "credible", "Opt_3": "ordinary", "Opt_4": "political", "Answer": "credible", "Opt_1_def": "unusual", "Opt_2_def": "believable", "Opt_3_def": "usual, typical, every day", "Opt_4_def": "to do government and politics"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "We view his behavior as very serious and we hope this ban will serve as an example.If you ____ the rules about downloading internet files, you will not be allowed to use the computer lab.", "Opt_1": "appeal", "Opt_2": "master", "Opt_3": "examine", "Opt_4": "violate", "Answer": "violate", "Opt_1_def": "to complain against an official judgment; to make a strong request", "Opt_2_def": "to (gain) control", "Opt_3_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_4_def": "to spoil or break"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "They met resistance from Nigerian government officials who did not welcome change and did not want to hear the ____ about the AidS epidemic in Nigeria.", "Opt_1": "margin", "Opt_2": "series", "Opt_3": "truth", "Opt_4": "quality", "Answer": "truth", "Opt_1_def": "amount; distance", "Opt_2_def": "a number of things, one after the other", "Opt_3_def": "actual reason or fact", "Opt_4_def": "worth or value"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The school's staff were told that they would not be getting an ____ of pay in the new year.", "Opt_1": "increase", "Opt_2": "consent", "Opt_3": "afford", "Opt_4": "presume", "Answer": "increase", "Opt_1_def": "to get bigger", "Opt_2_def": "to agree", "Opt_3_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_4_def": "to believe, assume"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The scientists that constitute the committee all work in the ____ of cancer research.", "Opt_1": "counsel", "Opt_2": "quantity", "Opt_3": "layer", "Opt_4": "field", "Answer": "field", "Opt_1_def": "advice; advisor", "Opt_2_def": "amount", "Opt_3_def": "level", "Opt_4_def": "area of interest or study"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Collecting information with no particular plan or purpose and then hoping to ____ it into a research project is not likely to succeed.", "Opt_1": "gather", "Opt_2": "transform", "Opt_3": "damage", "Opt_4": "form", "Answer": "transform", "Opt_1_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_2_def": "to change (often completely)", "Opt_3_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_4_def": "to make (into a shape)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Government ministers should not ____ on matters outside of their own domain; they often do not know enough about such topics.", "Opt_1": "programme", "Opt_2": "contrary", "Opt_3": "comment", "Opt_4": "scope", "Answer": "comment", "Opt_1_def": "a course of lessons; a project", "Opt_2_def": "opposite", "Opt_3_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion", "Opt_4_def": "extent, range"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "My father's contract in Germany will ____ at the end of the year.", "Opt_1": "indicate", "Opt_2": "terminate", "Opt_3": "verify", "Opt_4": "prepare", "Answer": "terminate", "Opt_1_def": "to show or convey", "Opt_2_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_3_def": "to prove or claim the truth", "Opt_4_def": "to get something ready (or to get ready for something)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The partners realized that their small ____ was not sufficient to support early stage start-ups in the environment of the early 2000s.", "Opt_1": "fund", "Opt_2": "gap", "Opt_3": "choice", "Opt_4": "labour", "Answer": "fund", "Opt_1_def": "money collected for a particular purpose", "Opt_2_def": "space, opening or time between", "Opt_3_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_4_def": "work"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "To ____ for the credit, fuel cells are required to be 500 watt capacity or greater with a generation efficiency of 30% or greater.", "Opt_1": "qualify", "Opt_2": "unite", "Opt_3": "supervise", "Opt_4": "impress", "Answer": "qualify", "Opt_1_def": "to become eligible", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_3_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_4_def": "to create a favourable reaction"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "A simple and often effective means to reduce blood pressure is to reduce the ____ of body fluid with a diuretic.", "Opt_1": "citizen", "Opt_2": "objective", "Opt_3": "volume", "Opt_4": "hypothesis", "Answer": "volume", "Opt_1_def": "person (member of a country)", "Opt_2_def": "aim or goal", "Opt_3_def": "amount", "Opt_4_def": "idea or prediction"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "If you ____ someone who is not qualified for the job, you cannot be surprised if they have problems.", "Opt_1": "appoint", "Opt_2": "recommend", "Opt_3": "preserve", "Opt_4": "proceed", "Answer": "appoint", "Opt_1_def": "to give a job to someone", "Opt_2_def": "to suggest something to someone because it is good", "Opt_3_def": "forward,\" said Michele Gougeon.", "Opt_4_def": "to go forward (and do ..)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "We recognize that circumstances ____ a family's control may inhibit a family's ability to contribute to educational expenses.", "Opt_1": "regarding", "Opt_2": "beneath", "Opt_3": "besides", "Opt_4": "beyond", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_2_def": "below", "Opt_3_def": "in addition to; as well as", "Opt_4_def": "further than: past"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Global warming and polar melting ____ to raise water levels and thus flood low-lying cities.", "Opt_1": "exchange", "Opt_2": "represent", "Opt_3": "threaten", "Opt_4": "associate", "Answer": "threaten", "Opt_1_def": "to give or change one thing and get a different thing", "Opt_2_def": "to be; to show or indicate", "Opt_3_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_4_def": "to link to; to make a connection to"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "The following publications are available for ____ from the Florida Solar Energy Center.", "Opt_1": "develop", "Opt_2": "perceive", "Opt_3": "purchase", "Opt_4": "confront", "Answer": "purchase", "Opt_1_def": "to grow or improve", "Opt_2_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_3_def": "to buy", "Opt_4_def": "to deal with someone or something (often a problem or unpleasant situation)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It operated below 60%, was ____ poorly designed and therefore not worth considering.", "Opt_1": "indirectly", "Opt_2": "definitely", "Opt_3": "approximately", "Opt_4": "generally", "Answer": "generally", "Opt_1_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate", "Opt_2_def": "certainly; without doubt", "Opt_3_def": "about; not exactly", "Opt_4_def": "usually"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "This is an artificial example to ____ how the method works. In real data, the sequences are much longer, and there's no mistaking a match.", "Opt_1": "illustrate", "Opt_2": "perceive", "Opt_3": "dismiss", "Opt_4": "prohibit", "Answer": "illustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to show; to make clear", "Opt_2_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_3_def": "to reject, to treat as unimportant", "Opt_4_def": "to ban, disallow"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "The amount of water that you ____ when you get into the bath is equal to the mass of your body.", "Opt_1": "displace", "Opt_2": "imply", "Opt_3": "distort", "Opt_4": "modify", "Answer": "displace", "Opt_1_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_3_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_4_def": "to change"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The developing world does not create many industrial wastes; ____ it has had little opportunity to develop proper disposal techniques.", "Opt_1": "hence", "Opt_2": "dramatically", "Opt_3": "thus", "Opt_4": "eventually", "Answer": "thus", "Opt_1_def": "so, therefore", "Opt_2_def": "very strongly, significantly", "Opt_3_def": "so", "Opt_4_def": "in the end"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "You must try to ____ a balance between work and play. At the moment it's too much play!", "Opt_1": "adapt", "Opt_2": "convert", "Opt_3": "achieve", "Opt_4": "ensure", "Answer": "achieve", "Opt_1_def": "to change (often in response to a changed situation)", "Opt_2_def": "to change from one thing to another", "Opt_3_def": "to gain or get something (often academic success)", "Opt_4_def": "to make sure (of)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "I need to ____ the importance of meeting the project deadlines.", "Opt_1": "disturb", "Opt_2": "emphasize", "Opt_3": "retreat", "Opt_4": "blame", "Answer": "emphasize", "Opt_1_def": "to interrupt, stop from working", "Opt_2_def": "to stress, to say something strongly", "Opt_3_def": "to go back", "Opt_4_def": "to accuse"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Dr. Carpenter told the jury that Hinckley was unable to ____ reality from fiction.", "Opt_1": "damage", "Opt_2": "separate", "Opt_3": "overcome", "Opt_4": "offend", "Answer": "separate", "Opt_1_def": "to spoil or break", "Opt_2_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_3_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_4_def": "to go against; to upset"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Thorough testing based on the test strategies and test plans created during the design ____ will assure that the clients receive the products they need.", "Opt_1": "phase", "Opt_2": "tradition", "Opt_3": "industry", "Opt_4": "friction", "Answer": "phase", "Opt_1_def": "a (short) period of time; stage", "Opt_2_def": "a usual, old-time way of doing things", "Opt_3_def": "area of business ( often manufacturing )", "Opt_4_def": "problems or arguments between two people or groups"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "He did not manage to develop a particularly good ____ in his own life until he was able to stop worrying about what others thought of him.", "Opt_1": "balance", "Opt_2": "mechanism", "Opt_3": "source", "Opt_4": "committee", "Answer": "balance", "Opt_1_def": "equalness", "Opt_2_def": "procedure, process", "Opt_3_def": "where something begins, where you can find something", "Opt_4_def": "a group of people meeting to discuss an issue"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "Lucy has been formed by the West Indies; she still is deeply influenced, yet she would resist and ____ that heritage.", "Opt_1": "offend", "Opt_2": "afford", "Opt_3": "deprive", "Opt_4": "reject", "Answer": "reject", "Opt_1_def": "to go against; to upset", "Opt_2_def": "to be able to pay for something", "Opt_3_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_4_def": "to refuse"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Slave remains appeared during an excavation at the ____ of these ruins.", "Opt_1": "site", "Opt_2": "quality", "Opt_3": "exponent", "Opt_4": "exercise", "Answer": "site", "Opt_1_def": "place", "Opt_2_def": "worth or value", "Opt_3_def": "someone who holds and states an opinion", "Opt_4_def": "a piece of work, activity"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The Board will consider a leave for a President for a ____ of approximately one month for each two years of service.", "Opt_1": "duration", "Opt_2": "facilities", "Opt_3": "contrary", "Opt_4": "evidence", "Answer": "duration", "Opt_1_def": "period of time", "Opt_2_def": "buildings and other places that can be used by people", "Opt_3_def": "opposite", "Opt_4_def": "proof, signs"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "You will have to ____ your documents to fit the required length.", "Opt_1": "annotate", "Opt_2": "displace", "Opt_3": "omit", "Opt_4": "edit", "Answer": "edit", "Opt_1_def": "to make notes on a piece of writing", "Opt_2_def": "to push out or take the place of something or someone", "Opt_3_def": "to leave something out or not do something", "Opt_4_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Badly- behaved students often ____ the learning of other students in the class.", "Opt_1": "supervise", "Opt_2": "anticipate", "Opt_3": "terminate", "Opt_4": "frustrate", "Answer": "frustrate", "Opt_1_def": "to control; to watch over people doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to expect", "Opt_3_def": "to finish or stop", "Opt_4_def": "to stop or prevent"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "According to him migrants and refugees do not ____ enough in Dutch society.", "Opt_1": "perceive", "Opt_2": "gather", "Opt_3": "integrate", "Opt_4": "accompany", "Answer": "integrate", "Opt_1_def": "to see; to become aware of with one of the senses; to think", "Opt_2_def": "to bring or get together", "Opt_3_def": "to fit into a new situation", "Opt_4_def": "to go with someone or something; to exist together"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The result will be an immediate and substantial ____ in the number of faculty of color who are tenured at this institution.", "Opt_1": "notice", "Opt_2": "store", "Opt_3": "apply", "Opt_4": "increase", "Answer": "increase", "Opt_1_def": "to see or realize", "Opt_2_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_3_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_4_def": "to get bigger"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "A thought- provoking ____ suggests we should expect the extinction of intelligent life on Earth soon.", "Opt_1": "limit", "Opt_2": "argument", "Opt_3": "strategy", "Opt_4": "revolution", "Answer": "argument", "Opt_1_def": "extent, boundary", "Opt_2_def": "justification or reason (for an idea)", "Opt_3_def": "a plan for how to achieve a goal", "Opt_4_def": "a time of great change"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Shortage of research space remains a significant ____ for future development.", "Opt_1": "loss", "Opt_2": "concern", "Opt_3": "constraint", "Opt_4": "feature", "Answer": "constraint", "Opt_1_def": "removal or reduction", "Opt_2_def": "worry, fear", "Opt_3_def": "to hold back; to prevent", "Opt_4_def": "part, aspect"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "If the human body is weak or cold, it is less able to ____ infection.", "Opt_1": "praise", "Opt_2": "resign", "Opt_3": "determine", "Opt_4": "resist", "Answer": "resist", "Opt_1_def": "to express approval about something someone has done", "Opt_2_def": "to give up (one's job)", "Opt_3_def": "to find out; to establish or identify; state", "Opt_4_def": "to fight against"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "What would you ____ the patient so that the injury not recur?", "Opt_1": "advise", "Opt_2": "apply", "Opt_3": "align", "Opt_4": "consist", "Answer": "advise", "Opt_1_def": "to say what someone should do; to give advice", "Opt_2_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_3_def": "to bring into line with; to make similar", "Opt_4_def": "to have in it; to have as part of it"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "Some organizations have tried to ____ without a clear hierarchy, but in most cases people want to know who their boss is.", "Opt_1": "manufacture", "Opt_2": "facilitate", "Opt_3": "exist", "Opt_4": "accuse", "Answer": "exist", "Opt_1_def": "to produce (with machines)", "Opt_2_def": "to make something easier", "Opt_3_def": "to be alive, to be in the world", "Opt_4_def": "to blame"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "A major defect in the proposal is that there is not ____ money to finance it.", "Opt_1": "sufficient", "Opt_2": "evident", "Opt_3": "compatible", "Opt_4": "reliable", "Answer": "sufficient", "Opt_1_def": "enough", "Opt_2_def": "clear", "Opt_3_def": "able to work with someone or something else", "Opt_4_def": "can be trusted, does not let you down \r\n"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "This ____ does not imply that the university will be responsible for any other expenses of the above-name student.", "Opt_1": "statement", "Opt_2": "legislation", "Opt_3": "penalty", "Opt_4": "individual", "Answer": "statement", "Opt_1_def": "a spoken sentence or sentences (sometimes prepared in advance)", "Opt_2_def": "governmental rule; law", "Opt_3_def": "negative consequence; punishment", "Opt_4_def": "one person"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The government expects to ____ resistance from some people to the prohibition of smoking in public places.", "Opt_1": "overcome", "Opt_2": "inspect", "Opt_3": "reject", "Opt_4": "disrupt", "Answer": "overcome", "Opt_1_def": "to conquer, defeat", "Opt_2_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_3_def": "to refuse", "Opt_4_def": "to interrupt an event; to damage"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "It was not the goal of this book to ____ whether America can win the war, or whether it must lose it.", "Opt_1": "discuss", "Opt_2": "drain", "Opt_3": "assimilate", "Opt_4": "force", "Answer": "discuss", "Opt_1_def": "to talk about", "Opt_2_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_3_def": "to take in", "Opt_4_def": "to make happen or to make someone do something"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "The police plan to ____ their inquiries across the border in France.", "Opt_1": "hesitate", "Opt_2": "react", "Opt_3": "pursue", "Opt_4": "compete", "Answer": "pursue", "Opt_1_def": "to pause before saying or doing something", "Opt_2_def": "to respond", "Opt_3_def": "to follow (or do)", "Opt_4_def": "to try and win against someone or something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "An employee or University student who wishes the matter to ____ a formal investigation and review should contact the EEO Officer.", "Opt_1": "receive", "Opt_2": "separate", "Opt_3": "enlarge", "Opt_4": "assist", "Answer": "receive", "Opt_1_def": "to get", "Opt_2_def": "to pull or put apart", "Opt_3_def": "to make larger", "Opt_4_def": "to help"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Solving a problem of this magnitude will ____ the collective will and shared sacrifice of all members of the university.", "Opt_1": "devote", "Opt_2": "raise", "Opt_3": "tend", "Opt_4": "require", "Answer": "require", "Opt_1_def": "to give (time) to", "Opt_2_def": "to lift; to make higher", "Opt_3_def": "to often behave in a certain way", "Opt_4_def": "to need"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "She always goes ____ what is expected of her. No wonder she gets such good grades.", "Opt_1": "against", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "except", "Opt_4": "due", "Answer": "beyond", "Opt_1_def": "opposed to; not for or in favour", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "but (not)", "Opt_4_def": "as a result of, because of"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "A ____ problem is that many companies will only employ workers with experience, but how do young people gain that experience if they are not given a job. This is called a \"vicious circle\".", "Opt_1": "typical", "Opt_2": "distinct", "Opt_3": "mobile", "Opt_4": "aware", "Answer": "typical", "Opt_1_def": "usual", "Opt_2_def": "clear and strong", "Opt_3_def": "moving; able to move", "Opt_4_def": "knowing"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She lied to the ____ and cheated in her test, but because of her family situation, it was decided to allow her to stay.", "Opt_1": "logical", "Opt_2": "principal", "Opt_3": "urgent", "Opt_4": "genuine", "Answer": "principal", "Opt_1_def": "making sense", "Opt_2_def": "most important", "Opt_3_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_4_def": "real and authentic"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "As yet there has been no ____ example of the sighting of a spacecraft from another world.", "Opt_1": "abnormal", "Opt_2": "feasible", "Opt_3": "credible", "Opt_4": "external", "Answer": "credible", "Opt_1_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_2_def": "possible", "Opt_3_def": "believable", "Opt_4_def": "outside"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Studies show that parents ____ influence the development of their child in all areas.", "Opt_1": "universally", "Opt_2": "absolutely", "Opt_3": "greatly", "Opt_4": "indirectly", "Answer": "greatly", "Opt_1_def": "all over the world; by everyone", "Opt_2_def": "completely; 100%", "Opt_3_def": "very much", "Opt_4_def": "in a indirect way; not straight or immediate"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Each graduate receives three tickets that will ____ guests into the auditorium.", "Opt_1": "admit", "Opt_2": "reform", "Opt_3": "suggest", "Opt_4": "invest", "Answer": "admit", "Opt_1_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_2_def": "to change and improve", "Opt_3_def": "to say an idea; to recommend", "Opt_4_def": "to put money into something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Newspapers ____ people to edit the articles submitted by their journalists, but not all mistakes are found.", "Opt_1": "threaten", "Opt_2": "confine", "Opt_3": "presume", "Opt_4": "employ", "Answer": "employ", "Opt_1_def": "to warn or show signs of danger", "Opt_2_def": "to limit", "Opt_3_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_4_def": "to give a job to someone; to use"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Whereas the origin of galactic magnetic fields has long posed a ____ for astrophysicists to explain, they nevertheless feel that they can say where they were not formed.", "Opt_1": "challenge", "Opt_2": "desire", "Opt_3": "scheme", "Opt_4": "role", "Answer": "challenge", "Opt_1_def": "difficult situation; problem", "Opt_2_def": "a want or wish for something", "Opt_3_def": "plan. idea, project", "Opt_4_def": "job or function"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "They argued that the law did not ____ to Cheney's task force, since all of its members were government officials, not outsiders.", "Opt_1": "disperse", "Opt_2": "rotate", "Opt_3": "apply", "Opt_4": "depart", "Answer": "apply", "Opt_1_def": "to spread out; to move apart", "Opt_2_def": "to turn or move (around)", "Opt_3_def": "to be relevant (to)", "Opt_4_def": "to leave; to be different from"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "I am surprised at the directors' ____ inability to understand how the workers are feeling.", "Opt_1": "utter", "Opt_2": "convenient", "Opt_3": "subtle", "Opt_4": "infinite", "Answer": "utter", "Opt_1_def": "complete, total", "Opt_2_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_3_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_4_def": "without an end"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "The government ____ a warning about the dangers of terrorist attack in the capital city.", "Opt_1": "attach", "Opt_2": "broadcast", "Opt_3": "succeed", "Opt_4": "threaten", "Answer": "broadcast", "Opt_1_def": "to put together with", "Opt_2_def": "to tell or transmit (often by means of a television programme)", "Opt_3_def": "to do well", "Opt_4_def": "to warn or show signs of danger"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "You are ____ going to fail the course unless you start working harder.", "Opt_1": "gradually", "Opt_2": "conversely", "Opt_3": "perhaps", "Opt_4": "definitely", "Answer": "definitely", "Opt_1_def": "slowly; steadily", "Opt_2_def": "opposite to what was just said; on the other hand", "Opt_3_def": "maybe, possibly", "Opt_4_def": "certainly; without doubt"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She was able to ____ the Smartboard screen controls so that the presentation was visible to everyone.", "Opt_1": "sustain", "Opt_2": "enforce", "Opt_3": "presume", "Opt_4": "manipulate", "Answer": "manipulate", "Opt_1_def": "to keep going; to maintain", "Opt_2_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)", "Opt_3_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_4_def": "to (use and) change"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The ASVAB is a ____ ability test given to all potential entrants to the Armed Services.", "Opt_1": "abnormal", "Opt_2": "mental", "Opt_3": "entire", "Opt_4": "ordinary", "Answer": "mental", "Opt_1_def": "not normal, unusual", "Opt_2_def": "of the brain or mind", "Opt_3_def": "whole, all", "Opt_4_def": "usual, typical, every day"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "He was absent yesterday for the third time this month. I ____ he has been having problems with his back again.", "Opt_1": "presume", "Opt_2": "procure", "Opt_3": "store", "Opt_4": "explore", "Answer": "presume", "Opt_1_def": "to believe, assume", "Opt_2_def": "to get or obtain", "Opt_3_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later", "Opt_4_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The course introduces students to the structure and function of cities and ways planners solve ____ problems.", "Opt_1": "urban", "Opt_2": "outstanding", "Opt_3": "automatic", "Opt_4": "classic", "Answer": "urban", "Opt_1_def": "of the town or city", "Opt_2_def": "excellent", "Opt_3_def": "happening by itself; happening naturally or usually", "Opt_4_def": "very good, the best or most used"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The US government is considering if it should ____ its army from Iraq.", "Opt_1": "contradict", "Opt_2": "admit", "Opt_3": "withdraw", "Opt_4": "manufacture", "Answer": "withdraw", "Opt_1_def": "to say or show that what someone has said is wrong", "Opt_2_def": "to allow to enter", "Opt_3_def": "to go back or take away", "Opt_4_def": "to produce (with machines)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Now retired and free to speak out about the scandal, Karpinski is devoting herself to publicizing her ____ of event.", "Opt_1": "custom", "Opt_2": "aim", "Opt_3": "version", "Opt_4": "asset", "Answer": "version", "Opt_1_def": "a habit (often particular to a culture)", "Opt_2_def": "goal or intention", "Opt_3_def": "form", "Opt_4_def": "advantage"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The best remedy is to change the nutrient solution every week ____ of every two weeks.", "Opt_1": "despite", "Opt_2": "beyond", "Opt_3": "instead", "Opt_4": "worth", "Answer": "instead", "Opt_1_def": "although", "Opt_2_def": "further than: past", "Opt_3_def": "in place of; rather than", "Opt_4_def": "useful; having a point or purpose"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "The prime minister has decided to ____ the planned visit to Batavia in view of the outbreak of war in the country.", "Opt_1": "cancel", "Opt_2": "circulate", "Opt_3": "insert", "Opt_4": "represent", "Answer": "cancel", "Opt_1_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_2_def": "to move from one place or person to another (often in a circle)", "Opt_3_def": "to put in", "Opt_4_def": "to be; to show or indicate"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Later in the year they plan to ____ up to 4000,00 more solar panels in a student village to be built for the university.", "Opt_1": "enlarge", "Opt_2": "attach", "Opt_3": "install", "Opt_4": "inhibit", "Answer": "install", "Opt_1_def": "to make larger", "Opt_2_def": "to put together with", "Opt_3_def": "to put in (often a machine or new system)", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent or stop"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "I think the new teacher will do very well. She has a lot of ____ with students whose first language is not English.", "Opt_1": "habit", "Opt_2": "struggle", "Opt_3": "experience", "Opt_4": "obstacle", "Answer": "experience", "Opt_1_def": "something you do regularly", "Opt_2_def": "a fight, a difficult situation to be overcome", "Opt_3_def": "knowledge and skills gained over a long period of time", "Opt_4_def": "barrier; problem"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "It is not in employers' interest to get rid of cheap illegal immigrants - only to ____ them of any rights.", "Opt_1": "dictate", "Opt_2": "deprive", "Opt_3": "advocate", "Opt_4": "distort", "Answer": "deprive", "Opt_1_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_2_def": "to take away (the opportunity)", "Opt_3_def": "to speak or write on behalf of someone or something", "Opt_4_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Scientists hope that in the future wind ____ will be able to generate 50% of the electricity we need.", "Opt_1": "power", "Opt_2": "point", "Opt_3": "minimum", "Opt_4": "aspect", "Answer": "power", "Opt_1_def": "the right or authority to do something", "Opt_2_def": "purpose; reason; value", "Opt_3_def": "the smallest amount; the least", "Opt_4_def": "environment that lifts people up,\" says Jain."}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "World leaders met in Bali to discuss global warming. Many people say that the whole ____ was a waste of time and money.", "Opt_1": "affair", "Opt_2": "magnitude", "Opt_3": "method", "Opt_4": "expense", "Answer": "affair", "Opt_1_def": "an event or series of events", "Opt_2_def": "size; amount", "Opt_3_def": "a way of doing something", "Opt_4_def": "cost"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "The library is going to ____ a new electronic system for checking out books.", "Opt_1": "introduce", "Opt_2": "combine", "Opt_3": "trust", "Opt_4": "enlarge", "Answer": "introduce", "Opt_1_def": "to talk about or bring in for the first time", "Opt_2_def": "to put or go together", "Opt_3_def": "to believe that someone or something will be or work as promised", "Opt_4_def": "to make larger"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government has set up a committee to ____ why more young people have started smoking in the last few years.", "Opt_1": "cancel", "Opt_2": "enter", "Opt_3": "demonstrate", "Opt_4": "inquire", "Answer": "inquire", "Opt_1_def": "to cut or stop from happening", "Opt_2_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_3_def": "to show", "Opt_4_def": "to ask"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "Even more extraordinary, every child ____ one was more than willing to state his or her name to the stranger.", "Opt_1": "beneath", "Opt_2": "regarding", "Opt_3": "due", "Opt_4": "except", "Answer": "except", "Opt_1_def": "below", "Opt_2_def": "about, concerning, with respect to", "Opt_3_def": "as a result of, because of", "Opt_4_def": "but (not)"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The department must ensure that all students and faculty members have access to a ____ range of learning resources.", "Opt_1": "broad", "Opt_2": "competent", "Opt_3": "enormous", "Opt_4": "probable", "Answer": "broad", "Opt_1_def": "wide, extensive", "Opt_2_def": "good at something (often a job)", "Opt_3_def": "very big", "Opt_4_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers."}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Arming the Bosnian Serbs was regarded as a ____ rather than a military issue.", "Opt_1": "political", "Opt_2": "authentic", "Opt_3": "urgent", "Opt_4": "medium", "Answer": "political", "Opt_1_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_2_def": "real, genuine; not made-up or artificial", "Opt_3_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_4_def": "in the middle"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Please ____ Einstein to your list of famous scientists.", "Opt_1": "add", "Opt_2": "blame", "Opt_3": "criticize", "Opt_4": "review", "Answer": "add", "Opt_1_def": "to include; to give or say extra", "Opt_2_def": "to accuse", "Opt_3_def": "to express disapproval; to say what you don't like or think is good about something or someone", "Opt_4_def": "to check over (and make changes)"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "China also experienced social upheaval, and was unable to ____ foreign domination of its trade.", "Opt_1": "inquire", "Opt_2": "distort", "Opt_3": "demonstrate", "Opt_4": "prevent", "Answer": "prevent", "Opt_1_def": "to ask", "Opt_2_def": "to change or affect something (negatively)", "Opt_3_def": "to show", "Opt_4_def": "to stop from doing or happening"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "She had a flash of ____ that she was going to fail her exams unless she started working.", "Opt_1": "substitute", "Opt_2": "item", "Opt_3": "insight", "Opt_4": "impulse", "Answer": "insight", "Opt_1_def": "a thing or person to take the place of another", "Opt_2_def": "thing, element", "Opt_3_def": "understanding (often of a complex problem)", "Opt_4_def": "reason or motivation to do something"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "The grade will be amended but the former grade will ____ on the record with an appropriate notation.", "Opt_1": "review", "Opt_2": "drain", "Opt_3": "remain", "Opt_4": "separate", "Answer": "remain", "Opt_1_def": "to check over (and make changes)", "Opt_2_def": "to take away; to get rid of", "Opt_3_def": "to stay; still exist", "Opt_4_def": "to pull or put apart"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Many arguments would not develop if people would ____ the words they use.", "Opt_1": "suspend", "Opt_2": "imply", "Opt_3": "appear", "Opt_4": "define", "Answer": "define", "Opt_1_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_2_def": "to mean; to give to understand", "Opt_3_def": "to come, be seen", "Opt_4_def": "to state what something is or means"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Most leadership training programs leave out the key question, ____ how leaders actually affect their groups.", "Opt_1": "predominantly", "Opt_2": "thereby", "Opt_3": "namely", "Opt_4": "seldom", "Answer": "namely", "Opt_1_def": "mostly", "Opt_2_def": "by doing this", "Opt_3_def": "specifically, that is to say ( .. used to list or explain)", "Opt_4_def": "rare"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "Caesar showed no reluctance to ____ the office of \"dictator for life\" in February 44 B.C.", "Opt_1": "dictate", "Opt_2": "maintain", "Opt_3": "impress", "Opt_4": "accept", "Answer": "accept", "Opt_1_def": "to tell someone what to do", "Opt_2_def": "to claim or state", "Opt_3_def": "to create a favourable reaction", "Opt_4_def": "to agree (to have)"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There is ____ that increases in short sale transactions precede stock price declines.", "Opt_1": "revolution", "Opt_2": "contrary", "Opt_3": "evidence", "Opt_4": "relationship", "Answer": "evidence", "Opt_1_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_2_def": "opposite", "Opt_3_def": "proof, signs", "Opt_4_def": "the way to things are connected"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "Previous studies have shown that children have ____ difficulties with mathematical equivalence problems.", "Opt_1": "urgent", "Opt_2": "technical", "Opt_3": "extraordinary", "Opt_4": "substantial", "Answer": "substantial", "Opt_1_def": "very important, must be done immediately", "Opt_2_def": "to do with machines or the way things work", "Opt_3_def": "very unusual", "Opt_4_def": "large"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "My biggest regret about the book is that Gruchy did not ____ his personal experiences explicitly into the text.", "Opt_1": "inhibit", "Opt_2": "explore", "Opt_3": "insert", "Opt_4": "interfere", "Answer": "insert", "Opt_1_def": "to prevent or stop", "Opt_2_def": "to look into a place or thing (in order to learn more about it)", "Opt_3_def": "to put in", "Opt_4_def": "to prevent; to harm"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "Under these treaties, US warships did not have to ____ the nature of the weapons they carried.", "Opt_1": "inspect", "Opt_2": "compete", "Opt_3": "declare", "Opt_4": "store", "Answer": "declare", "Opt_1_def": "to look at carefully", "Opt_2_def": "to try and win against someone or something", "Opt_3_def": "to state", "Opt_4_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "These questions are meant to help you research the ____ information you will need to evaluate some of the water quality issues in NYC.", "Opt_1": "background", "Opt_2": "scale", "Opt_3": "opportunity", "Opt_4": "privilege", "Answer": "background", "Opt_1_def": "family experiences; circumstances", "Opt_2_def": "extent", "Opt_3_def": "chance", "Opt_4_def": "a right (to do something)"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "There will be no ____ or written personal attacks on any individual or group of individuals based on age, ancestry, color, disability or handicap.", "Opt_1": "faint", "Opt_2": "inevitable", "Opt_3": "convenient", "Opt_4": "verbal", "Answer": "verbal", "Opt_1_def": "not strong", "Opt_2_def": "cannot be changed or avoided; obvious", "Opt_3_def": "easy, not causing problems", "Opt_4_def": "to do with words and language (especially the spoken language)"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "Marat used his ____ ideas to arouse the people, and set himself apart.", "Opt_1": "intrinsic", "Opt_2": "global", "Opt_3": "radical", "Opt_4": "probable", "Answer": "radical", "Opt_1_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_2_def": "world", "Opt_3_def": "extreme, strong", "Opt_4_def": "it is not probable that any thing better will be discovered than what was known to our fathers."}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "An employee or University student who wishes the matter to receive a ____ investigation and review should contact the EEO Officer.", "Opt_1": "intrinsic", "Opt_2": "dynamic", "Opt_3": "formal", "Opt_4": "considerable", "Answer": "formal", "Opt_1_def": "belonging to; inherent in", "Opt_2_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_3_def": "serious, not relaxed or everyday", "Opt_4_def": "very big; very much"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "Austen does not ____ us that a woman with Jane's mind, integrity, emotional intensity could fall and remain in love with such a dubious character.", "Opt_1": "improve", "Opt_2": "motivate", "Opt_3": "edit", "Opt_4": "convince", "Answer": "convince", "Opt_1_def": "to get better", "Opt_2_def": "to get someone interested enough to do something", "Opt_3_def": "to make changes in a piece of writing", "Opt_4_def": "to (try and) get someone to believe something"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "A ____ to save life has recently been waged at the Kwangtze Hospital in Shanghai. This ____ is not yet over, but it has already caused a great sensation.", "Opt_1": "battle", "Opt_2": "choice", "Opt_3": "symbol", "Opt_4": "surface", "Answer": "battle", "Opt_1_def": "fight, part of a war", "Opt_2_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_3_def": "a picture; the representation of an idea", "Opt_4_def": "the outside layer of an object"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "She thinks that the homeless children probably will ____ more poorly, educationally, than the children who come from homes.", "Opt_1": "fare", "Opt_2": "suspend", "Opt_3": "undergo", "Opt_4": "store", "Answer": "fare", "Opt_1_def": "to do or succeed", "Opt_2_def": "to stop (often for a short time only)", "Opt_3_def": "to receive or experience", "Opt_4_def": "to put something in a place where it can be found and used later"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "There is no point having a law if the police are not willing to ____ it.", "Opt_1": "conform", "Opt_2": "protest", "Opt_3": "culminate", "Opt_4": "enforce", "Answer": "enforce", "Opt_1_def": "to do what is required", "Opt_2_def": "to express anger or unhappiness about something", "Opt_3_def": "to end", "Opt_4_def": "to make something happen (particularly a law or regulation)"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "As life spans increase, the fraction of life spent in retirement will rise unless we ____ our exit from paid work.", "Opt_1": "delay", "Opt_2": "choice", "Opt_3": "coincidence", "Opt_4": "alternative", "Answer": "delay", "Opt_1_def": "lateness", "Opt_2_def": "decision, selection", "Opt_3_def": "an uncommon happening of two things", "Opt_4_def": "other possibility"}], [{"No": 1, "Stem": "As a consequence, it often takes many years of regular water quality data collection to statistically ____ a trend.", "Opt_1": "commence", "Opt_2": "retreat", "Opt_3": "detect", "Opt_4": "classify", "Answer": "detect", "Opt_1_def": "to start", "Opt_2_def": "to go back", "Opt_3_def": "to see, find or notice", "Opt_4_def": "to put into a category or class"}, {"No": 2, "Stem": "We will not violate the personal ____ of co-workers and customers, and will respect their right to privacy.", "Opt_1": "hierarchy", "Opt_2": "incident", "Opt_3": "property", "Opt_4": "theory", "Answer": "property", "Opt_1_def": "organizational structure (e.g. showing who works for whom)", "Opt_2_def": "happening; event", "Opt_3_def": "the things that belong to someone, especially their home", "Opt_4_def": "idea or hypothesis"}, {"No": 3, "Stem": "A very rapid response in real time is needed to ____ the optical emission while the gamma-ray burst is in progress.", "Opt_1": "record", "Opt_2": "interpretation", "Opt_3": "standard", "Opt_4": "comment", "Answer": "record", "Opt_1_def": "evidence; documentation", "Opt_2_def": "explanation; assessment", "Opt_3_def": "quality", "Opt_4_def": "a short written or spoken statement or opinion"}, {"No": 4, "Stem": "We should seriously pursue the idea of the internet elections, which are a totally ____ option.", "Opt_1": "political", "Opt_2": "preliminary", "Opt_3": "feasible", "Opt_4": "deliberate", "Answer": "feasible", "Opt_1_def": "to do government and politics", "Opt_2_def": "first; initial", "Opt_3_def": "possible", "Opt_4_def": "intentional, not by accident"}, {"No": 5, "Stem": "Shonekan was unable to ____ Nigeria's ever-growing economic problems.", "Opt_1": "enter", "Opt_2": "reverse", "Opt_3": "reward", "Opt_4": "halt", "Answer": "reverse", "Opt_1_def": "to go in or put in", "Opt_2_def": "to turn back or go back", "Opt_3_def": "to give something (e.g. a prize) for good work or behaviour", "Opt_4_def": "to stop"}, {"No": 6, "Stem": "While this was a great idea, the ____ were unclear about the requirements and how it would be graded.", "Opt_1": "belief", "Opt_2": "conflict", "Opt_3": "revolution", "Opt_4": "directions", "Answer": "directions", "Opt_1_def": "what you think; what you believe in", "Opt_2_def": "problem, struggle or battle", "Opt_3_def": "a time of great change", "Opt_4_def": "instructions"}, {"No": 7, "Stem": "The government is set to ____ a heavy defeat in the vote to approve its new tax policy.", "Opt_1": "evolve", "Opt_2": "arrange", "Opt_3": "enumerate", "Opt_4": "suffer", "Answer": "suffer", "Opt_1_def": "to develop (into something better)", "Opt_2_def": "to plan to happen; to group together", "Opt_3_def": "to list", "Opt_4_def": "to experience something bad or painful"}, {"No": 8, "Stem": "There is not a ____ answer to your question. The most complete explanation I have found is at the Howstuffworks site.", "Opt_1": "concise", "Opt_2": "dynamic", "Opt_3": "overall", "Opt_4": "willing", "Answer": "concise", "Opt_1_def": "short, not detailed", "Opt_2_def": "changing; growing; energetic", "Opt_3_def": "general", "Opt_4_def": "happy or prepared to do something"}, {"No": 9, "Stem": "The water ____ is one of the natural processes that are familiar to most students.", "Opt_1": "cycle", "Opt_2": "innovation", "Opt_3": "treatment", "Opt_4": "liberty", "Answer": "cycle", "Opt_1_def": "a complete series of events or processes", "Opt_2_def": "new object or idea", "Opt_3_def": "way of handing a person, situation or problem (often of illness)", "Opt_4_def": "freedom"}, {"No": 10, "Stem": "Traditional social skills strategies (such as board games about friendships and appropriate classroom behavior) tend to be too ____ for many children.", "Opt_1": "subtle", "Opt_2": "former", "Opt_3": "current", "Opt_4": "latter", "Answer": "subtle", "Opt_1_def": "not clear or strong", "Opt_2_def": "previous, the one before, the first of two", "Opt_3_def": "happening now", "Opt_4_def": "the second of two things mentioned"}]]